What do we do now? We can't go up any higher.
Do you have a plan?
I'm thinking about it.
Ah, I see.
This is where the real fight starts!
She's headed your way!
Did you get her?
I don't know.
Be careful.
Yeah.
Got you! Yes I did!
I was sure I'd taken off your head.
From the sound of it, I got the hard-headed nun.
It's your turn, Sawyer!
God damn it!
Revy, the knife-wielder's just a distraction. She's the real attacker.
Get going.
Of course. Helping you won't earn me one red cent.
Later.
Shit.
Get through this.
Yeah.
Feinting operation a success, miss hostage nun.
Hey, listen up, slut!
I count to ten till you throw away gun.
You'll go to hell if you let a nun die, not a good thing!
Revy! Don't worry about me and shoot her!
Nice act, nun. Slut's not inside.
Then-
Hey hey hey! Wait a second.
Listen to what I have to say.
I not stupid. Won't let you buy time.
I thought you go to hell for killing a nun.
I'm an atheist. Your religion doesn't matter to me.
Goodbye, nun!
Idiot. It's a little too early for the hell express.
Look behind you!
She's here.
She's here! She's here! She's here!
Do something about it!
Wait wait, don't panic.
Don't panic? Are you stupid?
Then, what else can we do?
A pitfall? That's just stupid!
Don't call it stupid.
The wood just in front of us is rotten.
Now...
got you.
We're almost in port.
We'll be able to see them soon.
Well, can you see anything?
Not yet.
Just the Buddha by the inlet and the city's lights.
That's...!
God damn it!
Aw shit, fuck you!
What's wrong, Dutch? Has Roanapur been nuked?
That'd be a lot better than this, God damn it!
If that'd happened, I wouldn't be the only one who lost something.
Some idiot's started a great big bonfire at my dock!
It hurts, God damn it!
Eda, you stupid nun! I can't believe you gave away that I was sneaking up on her.
Sorry.
I've been skewered!
You whore.
If I hadn't distracted her, I wouldn't have been able to shoot her.
Never mind. What's going on up top?
The ladder's no good, that ghost woman cut it down.
Damn, it hurts!
What's going on?
Who told you to start a Valencian fire festival?
Torch! My orders weren't to burn anything! It was to capture Jane!
They're on the roof.
The fire's so fierce, I can't get up there.
Come on. Come right this way.
Straight on like this.
She seems really happy for some reason.
Usually, I'd dismember you and call it good.
Jobs like this are good, every once in a while.
I won't kill you today.
What are you going to do? She started babbling!
But, I might be taking a few of your hands and feet.
I'm a cleaner.
Always cleaning up after people.
Today is different.
Today, I'm stepping over everyone to get higher.
I'm the forward. So, shall we begin?
Take responsibility for this.
How?
It's all right. I had my throat slit, but I'm still alive.
What now?
The fire got to the high octane gasoline in the dock! Damn it.
She's... still smiling!
She's going to start talking all creepy again and cut us up! Do something!
Don't be so unreasonable!
What?
What is it?
What? Explain this!
Don't be unreasonable. I don't know either!
Rock, are you all right?
What happened to that ghost woman?
Well... she's right here.
I don't really understand the situation. What did you do?
I don't really remember.
She dropped her voice machine and suddenly started acting like that.
She's one of those.
I bet she's got emotional problems.
I've seen one like this before.
This is a problem.
Hey, ghost woman.
Idiot, this is what you get for doing something you're not used to.
Revy, that wound...
Oh. It's all right. It's not as deep as it looks.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Is this building crumbling?
The dock's breaking up in the fire!
Can you seen Revy and the others?
I can't be sure.
But if we start something, they'll catch up with us.
That's how it works.
Benny!
Rush in and pull a 180 at the pier!
All right. I'm pretty good at pulling in.
Hey, hey, hey!
What's going on!
I'm here to take your life!
I have my reasons for joining this hunt.
My name is Wizard.
Rotton the Wizard!
I don't have any grudge against you, but...
Damn it. It's been completely destroyed.
Damn it.
It's the boat!
About time.
Good, it's coming in. Get to the pier!
It's them! Let's go!
Stop!
Touchdown, Dutch!
Get going, Benny!
All right!
Stop!
A few got onto the boat!
Rock! Get that woman inside!
Over here.
Oh, you're alive too.
You got the devil's luck.
Did you see that?
Mostly.
Did I look good?
You just looked like the king of idiots.
You should stop making entrances like that.
Are you all right?
Do I look like I can do the Lion Dance to you?
Next time...
you should wear a bulletproof vest.
It's good to have, just in case.
A real weapon is one of offense.
Either way, there won't be a next time with this wound.
I'll take you to a doctor.
I can't let a girl die...
right in front of me.
You're not the type to kill in this kind of city. You'd be a great host at a bordello.
I am much too clumsy for that.
If she's alive...
lets take her with us.
She's lucky, too.
Lobos! Where's that shithead Lobos?
Did you call me?
Where's Russel? Why hasn't he come back yet?
You can't ask the impossible. He's having trouble of course.
Bastard!
Do you realize how much my name is being dragged through the mud in front of Don Gerolam?
I understand how you feel, but...
You bastard!
If you've got a head capable of understanding anything,
start requesting soldiers from our homeland!
But that'll start a war with the Russians and the Chinese on this island.
Fine by me!
Take me to a phone right now! An international phone!
Please wait one moment.
There's a door here.
I'm going down, you guys take care of the gunmen.
Roger.
Damn it. I'm going back to the controls.
We don't have enough manpower, Dutch.
Tuff Hedeman: Retired world champion bull rider
I'll take them on a rodeo. Even Tuff Hedeman would be scared of this bull.
Sounds like fun, Dutch. Let me know when you're about to go wild.
Are you all right?
Sorry for rushing you.
Yeah, thanks to you I fell in head first.
Well now...
I let Dutch take over the driving.
Is she the guest?
Welcome aboard the Lagoon. Just call me Benny.
I'm Janet Bhai. Call me Jane.
Actually, we've got some uninvited guests on board, too.
So relax in my room.
The defense line for it will be short.
Oh, and please don't touch the hardware in my room.
Not a single thing.
We're about to start the rough stock.
You ready?
Wait.
Eda, hang onto this.
What is it?
All right, make this bull dance!
What do you think, Eda? You happy?
Fuck off!
Die!
One question.
Is this boat always driven like this?
It's just coincidence.
For a second, I thought your job was killing customers like this.
Bastards! Don't get excited, you bunch of punks!
You let your guard down, Revy! You're out of bullets?
If I take care of you then I'll get my wings.
Revy, here.
How did you like that rodeo?
It was great.
Don't kid around. I never want to go through that again.
Revy?
I'll take care of this one.
We've got one more that sneaked into the engine room.
Eda, take care of that one.
Got it, partner.
What is this place?
Jane! Where are you?
How long until we're at the destination port?
It's about eight hours away.
All right. That's plenty of time.
Mr. Japanese, get my PC from my bag.
You didn't have any bags.
Didn't... have any? Are you stupid?
What's the meaning of this?
I don't know. If it was so important, why didn't you take care of it yourself?
You don't get it, do you?
Get what?
Don't get rough.
You'll damage the electronics.
I can't do anything without my things!
If I don't have my PC or can't access the web...
PC!
Jane! Where are you?
Damn it, come out!
Damn, damn, damn it!
I don't have any way to move forward. How dare it mock me.
I'll show you, you stupid engine.
When this is over,
I'll drink until I get sick of it. I'll run all over Rawhide.
And I'll fuck expensive women till my balls hurt.
Way to go cowboy, I can see why they'd call you a stud.
But why don't you ask God if you should worry about your balls being blown to high heaven first?
Dutch, he's covering my field of vision with his fire.
Sounds like a pain.
I need another bull ride. Can you do it?
That guy's pretty quick for a lardass.
I'll signal you once I get him to his grave.
All right, that'll be easy enough. What are your chances?
It all depends on your timing.
I'm going!
Don't get in my way, you damned nun! I'm sick of dealing with you!
Like I care! You country bumpkin!
Then get off this boat!
Yeah right!
Shut up!
The plates are mine, shithead!
You don't have the plates?
The plates are on the ocean of the web.
All that was left was to collect all the engineering data from around the world and create it.
But because that data manager died, I can't get it out.
The encryption is automatically changed every day.
I give up.
We've already been paid by the Church of Violence, so it's OK.
But the problem is Eda.
As soon as she finds out that you don't have the plates, she'll find a new way to crucify you that would impress Christ.
You're kidding, right?
Roanapur is the kind of place where all the violence jokes come true.
Right.
Then, will you let me use your machines...
I don't want to.
Why not? Stingy, stingy, stingy!
I won't lend it to you no matter what.
I'd rather drink a pint of beer that's gone bad than let anyone use my machines.
But if I'm using them, that's a different story.
I'm a little interested in what your operator was doing.
Don't disappoint me.
If it's something a middle schooler could've come up with, I'm charging you extra.
Oh my, it's a lot of fun playing chase with a young lady like you.
But my body just can't keep up.
How about it, miss? Just give up and be burned.
It's only a moment.
My wife didn't even take five minutes.
I'll be content as long as I can smell your skin char.
This is wonderful weather, little lady.
It's perfect for a barbecue party.
Dutch, ride!
You're the rocket man, baby!
I understand. This boat is really out to kill me.
It really is just a coincidence.
I see. At least let me see the data before I die.
It's not an IFSR or an exchange code. My gut tells me it's a ghost type.
We could also cause a buffer overflow and take control quickly. But using force isn't very elegant.
Who cares about elegance?
Don't rush.
I'm running six paths in parallel against the ghost.
If one of the indicators on the screen is a hit, it'll start downloading soon.
By the sound of it, my partner took care of fatty.
You're the only one left, cowboy.
If you resist, I'll blow your head off and toss you in the ocean.
I got it, I got it.
Damn it, This isn't even amusing any more. How could I possibly go back to the boss?
There's no need. Lobos will take care of it.
He knows how things work here really well.
That bastard Lobos?
Take care of Mr. Elvis?
Like he could do that...
What?
Wait a second, I've seen you before.
In Florida... no, that's not it. I know, in Dirty City, in Washington D.C. I'm sure of it!
Is that so?
I don't know you.
I was born in Alabama. I've never even been to D.C.
Then I've met a woman who looked just like you.
You've been wearin' those sunglasses and that outfit so I never recognized you.
When was it?
When Don Gerolam was in D.C. It was him. That man!
Hey, you better stop, cowboy.
It's just your mistake anyway.
I remember! That stupid senator, Jack Bonham!
Tally ho! It was a ghost!
You're operator was skilled, but he's not thorough enough.
I'm as great as Kevin Mitnick. Yeah, yeah! I'm amazing!
Kevin Mitnick: Notorious computer hacker active in 80s and 90s
Now then, I won the bet.
What's my prize?
Hey, hey... you're so cute and sexy.
That woman... was wearing a navy blue suit, right?
She came into contact with the senator, with several men.
In a French restaurant named Fountainbleu.
Yeah, the Foutainbleu!
But why were you with a senator?
At that time, she and her superiors were talking about contact...
with foreign countries within the EAC that opposed NAFTA.
And how to deal with them.
You couldn't be...
It's your mistake. She's someone else.
I'm just a damned nun from the Church of Violence.
But I'll tell you one thing that's true.
I wasn't born in Alabama. My home is Langley, Virginia.
You're CIA?
You sure took your time.
Yeah.
Did you send him to Hell?
We're almost in port. Let's take it easy.
Oh yeah.
God's in his heaven, and all's right with the world.
So, I'm going out for a little while.
Then I'm coming, too.
Partner.