It should be daybreak there soon.
The sea at daybreak.
Appreciating that is something a worthless student would do.
But it is a disgusting winter sky.
Right now, Okajima-kun is in the Sea of Heaven.
Would you prepare two plane tickets?
Yes sir.
A business trip, sir?
Let us go there as well, to the Sea of Heaven.
Why do I need to suffer like this?
Rock, you bastard!
How much do you think a gun costs?
They came here to kill me.
Why is the Department Chief causing me to go through this?
You have something mixed up.
They want to destroy that data disk, right?
Your life is just-
My life is just an accessory to that. Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
You know, there's a torpedo in there.
Shut up!
Doesn't this seem weird to you, Benny?
Yeah, something's weird, Dutch.
They're not shooting at all now.
They should be able to make us into swiss cheese.
I agree. Something's strange.
Dutch! What's going on?
Where'd they go?
Benny-Boy.
They're 5,000 meters behind us and they're keeping that distance.
What are they after?
Something...
Damn it.
The water way!
Yeah, the water way.
The path from here to Balawan is filled with rocks and mangroves.
If we keep going it's just going to get tighter.
In the end we won't even be able to take evasive maneuvers.
Let's bolt.
Yeah.
Don't say that I suck at this.
I guess it doesn't matter now.
I won't say it.
I had no choice but to evade to the right.
I know.
We drove into the mouth of a river?
Isn't this a river?
Won't we run out of places to run if we keep going?
We know that.
We've been completely trapped.
The enemy got behind us again.
He's looking down on us from 5,000 meters back.
Look at that: A sunken ship. Fucking inauspicious.
This is fine.
We'll stay here.
Go on, go on.
Show me your asses and go on.
But, you guys will come back to me.
And then you'll have to face me.
Hurry up and come back!
Let's end this.
Dutch, they've stopped by the sunken ship.
They're not chasing us.
So there's no point in even giving chase.
That's what it means.
Damn it.
A dead end.
Seems like it.
Damn it!
Hey, Mayer.
Yes?
Don't you get excited when you wonder how they'll react in this crisis?
They don't have a chance.
They'll become a beehive before our superior weaponry.
That's why I can't wait to see how they'll react.
If they're boring and won't even try, then we'll just torture them to death.
There's no road ahead of us.
We'll have to turn around and go back.
But he'll be waiting for us.
My gut tells me they set this ring.
They want to finish this face to face.
So, who's going to ring the gong?
Sometimes you'll find them around.
Ancient bastards who think they're gunmen.
Wait a sec!
So the only choice left is to die?
Well calm down, calm down, Rock.
Let's call the police. That's better than dy-
You're helpless. Calm down.
Nothing's gonna get solved if you panic.
If you want to survive use your head, your head!
Dutch, how about waiting for them to run out of fuel?
The bastards are from E.O. They'll come to finish us before that happens.
Damn it.
Why did it end up like this?
Not this one.
I'd like a business paper.
I want to check on my stocks.
Understood, Kageyama-sama.
How's the damage to the ship?
Nothing much so far.
I'm just worried about that.
If even one round hits the torpedo we'll fly to the moon.
It's your own fault for keeping it on the ship, you dumbass.
I thought, I might have been able to use it for something.
It's a waste, but let's just throw it overboard.
I guess we don't have a choice.
What a waste.
Wait.
Dutch, listen to me.
Just stay asleep.
I understand something, now that I've thought about it.
Hear me out.
If you bother my thought process, I'm gonna let Revy nail you again.
Then let's have a shoot out, face to face.
Are you an idiot?
Shoot out?
At most we have an anti-tank rifle.
They have rockets!
It looked like that chopper had heat-seeking homing missiles.
Damn it. We're not even close.
You think so?
We've got something.
Revy, what did you give him to drink?
It wasn't me.
It's a head-on game of chicken right?
This ship's speed and armaments, that sunken ship, they're all here.
What...
...are you thinking?
What you guys were just talking about.
Let's fly them to the moon.
Impossible.
There's no way we can do it.
By all accounts this ship is made to accelerate quickly.
At full speed we're only this much into the water.
Dutch, we don't have anything else.
I'm in.
The plan won't work unless they're right in front of us.
Do you have any guarantees, Rock?
They're having a blast chasing us around.
Despite having a complete advantage.
What reason would they have to restart the whole fight?
You said it yourself.
He's the type to imagine himself as a gunman.
If we start a chicken race, he'll face us.
I don't have any guarantees. From this point on, it's up to you as Captain.
We sure picked up one crazy son of a bitch.
You've got to be insane.
But this is exciting,
and being exciting is an important thing, Rock.
Let's do it!
The radar, Captain!
They've started moving.
Let's take their challenge.
Rock!
Do you know what you're doing?
If they fire a rocket, fire the signal flare away from the ship.
Correct!
I see our dumbass.
Revy!
It's a chicken race! Make them play!
They're shooting!
Of course they are!
Exciting! I accept!
Rock! It's coming!
Use the flare gun!
We did it.
We're on the alpine course.
Both of you get in the cabin.
They plan on using the sunken ship as a shield. Useless.
Mayer.
Sir!
When we cross paths we'll get them in one shot.
We're going to end this duel.
I'm gonna fuck you baby!
300 feet left.
150.
100!
Fire #1! Fire #2!
I fucked you!
My head's not torn off.
My sunglasses aren't broken.
Amen, hallelujah, peanut butter.
Lordy lord fucking Christ.
I'm never doing this again.
Benny? You ok?
I'm alive somehow.
But the instruments are messed up.
We need to fix them up. We're-
Hey! How about Rock?
He's out cold over there.
Right before we hit, he howled.
Like a line by William Holden out of "The Wild Bunch".
And he looks so comfortable sprawled out like that.
No kidding.
When that moment passed, the excitement from the adrenaline faded away.
My boiling blood had gone back to normal.
Where am I?
And what am I doing here?
Good job.
Smart business is lovely, Dutch.
But, you look terrible.
It's like we're going to a Soho social.
Leave us alone.
Then, Mr. Kageyama.
We at Hotel Moscow have a code of honor.
Oh? I thought you were the Burgenbiria Trade Company?
We followed through in our own way.
There shouldn't be any grudges.
The world is full of things that can't be helped.
Now, it's your turn to follow through in your own way.
We'll cover the details at the hotel.
Understood.
Good job, Okajima-kun.
Now, let's go.
Okajima-kun? What are you doing? Come on.
Department Chief, don't you remember?
I'm already dead.
You told me so.
My name is...
My name is Rock.
I see. As you wish.
Let's go, Fujiwara-kun.
Yes sir.
Rock?
I apologize for making you stay with those idiots.
But, it'd be a waste to keep such a tough guy as a Japonski.
Come to us, if you ever need help.
Take care.
Okajima-kun...
He is no longer an employee.
A manager should no longer care.
But, why so suddenly?
It doesn't matter.
So, Rock...
What will you do now?
I'm not a hostage anymore.
I've got nowhere to go.
I know a place that could use a sailor.
Are you interested?
They're a delivery company...
...and brush against the law from time to time.
Right?
What's wrong?
There's a boat that's blocking our way.
We're blowing our horn but it's not moving.
What is it?
Well, it couldn't be helped, to let that little bit leak.
We were prepared for that much.
Job well done, Kageyama-kun.
Thank you very much.
Testing, testing.
Good morning everyone aboard the St. Joan.
Why don't you wear the aloha shirt I got for you at the market?
Because, we're on the job.
This has become my job now.
Everyone of the St. Joan, I apologize for the sudden request but...
...please stop your ship.
My personal opinion is that-
Complying with the request as quickly as possible, would be the best course of action!
Dutch, the St. Joan have opened up their communications.
We made contact.
And, what did they say?
Unless we get out of their way, they will force their way through.
It can't be helped.
Ok, Benny.
Revy?
I couldn't wait.
The time for being a gentlemen is over.
Everyone, please take cover!
These moments make my prehistoric blood awaken.
What was that?
They have a rocket launcher!
Give it here!
Stop it!
Listen up limp-dicks!
My rockets are faster than electric signals!
If you don't want to end up as a blood filled ghost ship, then stop, you shit-heads!
Benny-Boy, report to the Lun-i Pan that we've taken the St. Joan,
and that they need to come get it before anyone starts a ruckus.
Roger.
I'm home.
Ohh, John. Good boy.
Takanori, how's it going,
with your studies for college acceptance?
Not very well.
Are you home today?
About your daughter, she's been coming home late.
She's only 18. Will you say something to her?
Isn't that your job?
Stocks.
Daddy?
What color was the sea, when you went to the south on your business trip?
Color of the sea?
I don't know.
Daddy was busy with work.
No one may believe me, but...
...I became a pirate in the South Seas.
That huge ship was today's prey.
Let's get back to port before lunch.
The China bowl at Tao Han...
...sells out fast.
We're being targeted by pirates?
What's the background on our client?