For this past year, these are the places I have woken up in with hangovers:
Sometimes in the cabin on a torpedo boat.
But here was my lair.
A cheap hotel room looking over downtown Roanapur.
For the first time in a year, I'll leave this country for a far off place.
A place that is far removed from the current me.
That country...
Is that you, Rock? Happy new year.
It doesn't really feel that way here, though.
Just the Chinese's fireworks.
Yeah.
Everything's decorated nicely for the new year here.
How's Revy doing?
All she does is complain.
Tokarev: A gun of Soviet origin
She didn't like the Tokarev she was given. She was in a bad mood over that yesterday, too.
You sure are a lady's man.
She came with you because she was worried in her own way, right?
Yeah.
It's almost time.
I'll call you again later.
It's snowing.
New York gets it worse,
but it feels familiar.
Since I left that city, it's been a long time that I haven't seen snow,
How do you like Japan?
I've been hit on by a few guys already.
Gaijin: Japanese word for foreigner
When I talk back, they make a funny face and keep calling me a "gaijin".
This country pisses me off.
Today is the first time we meet face to face.
Thank you for coming all this way.
These are my men.
So, how should I address you?
Just Balalaika is fine.
I've heard everything from Laptev.
We've been eager to create a base of operations in Tokyo for some time.
I do appreciate your assistance.
If you guys form a team with us, there'll be nothing to fear.
As you must have heard, the Kanto Peace Council wants to keep foreigners out.
Mr. Laptev from Russia was thrown out because of that.
So I thought...
we'd hold out a helping hand.
I thought the Washimine Group was part of the Council.
There's only so much one will suffer for obligation's sake.
We've paid a lot of tribute to the Kousa Council.
And I think we've done a lot for the Peace Council.
But we can't stay at the bottom of the pile simply out of obligation.
Our interests are mutually beneficial, Mr. Bando.
You wish to expand your influence with our power.
We will light a new fire in this city.
You're quick to understand.
If you suppress the Kousa Council with your power, then the Peace Council can do nothing about us.
Our emblem still has some power behind it.
I hear you're most used to being in a fire, out of all the Russians.
You are curious about our forces?
Our forces are nothing like those of this nation.
We are the military.
It's me. Are you in position?
Good.
Mr. Translator.
She's switched to Russian.
Perfect.
Begin.
To start things off, we've blown up one of the clubs owned by the Kousa Council.
Blown up? You idiot! What were you thinking?
Intimidation with handguns is pointless.
This is how we at Hotel Moscow show force.
We destroy everything that is in our path. That is why we are here.
Fine by me.
It's one hell of a firework to start off the Washimine Group's fight.
I like you, Miss Balalaika.
3rd  at  6pm,  an  explosion  occurred  at  Kabuki  Town.
All those yakuza were paralyzed with fear.
I finally get to come back, but that was too much.
I wish they wouldn't make my country into a war zone.
She was in a really great mood.
There hasn't been a big fight in Roanapur lately.
She's the type to give up fucking if there's a war to be had.
There's something wrong with her.
They're war maniacs.
They left a few screws back in Afghanistan.
Hey Rock, what's that?
They have a fair up. It's almost the new year.
So it's a carnival. Sounds like fun.
Thanks.
I don't see any Ferris wheels.
We don't have those at Japanese fairs, Revy.
Here you go!
Thanks.
That's the third one!
I guess you're living up to the name of Two Hands.
You got that right. Who do you think I am?
As Miss Rebecca, I have no equal with a gun.
That's the fourth.
It's a shame I don't have my Cutlass. I could close this shop down in three seconds.
Of course, this is the hardest country in the world to have a gunfight in.
And you can't bribe the cops here like in Roanapur.
If we get thrown in, it's the...
You remembering something?
Like what?
Who do you mean "like what"? This is your country.
Don't you have anyone, like...
family or such?
It's not like you were born from a crotch of a tree.
I thought snoops weren't well liked.
It's nothin'.
I was wondering what you were thinking.
You looked like you were thinking hard.
From the time when you pulled a gun on me, on that boat...
It's already been a year.
Yeah.
I don't understand it. This is a place I knew well...
but I feel like I don't know it at all.
My family doesn't get along.
My older brother turned out well and got a government job.
I didn't get into college at first and ended up in a company.
They didn't expect much of me.
I guess they really didn't care.
But your folks are alive, right?
At least contact them.
You haven't been arrested yet.
This is your only chance.
If you keep this up, one day you won't be able to see them anymore.
From our point of view, you have a normal family.
Isn't it worthwhile to go home?
You've got this far without stealing or killing.
Don't misunderstand me.
I'm just saying you should at least go see their faces.
Can't say I'm really normal.
I'm hanging around you guys, right?
What?
All right! One more and I get the high score!
Damn it, I bet it's weighed down!
Hey hey!
Got it! Hey, Rock!
She says she took first place, so give me the prize.
No, no. She can't cheat.
He says it doesn't count,
since you knocked it over by poking it.
What, you bastard?
What the hell? Speak Japanese!
What the hell are you saying?
Revy, cut it out!
We're in Japan! Speak Japanese!
Mr. Gin...
Miss Customer, 'scuse me.
We're in the middle of new year's week.
Why don't we all just have fun?
Please lay your aggression aside.
Who the hell?
Revy! Let's go! We're being a nuisance.
Rock, baby. Are you taking his side?
You shouldn't be so unreasonable.
Life is short, and we'd all just like to enjoy it.
You had your fun.
Could you take this opportunity to save face?
Ummm...
Ummm, sweet wine...
Would anyone like sweet wine?
It's cold and standing around in the cold is a bit...
Miss...
Yes, I agree.
I don't like fighting, so lets do that.
So, how did we end up like this?
Come on.
Besides, there's nothing to gain from making a big scene.
I'm not even in the mood anymore.
I'm really glad it calmed down.
Ummm, well. I-I'm sorry.
Please go ahead.
Well...
You look like a student, or are you a vendor?
Well, yes.
They're both correct.
My father was...
My father was a vendor.
He is...
Mr. Ginji was like my father's student.
If there's an argument here, everyone goes to Mr. Gin.
He's big, isn't he?
Before he realized it, he was the arbitrator of Takamachi.
I see.
I thought I would come help close shop after my college entrance exam class.
So I was a little shocked.
She's just ultra short-tempered.
I'm just glad it didn't cause a big scene.
Is she...
Japanese?
She's Chinese-American.
How to say it...
she works with me.
I came to translate for a Russian, and she came with me.
An international occupation is impressive.
Not so much.
It's a small company and always troublesome.
It's a lot of work and very dangerous.
It's dangerous?
Yeah, something like that.
What's with him?
Missy, you're not a decent woman are you?
It's those eyes.
Those aren't good eyes.
Those are the eyes of a dog.
You're the same as me.
You stink of blood and guts.
It's getting cold.
Miss, if it gets too cold, it won't be good for your body.
All right.
Farewell.
That's how we met.
Oh, what's your name?
It's Yukio.
Yuki as in snowman and O as in sandal straps.
I...
that day, I didn't know how powerful darkness was.
02:30.
We assaulted a Kousa Council office.
Result: 12 kills, no fatalities, no casualties.
All men had left the scene by 02:37.
I could have them prepare Russian tea.
No, I don't like making a fuss.
How about toast?
Would you like some, Sergeant?
No, I am fine.
Don't skip breakfast, Sergeant. It's not healthy.
When did the police force intervene?
The scene started to be closed off at 03:05.
They are on a heightened security status.
I had a member of the Washimine Group transcribe their wireless communications.
We must wait for Rock's translation for the details.
The reliability of the information could mean life or death.
Have him translate it immediately.
As I would expect from Balalaika.
I see why Boss Slevenin acknowledges you.
Whose ass do you think I'm wiping, Vasily?
You dragged the face of the organization through the mud.
I want to wrap up the operation here and get back to Roanapur.
That place is full of gunpowder. I can't leave it alone for long.
See you in six hours then.
Don't get high and mighty, Balalaika!
I'm one of the bosses back in Moscow.
Oh, I'm sorry. It's hard to remember those who rose up through money instead of skill.
I better write your name down on a dollar bill so I can remember.
Keep barking, you ex-military bitch!
I'm warning you.
There are two things in this world I can't stand.
Blintz: a thin pancake of Slavic origin, similar to a crêpe
Cold blintzes,
and idiotic ex-KGB shitheads.
Live with your head low so the bullets won't hit you.
Boss.
I think kids nowadays would rather have  those video games than these.
How long do you think you'll have to endure this?
This is the job of a vendor.
I think it's better than selling meth or women.
Do you think I do this because I want to?
When the old man died, he left us this group that can barely get tribute.
Then only reason we've come this far is because the old man and the Kousa Council's last head took each other as brothers.
Now that they're gone...
those bastards haven't let anyone take the head of our group, even after three years.
We're the only ones left with any sense of obligation to the old man.
He took care of me when I came from the Kyoto-Osaka district.
That is why we need to do something.
Gin, you said that dealing with low-lives was a shame upon a yakuza.
But that only matters if we have a name.
That's not what he said.
I'm pulling off a big job right now.
Joining up with the Russians to take out the guys above us.
Boss, do you know what you're saying?
They tried to take us out first!
But, Russians are Russians no matter where they are.
They don't have a shred of honor.  So we need to take care of what we can.
So what are you saying?
I want you to take it up again...
that white scabbard.
The name that still puts fear into all yakuza.  "Man-slayer Ginji".
Won't you show it to me once more?
Boss...
I am grateful that you're looking after the Miss.
I understand what you're saying.
But...
what you're saying now doesn't have a shred of justice.
When I held the white scabbard for the old man, he had that.
I see. Too bad, I'll come again.
Those Russians,
did they bring their own translator?
Yeah, they did.
What kind of guy was he?
Young guy with a pretty but ill-bred looking girl.
Well, he didn't look like anything more than a normal guy.
If I had to make an analogy,
he looked like the guy who brings the bird, soup, onions, pot, and even the stove to a violent bar.
So, I'll be gone for a while.
Hurry up and go! Shoo!
I'll wait for ya, but not for long.
Just until I finish this.
After that, I'm gone, partner.
OKAJIMA
The sky looks the same no matter where you are.
Here... at Mott Street...
Amazing!
That's really amazing!
It's like magic!
Just like Annie Oakley, right?
Jack McCall! I'm here to avenge Wild Bill!
Can you defeat me, Jane?
Now, come at me.
We were defeated.
That's not how people go down when they're shot. They only go down like that in movies or TV shows.
In reality, you suddenly lose all your strength. Understand?
Like everything below your knees disappears, your feet stagger, and you go head first.
I'll show you an example.
You there.
That's not very cool looking, sis.
It's always like this when you die.
It's never that cool.
What are you doing?
How long have you been watching?
Since about the time you charged into the Deadwood Saloon.
The story is different than the one I remember.
"buy the farm": slang term meaning to die
Calamity Jane didn't buy the farm in the saloon.
Damn it...
My toy gun!
Listen up!
You tell Dutch or Benny about this, and I'll cut off your balls and pole and feed them to you!
I won't! I won't say a thing!
And?
Did you meet your folks?
Well, I went to their house...
but, I didn't see them.
They weren't home.
What is it?
Nothing.
But we still have a few days.
You're right.
Why doesn't he go home?
It's like this place was made for him.
Geez, this guy...
Boss! The Russians aren't holding back!
They blew something else up today!