Scar appears in Central once again.
In order to lure out the Homunculi, Ed and Al work with Ling in order to purposely attract Scar's attention.
The plan works, and Gluttony and Wrath make their appearances.
However...
Ran Fan!!!
You deflected the slash with your kunai, eh?
Can I eat her?
Make it quick.
Ran Fan! Pull yourself together!
You think you can escape my eye?
Seems you're quite experienced.
He's constantly trying to bring his attack toward my left side, my blind side.
Gluttony!
Roger!
Now, no one can see us here.
I've got a lot to ask you.
Just what are you folks?
How can you tell what's inside Gluttony?
You're still trying to escape in this situation?
If you throw that extra baggage away,
I bet you'll be able to save your own tail.
Baggage, you say?
You're the highest ranking man in this country, right?
If I remember correctly, your name is Führer President King Bradley.
The king exists for his people.
Without his people, there is no king.
King Bradley, you'll never be able to become a true king!
You're far too inexperienced.
There is no such thing as a true king!
You rely on your eye too much!
From the draft, the exit should be...
What's wrong?
I still have this eye, you know!
Winry.
We'll be back soon.
So be good now, you hear?
Winry.
We're here.
Maybe I was thinking of Mr. Hughes as my dad...
Come see him every now and then, okay?
He always hated being alone.
Miss Gracia...
I heard the Elric Brothers are fighting!
What? Again?!
Military police are running all over the place!
What are they fighting over this  time?
Geez...
Apparently, they're fighting against that guy who only goes after State Alchemists.
They still haven't caught him yet?
What the heck is the army doing?
No... What am I thinking?
A dead end!
Dammit!
Nice, my little brother!
Shut up and run!
Have we been given permission to engage yet?!
Not yet, sir!
Dammit! What's going on?!
We haven't gotten the signal from Lin yet.
Brother is starting to get tired, too.
I should buy some time.
Scar! You use alchemy, too.
Why are you so against alchemists
with the mindset they oppose God?!
I told you in East City.
There are ones like you, who create, and ones like me, who destroy.
You...
You just want to justify murder by using God's name!
Didn't you kill Shou Tucker and Nina by acting as God's hand?!
I see. So you guys saw that chimera, too.
Techniques that give birth to such tragedy...
Is that the alchemy you fools so worship?!
You turned your brother into that form...
...with your own hands.
Techniques that bring about the creation of matter...
Isn't that the vanity which gave birth to that chimera?!
Even so...
Why did you have to kill her?!
Why did you take her life?!
I'm sure you fools understood it, too.
That chimera would never have been able to return to her original state.
If I had let her be, she would have received
the same treatment as other experimental animals,
and she would never have been treated as a human again.
That's right. Back then, we knew in our hearts
there was a possibility Nina would be experimented upon.
We were just postponing a problem we didn't know how to solve.
We didn't do anything...
Nothing...
As you say, we, alchemists, have done wrong.
But still, we can't approve of what you're doing either!
Do you recognize...
...the name of an Amestrian doctor, Rockbell?
They went to Ishbal during the civil war and continued to treat Ishbalans even after orders were given to destroy the country.
Wait, Brother!
Do you remember the couple who saved you,
which you killed shortly after?!
Brother!
What do you mean?
Winry...
This man...
...killed Dad... and Mom?
No way...
They were killed... by one of their patients?
Why?
What did Dad and Mom do?
They didn't do anything to deserve to die... did they?
Give them back...
Give back Dad and Mom!!!
Wait, Winry.
Don't...
You can't do that!
Winry!
Please, stop!
I understand your resentment.
But all revenge does is give birth to more revenge.
You must persevere.
You're those doctors' daughter, huh?
You have every right to shoot me.
Brother!
Brother! The army is already nearby!
Forget about your research and-
Hang on. I'm almost done.
What is that tattoo?
Oh, this?
The basics of alchemy are understanding, decomposing, and reconstructing.
My right arm is for decomposing,
and my left arm is for reconstructing.
I researched Eastern Alchemy and arranged it myself.
What I realized from that...
...is that this country's alchemy is a bit strange.
Who cares?!
More importantly, the army's-
Hey.
Why are you stopping me?!
We need to get out of here immediately!
Please, restrain yourself.
Your brother's research may save Ishbal.
What?
Did you hear about the State Alchemists?
They're using their horrifying powers as
weapons of war and are laying waste to Ishbal.
Even though we're citizens of Amestris, too...
I know that, but...
What does that have anything to do with my brother?
Your brother may discover a way to gain power enough to face those State Alchemists...
...and perhaps even enough to destroy their army!
With power that far surpasses theirs...
To retaliate against them with alchemy!
Make them pay for their sins with blood!
Look, Brother.
This is the alchemy that you've been devoting yourself to.
Even if you wish for your efforts to benefit the people and for happiness...
No one views it the same way!
So this is alchemy...
You think something like this will save Ishbal?
Something like this, which creates an endless cycle of destruction and slaughter?!
Oh no!
Father! Mother!
You were safe!
Yes, we're fine.
It's a good thing we were out getting ready to escape.
I made it in time!
I was compiling all my critical papers, so I was a bit late.
Critical papers?
You hold on to this.
What is this?
My research.
This was all I could bring.
Take it and run.
Hang on-
If something were to happen to me,
all my research would go to waste.
Why don't you hold on to it yourself and run?!
You're a powerful monk and have gone through rigorous training.
You have a better chance of surviving than I do.
Look.
My legs won't stop trembling.
I'm a pathetic older brother.
Brother...
A soldier?!
Transmutation circles?!
A State Alchemist!
Get down!
Hang in there...
Don't die!
D-Dammit... It won't stop bleeding...
His arm...
Where is his arm...
Dad...
Mom...
Everyone... Someone...
Live...
You can't die.
I'll show them the honor of an Ishbalan!
If you really feel that way, then run!
That's right! I didn't treat you to let you die!
You, too, Doctor! You have to flee with your wife...
You're a patient! Don't be worrying about us!
Brother...
Get down!
No way...
He... shielded me?
Brother...
If you have the strength to escape, do so!
He woke up!
Don't move! Your wounds will re-open!
Dear, come!
Dear!
You have to rest!
Someone! Get that cart!
Please, take him with you!
Brother, is that you?
Thank goodness... Brother was safe-
What the hell is this?!
Sedatives!
We're out! We used them up on that other boy!
State Alchemists...
Amestrians...
I won't forgive them...
You... You guys...
Dr. Rockbell!
Shoot me.
Don't shoot, Winry!
Put the gun down!
You shouldn't hold something like that!
Winry!
Shoot me.
But if you do, I'll take you for an enemy that very instant.
Scar!!!
If you lay a finger on Winry, I'll-
Kill me?
That's fine, too.
The chain of hatred will not end unless one of us dies.
But don't forget this!
The ones who first pulled the trigger in that civil war were you...
...the Amestrians!
No! Don't shoot!
Put the gun down and leave this place!
Winry!
If you can't shoot, then get out of here.
You're in the way!
Don't shoot!
Get down!
Brother...
You stupid brother! What are you doing?!
Are you trying to get both of you killed?!
Hurry and get Winry to a safe place!
Winry, let go of the gun.
I couldn't shoot...
Please don't shoot. I'm begging you.
But... he killed Dad and Mom!
He tried to kill you and Al, too...
But why?!
You helped a woman give birth in
Rush Valley, and saved her and her baby.
You gave me an arm and leg so I could stand again.
Your hands aren't meant for killing people.
They're for helping them live.
So...
Must one throw something away to protect someone?
And those not prepared to do so will lose both and fall?
No.
The resolve to protect will spread to all and outshine the disaster.
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Episode 23, The Girl on the Battlefield.
I won't show tears of sadness...
...because I promised not to.