Ed and Al infiltrated the former Research Laboratory 5,
seeking the secret of the philosopher's stones.
There, they encountered people who had their souls affixed to suits of armor.
Due to what Number 66 said during their battle, Al started to question whether he was a faux soul, created by Ed.
Looks like you're able to get up now.
What happened to Research Laboratory 5?
About that...
It was blown up by someone and has been completely destroyed...
Dammit!!! It's all gone?!
O-Oww...
D-Dammit...
I was so close to the "truth", too!
I can't be sitting in a hospital like this!
Mr. Fullmetal Alchemist!
We apologize for the rudeness in advance!
Huh?
Doing whatever you wanted...
If things had gone badly, you would have died!
Instead of trying to do everything by yourselves, rely on the people around you!
It wouldn't hurt to trust your elders, don't you think?
That is all!
Please forgive our rude language and violence toward a higher-ranking officer, sir!
N-No...
My fault.
Punishment... for the slap, sir?
No, I wouldn't dream of it!
Why do you guys try to be so considerate around me?
Because being a State Alchemist is equivalent to being a Major in the army.
I didn't get my state qualification for something like that.
You guys don't need to be so polite to me, either.
Oh, really?
Wow, all those times have been a waste, haven't they?
What a quick change!
Oh... now that I think about it, where's Al?
I scolded him with a fist earlier.
Ow...
I forgot about the other person who's going give me a scolding.
Hello? You've reached the Rockbells,
specializing in prosthetics and orthotics.
Ed?
It's rare for you to call.
U-Umm...
This is extremely difficult for me to say, but...
Do you mind taking a trip to Central for a little maintenance?
Trip?
Well...
It's my right arm.
My fingers move, but I can't lift my arm at all.
So it was no good, after all.
Huh?
No, no, it's nothing.
Did you do something before your arm stopped moving?
I-I was in an all-out brawl.
AGAIN?! Quit using my automail for things like that!
H... Hello?
Miss Winry?
I guess there's no choice.
Where in Central?
Hey, you're kind of nice tod-
I mean... Nothing...
Okay. Gotcha.
Sorry for the trouble.
Yeah.
Thanks.
A love call to your girlfriend?
Who's my girlfriend?!
How boring.
When I was your age, I had...
Huh?
What are you doing over there?
Hey, Al!
Brother...
Want to head to our room?
Hm?
No, it's nothing.
I'll meet you there.
Okay.
Bye!
...maybe you're an armor doll that your "brother" created?
Oww, my rear...
I don't see how Ed and Al can ride these things all the time.
He said there'd be someone waiting for me at the
west gate, and I'd be able to spot him right away, but...
Oh.
Major Armstrong!
Ah, Miss Winry!
Where are those stupid Elric brothers?
To tell you the truth...
Ed's in the hospital?!
Th-That was fast.
You're planning on charging me a rush fee, aren't you?
But... you were injured this badly when your automail broke, because I...
...I didn't equip it properly, right?
I-It's not your fault or anything!
I'm the one who used it recklessly,
and the maintenance was perfect, as always.
He didn't notice the missing screw?
And there's also the fact I didn't have to get hurt more because my arm broke!
So don't worry about it! Yeah? Yeah?
So it all works out?
Okay, so about this maintenance trip!
On second thought, I'll be charging a rush fee!
Huh?
You didn't drink your milk.
I... don't like milk.
And that's why you're so short!
Shut up!
I can't help that I don't like it!
You're being picky, Edward Elric!
All the kids drink it.
You won't get any girls if you can't drink milk.
Al?
Al's been acting strange lately.
What do you mean by strange?
Seems to me something's on his mind.
...maybe you're an armor doll that your "brother" created?
Just accept it. It'll make you feel better.
There! Maintenance complete!
Awesome!
It's finally fixed.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
Yo, Ed!
So I heard you're kind of occupied after bringing a woman into your room.
She's just my automail mechanic!
Wow... so you sweet-talked your mechanic, huh...
When I say one thing, you come up with another!
I'm Maes Hughes.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Winry Rockbell.
Won't you get in trouble for ditching work?
No need to worry!
I left Sheska with overtime work.
What are you, a demon?
Oh yeah, you guys are almost free from your escorts.
Really?!
Escorts?
Hey, you...
Just what kind of dangerous situations are you getting yourself into?!
Well, look. How should I put it...
I-It's not a big deal.
That's right.
You two never tell me anything, anyway.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm going to go look for a place to stay for the night.
What?!
Then stay at my place!
But...
Don't worry about it!
My wife and daughter will be delighted.
No, but...
All right, it's settled!
Huh?! Wait!
Come on, let's go!
Hang on!!!
Happy birthday Elicia!
U-Umm, Mr. Hughes? What exactly is...
Why, thank you for asking.
Today is Elicia's birthday, so to speak!
So to speak!
So how old are you now, Elicia?
Tw-
Three!
Sh...
She's...
So cute!
I've been with them ever since we were little, so they're kind of like my brothers.
You must always be worried about them with the way they are, aren't you?
You bet!
They came home after such a long time,
and Ed's arm was in pieces.
And when they called me up, Ed's severely injured...
...and Al's being troubled by something...
But they'll never tell me what happened.
Even when they left Resembool...
They probably didn't feel the need to discuss it.
They probably thought that you'd understand, even if they didn't tell you.
But... there are some things in life that will only be understood through words.
I guess that's just the way things are.
Guys always convey things with actions, not words,
so if it's something tough, they don't want others to have to put up with it.
They don't want to worry people, either.
So they don't say it.
But even then, if those brothers happen to whine...
...you comfort them and set them straight.
I think that's perfect.
Elicia, let's play!
I'm getting off!
Here you go.
Hey! Elicia's going to be playing with me!
What? I'm  going to be playing with her!
Your daughter sure is popular.
No!
She's mine!
Hey, you brats!
Do something to my daughter and see what happens!
You don't need to convey things with actions that  much!
Are you sure?
You can stay here for as long as you're in Central, you know.
No, that would be too much trouble...
She's gotten so attached to you.
From this perspective, they almost look like sisters.
Winry!
Have a nice day!
Come home soon, okay?
Looks like it's decided.
It's like I have a little sister now!
So you came again, bastard.
You've got a living body...
...so you have to drink it.
I can't help that I don't like it!
I'm actually growing, despite how I look.
But everyone just calls me puny...
You've got it easy, Al.
Since you're so big already.
I didn't become like this because I wanted to!
M-My bad...
You're right.
It's my fault we became like this, after all.
That's why I want to get your body ba-
Is there really a guarantee
I'll be able to return to my old body?!
I'll make it come true.
Believe in me.
Believe?!
What am I supposed to believe with this empty body?!
Memories are just information if you really think about it!
It should be possible to create them artificially!
What are yo-
Brother, you once told me there was something you couldn't say to me because you were too afraid, right?
Could it be you were trying to say...
...that I'm just a fake... an artificial soul and a set of memories you created?!
Winry, you and Granny are both trying to deceive me, aren't you?
Am I right, Brother?!
Are those the thoughts you've been holding in?
Is that all you've got to say?
I see.
Ed...
Ed!
Al, you...
IDIOT!!!
W-What was that for?!
Winry?!
You moron!
You don't even know how Ed feels!
What Ed was afraid to ask you...
...is whether you hate him or not!
It's all... my fault...
He can't even eat, sleep, or feel pain anymore...
He... He hates me for sure...
Al wouldn't.
Why don't you just ask him?
I... I'm scared...
I'm too scared to ask...
And... And yet...
You...
Just who the heck would be prepared to
give up his life just to create a fake brother?
Don't you two only have each other?
Go after him!
Y... Yeah.
MOVE!
Yes, ma'am!
Brot-
Now that I think about it, I've gotten a bit rusty because we haven't sparred in a while.
Huh?
Wha? Wa-
W-Wait a second, Brother!
Hold on!
Your wounds are going to open back up!
I win!
For the first time in my life, I beat you!
That wasn't fair, Brother.
Sh-Shut up!
A win's a win!
We've always fought a lot, haven't we.
Yeah.
Now that I think about it, we fought for the dumbest reasons, didn't we?
Like who gets to sleep in the top bunk.
Yep.
We fought over snacks, too, didn't we?
We also fought over toys.
I won.
Even when we played by Raine River...
You pushed me in, didn't you?
We fought all the time during our training, too, remember?
That was a draw since Master nearly beat us both to death for being "annoying".
We also fought over who would marry Winry.
I don't remember that!
I won. But she said no.
I-I see...
Are you going to tell me all that was a lie?
I'm sorry...
We want to return to our bodies, no matter what it takes.
Are you trying to say those feelings are artificial, too?
They're not.
That's right.
We decided to return to our bodies together, for sure.
We're going to be moving forward!
If we move forward, we'll get stronger, both physically and mentally.
What about milk?
I'll drink it!
...as much as possible.
Let's get stronger.
Yeah.
Mr. Hughes.
There are things that can only be conveyed through words. Don't you agree?
You're right.
Brother...
Master...
Where... did everyone...
Hi.
You're not an Ishbalan, are you?
Ah, pardon me.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm a State Alchemist who is going to be in charge of destroying this area.
Oh, he's awake.
Where am I?
You're in the slums on the outskirts of East City.
Sir... you are...
I'm Ishbalan, just like yourself.
Don't worry, I won't sell you out or anything.
Are there other Ishbalan survivors in this place?
There sure are.
Even a soot-covered place like this feels like a city if you live here.
In other words, "All of this world is within the bosom of our God, Ishvala."
I... see...
Don't push yourself!
You were floating around in the sewers, covered in wounds.
Hey...
Is my right arm still attached?
Yeah, it is.
These tattoos are amazing.
Yeah.
It's a precious bond I received from my family...
Your best friend eventually becomes your comrade-in-arms, and finally, an everyday fixture in your life.
Even if the future you discussed had turned into a shade of lead, your best friend hadn't changed and was always there.
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Episode 10, Separate Ways.
A fixture in one's life. Something like that cannot be replaced.