Alchemy is a science where one understands the structure of matter, breaks it down, then rebuilds it.
However, it is not an all-powerful technique,
as one cannot create something out of nothing.
If one wishes to gain something,
one must present something of equal value.
This is the concept of equivalent exchange, the fundamental basis of alchemy.
However, there is a taboo in alchemy. Human transmutation.
One must not commit this act.
In the city of Lior, a High Priest of Leto deceived people through the use of the Philosopher's Stone and alchemy.
Ed and Al, who ventured into the church, stopped the High Priest's plot.
However, the Philosopher's Stone was a fake.
"Get up and take a step. Walk forward."
Ed's words pierced Rose's chest, who had lost all hope.
But, those words were also meant for themselves, as well.
You're Basque Gran, the "Iron Blood Alchemist", aren't you?
Who are you?
Alchemists who go against God's path...
...shall perish!
So you're the killer who only goes after State Alchemists.
But!
You picked... the wrong opponent!
You're fast! But...
Well, then...
How foolish.
W-What?!
Perish.
Another State Alchemist?
Looks like quite a mess.
You have to be careful, too, Major.
You may be his next target.
Yes, sir...
Führer President!
Why are you here, sir?
I heard the news.
Lt. Colonel Hughes, are you in charge of dealing with this matter?
Yes, sir!
If there are people whom you require assistance from, request them immediately.
We must bring the iron hammer down on the traitors.
Yes, sir!
Second Lieutenant Breda.
All right...
Seriously... The Colonel must have been procrastinating again.
Hey, Havoc, do half of these for me.
I've got my hands full over here, too.
Umm, who is this again?
That's Lieutenant Yoki.
He's a little rascal who was lining his pockets with the authority he was given at the coal mines of Youswell.
He's currently on the run after having
his actions exposed by the Elric Brothers.
Sergeant Fuery, how is the radio?
The receiver is broken.
We'll need to replace some parts...
Edward-kun! Alphonse-kun!
Welcome back, you two.
The Colonel has been waiting for you.
The matter in Lior is settled all thanks to you.
I'd like to express my gratitude.
It wasn't for you or anything.
And, was the search for
the Philosopher's Stone a failure again?
The stone was a fake.
But the power was unbelievable.
He transmuted a huge chimera, too.
I wonder how you could use the stone to make something like that?
I'm not really familiar with the field of
Biological Alchemy, so I wouldn't know, but...
Yeah, I'm a little curious.
If we put our effort into researching it,
we may find something useful in getting our bodies back.
Yeah.
Then, how about seeking help from a specialist?
Huh?
The Sewing-Life Alchemist, Shou Tucker.
He is a scholar in chimera Transmutation.
I'll introduce you to him.
You're going to go out of your way to do that?
I-It's a trap! There's definitely more than meets the eye!
Don't look at me with those suspicious eyes!
We're even after that case in Lior!
It just feels disgusting to know that I owe you.
Tucker became a State Alchemist two years ago after transmuting a chimera that understood human language.
"Understood human language"?
It could speak?! The chimera?!
Yeah. Apparently, it did.
Just one sentence...
"I want to die."
It never ate afterwards and died.
What a huge house.
B-Brother!
Wow, we've got a lot of visitors!
Nina, we have to keep the dog tied down.
I'm terribly sorry.
This house has been in a mess ever since my wife left.
Well, pleasure to meet you, Edward.
I'm Shou Tucker, the Sewing-Life Alchemist.
He is interested in the transmutation of living organisms.
He said he would love to have
the honor of seeing your work.
Sure, that's fine with me.
One thing, though...
If you'd like for me to show you my hand,
I'm going to need to see yours, too.
Isn't that what being an alchemist is about?
Why are you interested in the transmutation of the living organisms, exactly?
Oh, well... he's...
Colonel.
Transmutation of your mother?!
As an eleven year old child?!
Ah, I see. So that's why you're called "The Fullmetal Alchemist"...
You've experienced a tough past, haven't you...
I'm not sure whether I could be of any help at all,
but please take a look at my laboratory.
Wow...
Ah, this is a little embarrassing.
People call me the "authority" on chimeras, but in reality, it's not really going very well.
Wow, this is awesome!
That's the reference room. Feel free to take a look around.
All right. Then I'll start with this shelf.
Then I'll start with that one over there.
I'll be returning to work.
I'll send someone to pick them up in the evening.
Wow, he's really into it.
He can't even hear what's going on around him.
I guess geniuses really do exist.
Up high! Up high!
Al, what the heck are you doing?!
Nina seemed like she wanted someone to play with her.
Hey, what the heck do you think we're here for-
Alexander wants someone to play with, too, he says.
You've got some guts.
It's said that even when hunting rabbits, lions put forth their fullest effort.
I, Edward Elric, shall deal with you with all of my physical and spiritual might!!!
You damn dog!!!
Yo Boss, I've come to pick you up.
What are you doing?
Eh, just taking a break from research...
Did you manage to get good data?
You're welcome to visit tomorrow, too.
You'll come visit again?
Let's play tomorrow, all right, Nina?
Okay!
Oh right, Mr. Tucker, I've got a message for you from the Colonel.
He told me to tell you, "It's almost the day of the assessment. Don't forget."
Yes, understood.
Well, then.
Daddy.
What's an "assessment"?
Well...
A State Alchemist has to report the results of his experiments once a year.
Daddy couldn't get a good evaluation last year.
If Daddy messes up this year,
Daddy won't be a State Alchemist anymore.
What?!
You'll be fine, Daddy!
You're always studying so much!
You're right. I've got to do my best.
This... is my last chance...
Huh, your mother left home two years ago?
Daddy told me that she went back to her parents' home.
Oh... it must be kind of lonely for you,
being alone with your daddy in a big house like this.
Nope, I'm fine.
Daddy's really nice, and I've got Alexander with me, too.
But... Daddy's always at his lab these days, so..
I guess I'm kind of lonely...
Ugh, my shoulders have gotten a little stiff.
Why don't you exercise a bit, Brother?
That sounds kind of nice.
Hey, dog!
Accompany me on my exercises!
You, too, Nina.
Wait up!
Watch this!
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait, you!
Wait!
You can do it, Alexander!
"It's almost the day of the assessment. Don't forget."
But... why does he only target State Alchemists?
If the army is his target, he can just attack soldiers indiscriminately.
Since Alchemists possess special abilities, they're not easy to kill.
And one with a state qualification should be much tougher.
Perhaps it's the qualification that's the reason?
Hm?
An immense reward and various privileges.
Many are envious of them.
Also...
"Alchemists, work for the good of the public."
Alchemists, who are supposed to be searching for the truth,
turn into the army's human weapons
as soon as they earn their state qualifications.
And also, after that civil war in Ishbal,
there are many who hold a grudge against us.
Reporting.
Yesterday, around 9:30PM, many station employees witnessed a man with a large scar on his face at Central City Station.
Station?!
Did he run away?!
Our lives before I got my state qualification were terrible.
We were so poor.
My wife couldn't stand living in conditions like that, and she left our home.
I need to pass the assessment, no matter what...
I don't ever want to return to those days.
It's okay, Daddy!
If they tell you "No", Alexander and I will go and scold the higher-ups!
Nina sure is strong.
Nina... what do you say we play together tomorrow?
Really?!
Yeah.
Yay!
Alexander, Daddy said he'd play with us tomorrow!
Good morning, Mr. Tucker!
We're going to be using your place again today!
Huh?
Mr. Tucker?
Hey! Nina?
Oh, so you are here.
Hey...
It's complete. The finished product.
A chimera that understands human language.
Watch.
This person is Edward. Got it?
Ed...ward...
That's right! I'm so proud of you!
This is amazing... it really did talk.
Now I won't have to lose my state qualification.
Ed...ward...
O...nii...chan...
Mr. Tucker...
When did you get your state qualification again?
It was two years ago, I believe.
And when did your wife leave you?
Two years ago.
Can I ask you another question?
Nina and Alexander...
Where are they?!
I don't like sharp brats like you.
Brother!
Yeah, that's how it is!
You've done it, haven't you?!
It was your wife two years ago,
and this time, you used your daughter and your dog to transmute a chimera!
Since there are limits to animal experimentation, after all!
It must be a breeze if you use a human!!!
W-What's there to get angry about?
The mankind's advances are the product of many experiments on humans, aren't they?
If you're a scientist, too, then you should-
Don't screw around with me!!!
Do you really think something like this will be forgiven?!
Something like this... toying with human life?!
Human life?
Ah, human life, you say?
Fullmetal Alchemist!
Your limbs and your younger brother.
Aren't those the results of what you're saying right now? Toying with human life?
NO!!!
We're the same!
You and I!
No, we're not!!!
Yes, we are!
There was a possibility in front of us, so we tested it out.
Even though we knew it was taboo!
You're wrong!!!
I!
Alchemists!
Don't!
I... I!!!
Brother!
If you go any further, he'll die!
Da...ddy...
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
We can't change you back to normal with our powers.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
Let's... play.
Let's play...
I made it in time.
With this, I can continue being a State Alchemist...
State Alchemist, my ass...
Stop kidding yourself...
Let's... play.
DAMMIT!!!
If something such as an act of the Devil exists in this world,
this case is just that.
The Devil, huh...
But if it is an order, State Alchemists must make
their move, without hesitation, to take human lives.
If it's about handling human lives,
there really isn't much difference between where we stand and what Mr. Tucker did.
You were aware of that, and yet you chose this path.
Am I right, Fullmetal?
I'm sure you'll run into incidents like this in the future again.
There may be times when you have to soil your hands.
Are you going to come to a stop like that every time it happens?
Whether they call me a dog of the military, or curse me as a devil,
Al and I will get back our bodies.
But...
We're neither devils,
nor gods at that!
We're humans...
We're just humans!!!
Puny, powerless humans...
...who can't even save one little girl.
I wonder why no one understands us...
...Nina...
You're Shou Tucker, aren't you?
Who are you?
Looks like... you're not from the military!
How did you get in?!
There should have been military policemen stationed out front!
Alchemists, who go against God's path...
...shall perish!
Da...ddy...
Daddy...
How miserable...
But now that you are in a state like that,
there is no way to return you to normal.
At the very least, leave this world in peace.
God,
two souls have just returned to your side.
Please usher them into your broad bosom,
and grant rest and salvation to their miserable souls.
Still grief-stricken over Nina's death,
Ed and Al are attacked by the mysterious man, Scar.
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Episode 5, Rain of Sorrow.