South-southeast!
Your next location is south-southeast!
I heard you!
I heard, so give me a break
and quiet down!
I'm begging you!
I got the message, so please!
Please!
Please! Please! Please!
Please marry me!
I could die any day, you know!
That's why I want you to marry me!
So please! Please, I'm begging you!
Wh-What's up with that?
What on earth?
Huh?
EPISODE 11:
DRUM HOUSE
I'm begging you!
There's no one else!
You're all that I have!
I see! Gotcha!
I'll do something about it!
Please help me! Please marry me!
I'm begging—
What do you think you're doing
right in the middle of the road?
Can't you see she doesn't want this?
And don't go making trouble
for your sparrow, either!
That uniform!
You're that guy from the Final Selection!
No one I know is anything like you!
I don't know you!
But we met, remember? We met, remember?
You're the one with the problem!
Like your memory!
Okay, it's alright now.
You can head home now
without any worries.
I will. Thank you very much!
Hey!
Stay out of my way!
That girl is going to marry me!
Because she's in love with me, all ri—
Hey! Ouch! That hurts!
Stop it! Stop it! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
H-Hey, calm down!
When did I ever tell you that I loved you?
You were crumpled up on the side of the road
looking ill, and all I did was speak to you!
Doesn't that mean that you talked to me
because you were worried because you love me?
I already have a fiancé, so not on your life!
With all that energy,
you must be fine now, right?
Goodbye!
W-Wait, come back!
Come...
Look, cut it out!
Wh-Why'd you get in my way?
This has nothing to do with you!
What sort of an expression is that?
Stop that!
Why are you staring at me
like I'm a creature or something?
Hey you! You're responsible for it!
Since it's your fault
that I missed out on getting married!
Say something!
Listen up! I'm going to die soon!
During my next job!
The thing is, I'm horribly weak, okay?
I'm not kidding!
You gotta protect me
until I manage to get married, all right?
My name is Kamado Tanjirou!
Is that right? My apologies!
I'm Agatsuma Zenitsu!
Please save me, Tanjirou!
What do you mean, save you?
What was your reason
for becoming a swordsman, Zenitsu?
Why are you being
so blatantly shameless?
That's a harsh way to put it!
I got swindled by a woman
and racked up all this debt!
The old geezer who took it over
for me was a cultivator!
Day after day, I had to go
through hellish training!
It was so bad that I thought
I'd be better off dead!
I was really thinking I would die
during the Final Selection!
But since I was lucky enough to survive,
I'm still going through hell every day!
I'm so scared! Scared! Scared! Scared!
I just know that I'm gonna get devoured
and killed soon by a demon!
My brains are gonna get sucked
through my ears while I'm still alive!
No! No!
Please save me!
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
How are you?
Well...
Now that I'm calmer,
I'm getting hungry.
Don't you have any food on you?
Nope.
Here, take this.
Would like to eat it?
Hey, thanks.
You're not eating, Tanjirou?
No, since that's all I've got.
Here.
You eat half.
You sure?
Thanks!
I know what you mean
when you say you're scared of demons,
but you can't make trouble
for your sparrow.
Was it distressed? The sparrow?
How can you tell?
Well, he says that you're always whining
about not wanting to go to work,
and you're always hitting on girls,
and that you snore so loud, he's had it!
So he says.
He's saying that?
You can understand bird language?
You're lying, right?
You're just trying to trick me!
Start running! Start running!
Tanjirou, Zenitsu, run!
Both of you head over
to your next destination!
Run! Run, Tanjirou, Zenitsu!
That crow is talking!
Hey, Tanjirou,
on second thought,
I'm not gonna make it.
Even if I go along,
I'm gonna be totally useless.
The demon scent
is getting stronger little by little.
There's something up ahead.
What's that?
I can smell blood.
But this particular scent...
You smell something?
Something I've never smelled before.
I don't know about that,
but do you hear that sound?
Also, are you and I gonna work
together, after all?
Sound?
K-Kids...
I wonder what's wrong.
Hey, guys, what are you doing here?
They seem really shocked.
Okay, wanna see something cool?
Ta-da!
A sparrow in my palm!
See? Isn't he cute?
Please tell me.
Did something happen?
Is this your house?
No. No, it's not.
This...
This is...
A-A monster's...
house!
Our big brother got taken away.
When we were walking
down the road at night,
this monster we'd never
seen before showed up.
It didn't give us a glance.
Just our brother.
And they went inside that house, right?
Yeah.
Did you two follow them here?
You did good!
Great job!
We followed the traces of his blood.
Because he got hurt!
Hurt...
Don't worry!
We're going to defeat the bad guy
and rescue your brother!
Really? You really will?
Yeah.
For sure!
Tanjirou...
Hey, what is this sound?
This creepy sound never stops.
Is it a drum?
Sound?
I don't hear any.
Don't look!
Are you all right?
Stay with me!
The wound is so deep.
Is this...
Even though... I got out...
Even though I made it out...
Made it outside.
Still...
Am I gonna die?
Am I still gonna die?
And now he's gone...
It must've hurt a lot.
You must've suffered.
Tanjirou, by any chance,
is that guy these kids'...
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
We couldn't save him.
If only we'd gotten here a little sooner,
we might've managed to save him.
Hey,
is this man your...
H-He's not our brother.
Our brother's wearing
a persimmon-colored kimono.
I see.
So it's captured more than one person.
I promise to bury you when I return.
Forgive me.
All right.
Zenitsu, come on!
But no one else can help them now
but you and me.
Is that so?
I understand.
Hey, come on! Why are you making
that face full of fury at me?
Okay, I'll go!
I have no intention of forcing you to.
I said I'll go!
In case of an emergency,
I'm leaving this box behind.
Even if something happens,
you two will be protected.
Okay, we're going now.
Tanjirou!
Hey, Tanjirou!
You'll protect me, right?
Zenitsu, I hate to put you
on the spot, but...
I've got a broken rib and leg
from my previous battle.
And neither are fully healed yet. So—
What do you mean, broken bones?
Don't go breaking any bones on me!
If you've got fractures,
you can't possibly protect me!
I-I-I'm gonna die!
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?
I'm gonna die now!
Gonna die, gonna die, gonna die!
Broken bones? How could you?
I'm a dead man now! 99.9% dead!
I'm dead! I'm dead! I'm dead!
Zenitsu, quiet down!
You'll be all right!
Don't sugarcoat it!
I'm not! I can tell, all right?
Zenitsu, you're—
You can't!
You come in here!
O-onii-chan, we heard scratching sounds
from inside that box!
E-Even still, it pains me
that you left it behind!
I mean, it's more precious
to me than my own life!
Sorry! My butt...
It's a different room.
No.
Were we the ones that moved?
To the beat of that drum?
Sorry you got separated
from your brother, okay?
But I'm gonna protect you
no matter what.
And Zenitsu is gonna protect your brother.
Don't worry!
What's your name?
Teruko.
Is that right? Teruko?
That's a fine name you have—
Even among all these scents,
this is the strongest one
that this house is steeped in!
This one's devoured
a whole slew of humans!
This one's the master of this house!
I'm gonna die!
Gonna die, gonna die, gonna die,
I'm telling you!
Tanjirou and I got split up!
Teruko!
No, no, no, no!
Don't yell like that!
If you yell and the bad guy hears you,
it won't be pretty!
Come on, let's step outside!
What...
Why outside?
Are you trying to escape all by yourself?
All this constant yammering about dying...
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Clinging onto a younger person...
Don't you feel pathetic?
What are you wearing that sword
on your hip for anyway?
Those words cut so deep.
That's not it!
I'm not gonna be of any use anyway,
Let me go!
so I'm gonna call
a grownup here, okay?
Let me go!
Because this isn't something
us kids can resolve on our own!
You're kidding me, kidding me, kidding me!
I'm sure this was the front door!
Where'd the outside go?
I mean, this door was...
Is it this one?
How about this one?
What about this one?
It's a monster!
What the heck?
What's that look in your eyes?
Stop looking at me like that!
If it hadn't been...
If it hadn't been for their meddling...
Teruko, you gotta try not to scream.
Even if the room moves,
don't go into the corridor.
Step back and hide behind the shelves.
Curses, curses!
Thanks to them, he got away!
When he was my prey!
Why is it? Why do they all keep
barging into someone else's home?
It's infuriating.
That was my prey!
My own prey, discovered on my own turf!
Curse them!
Hey! You!
I'm with the Demon Slayers Corps.
Rank 10, Kamado Tanjirou!
I am going to cut you down now!
A child with rare blood
that I found myself!
Got him!
Teruko!
The tatami mats are on the sides!
The room's been flipped!
So, this is that demon's Blood Demon Technique!
This entire house is this demon's territory!
What's this?
An odd scent is coming this way.
It's not a demon!
Pig assault! Pig assault!
Pig assault!
Wh-What's with that guy?
He's wearing a boar's hide!
And he's wielding Nichirin Swords!
All right, you monster...
Die on the battlefield
and serve as my springboard!
So that I can become more powerful
and soar even higher!
Infuriating!
Here goes...
Pig...
assault!
PREVIEW
RUSTLE RUSTLE
Hey, Tanjirou,
I think that girl you forcibly pulled
away from me loves me after all.
What are you talking about?
It was so obvious
that she wasn't into you!
That's not true!
She might've said all those things,
but she could've really wanted me
to chase after her, right?
I think there was love in her eyes
when she slapped me,
and then all the other times she hit me,
she was really putting her heart
into it every single time!
She must be in love with me
for sure, for sure, for sure!
Say something, will you?
Now, it's time for a Taishou secret!
I hear that Zenitsu gets self-conscious
in front girls, and his heart starts fluttering.
Well, I can't help it!
Girls are so adorable,
so soft, and they smell so nice!
Oh, man, now that I'm thinking about them,
I just remembered that girl!
If I make it out of this house,
I'm gonna go right after her
and rub my cheek against her!
Next, Episode 12,
"The Boar Bares Its Tusks, Zenitsu Sleeps."
Hey, don't just ignore me, Tanjirou!
TO BE CONTINUED