That mask.
I can tell by the fox masks.
Everyone got eaten just because
they were wearing them.
Full Focus!
Breath of Water!
First Form!
Water Surface Slice!
EPISODE 5:
MY OWN STEEL
Urokodaki!
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
My body's crumbling and disappearing.
I can't stop it!
Dammit!
To think that the face of a Demon Hunter
will be the last thing I'll ever see...
How did it come to this?
I'm so scared. I'm all alone.
Nii-chan, where are you?
I want you to hold my hand!
Like you always do!
Why?
Why did I devour you, Nii-chan?
Huh?
Who's this "Nii-chan" person?
What a sad scent.
God...
Please...
The next time this man is reborn,
please make sure
he doesn't turn into a demon.
Nii-chan!
Nii-chan! Nii-chan!
Hold my hand, will you?
You're hopeless, you know?
Still such a scaredy-cat.
Sabito, Makomo...
and the other children who were killed...
I won.
You can rest easy now.
I guess you're going home as promised.
Even though you're just souls,
you're going back to Mt. Sagiri...
...and to your beloved Urokodaki-san.
If I die,
my soul will return there, too.
There's something I wanna ask you!
How do I turn someone who's become
a demon back into a human?
Please tell me!
How can I turn Nezuko...
back into a human?
Wisteria?
I made it.
Only four of us?
But there were at least twenty.
I don't see that guy here, either.
It's all because I blacked out
at that moment.
I couldn't save him.
I'm gonna die. I'm a goner.
Even if I survive now,
I'm gonna die in the end anyway.
- Welcome back.
Congratulations.
We're pleased to see that you're safe.
So? What am I supposed to do now?
Where's my sword?
First, we shall issue you all uniforms.
We will take your measurements,
after which your rank will be engraved.
There are ten ranks in all...
Kinoe.
Kinoto.
Hinoe.
Hinoto.
Tsuchinoe.
Tsuchinoto.
Kanoe.
Kanoto.
Mizunoe...
...and Mizunoto.
Currently, you are
at the lowest rank, Mizunoto.
And our swords?
Today, we will let you
choose the ore for your swords.
However, the swords will take
ten to fifteen days to complete.
Are you kidding me?
But first...
We will now assign each of you
your own Kasugai Crow.
Kasugai Crow?
These Kasugai Crows can be used
primarily for communication.
Did you say "crow"?
Isn't this a sparrow, though?
Don't give me that crap!
Who the hell cares
about some stupid crow?
I want a sword, you hear?
Gimme one right now!
The Demon Slayers' sword!
The Color Changing Sword!
Take your hand off her!
Or else I'll break your arm!
Who the hell are you?
Wh-Wh-Wh-What should I do?
Let's see you try it!
Are you finished chatting?
Now then, please select an ore.
The steel for the sword...
that will annihilate demons and protect you...
will be of your own choosing.
I'll probably die really quickly.
They're asking us to choose,
but how are we supposed to pick one out?
I've never seen an ore before,
and I can't tell the difference anyway.
I have absolutely no clue.
I see.
As many as five of them
managed to survive, huh?
Excellent.
The number of my children
has increased again.
I wonder what kinds of swordsmen
they'll become.
I was so naive.
I couldn't even have a talk with a demon.
All they did was attack me
and try to kill me right away.
Sorry, Nezuko.
I never got to ask them...
how to turn a demon back into a human.
Even my uniform is heavy.
I wanna get home as soon as possible,
but my whole body hurts.
I made it.
Nezuko... Urokodaki-san...
Hey! Nezuko!
You...
So, you're awake?
Nezuko!
Why...
Why'd you fall asleep all of a sudden?
Never waking up once!
I was worried
you were going to die, you know?!
You came back to us alive.
I see. You killed that morphed demon.
Yes.
At last.
I'm truly impressed
that you made it back.
Yes.
There are several kinds of demons.
The demons who use a special spell
called the "Blood Demon Technique"
possess supernatural abilities.
You may have to fight
those demons, as well, from now on.
And battling them will be far more difficult
than anything you've known until now.
Even so, Tanjirou,
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Right.
Um...
I think that Nezuko's not
like the other demons.
Do you think it could it be
that Whatchamacallit Technique?
No, I don't think so.
I wouldn't call that an example
of the Blood Demon Technique.
I'm just guessing here,
but it could be that Nezuko's recovering
her strength by sleeping
instead of consuming human flesh.
I'll protect you, Nezuko.
15 DAYS LATER
Uh...
My name is Haganezuka.
I have forged Kamado Tanjirou's sword,
and I am here to deliver it.
Um, I'm Kamado Tanjirou.
Please come inside.
This is the Nichirin Blade.
And I forged it.
Um...
Please come in
so I can serve you some te—
The materials for a Nichirin Blade
can be obtained from the mountain
closest to the sun.
Scarlet Crimson Iron Sand
and Scarlet Crimson Ore.
These produce steel
that can absorb sunlight.
Wow, is that right?
Mt. Yoko is bathed in sunlight
all day long, you see.
Never a cloud in the sky,
nor any rain.
There he goes again,
You're going to get dirty,
so could you get up for a second?
never listening to what others say...
A clown mask?
Ah, you're a Child of Burning Crimson,
aren't you?
Now that's what I call lucky.
Oh no, I'm the son of Tanjuurou and Kie.
That's not what I meant.
See how your hair and eyes
are a reddish color?
When a kid like you is born
into a family that works with fire,
it's considered lucky
and a cause for celebration.
Is that right? I had no idea.
There's a good chance
that this sword will turn red!
Right, Urokodaki?
Yeah.
Come on, hurry up and draw it!
Nichirin Blades are also known
as "Color Changing Swords."
They change color
depending on the bearer.
Black!
It's black, huh?
Is it bad or something
if it turns black?
Is it unlucky?
No, not necessarily.
But you don't see
this pitch black too often.
And I was so hoping
I'd get to see a bright red sword!
Dammit!
Ouch! Stop!
Please calm down!
How old do you think you are?!
I'm thirty-seven!
Kamado Tanjirou!
Here are your orders!
It talks!
Make your way to a town
to the northwest!
Young girls have been vanishing there!
Night after night,
young girls have been vanishing!
Hunt down the demon
lurking there and kill it!
Kamado Tanjirou, prepare yourself
well for this task!
This is your first assignment
as a Demon Hunter!
My first... assignment...
PREVIEW
RUSTLE RUSTLE
Kasugai Crow, say hello to everyone.
I don't take orders from you!
Jeez.
Now, it's time for a Taishou secret!
Forget that! It's time
for the next mission! Hurry up!
All right! I got it!
Next, Episode 6,
"Swordsman Accompanying a Demon"!
Hey, you there!
If you miss it, I'll peck you!
Hey!
TO BE CONTINUED