The blood of the Twelve Demon Moons
should have a high degree
of Kibutsuji's blood.
If I can extract it,
the medicine that will turn Nezuko
back into a human can be completed sooner!
Hold on! Inosuke!
So, did you defeat it?
Are you all right, Inosuke?
I asked you whether you defeated
that thing or not!
Uh, yeah, I did!
But anyway, Inosuke,
how are you feeling?
Don't go showering me
with your sensitivity and kindness!
You hear me? Got that?
After all, anything you can do,
I can do, too!
Before you know it,
my head will be harder than yours!
Not to mention... Not to mention...
Um...
He's wounded severely.
I couldn't save our other comrades, either.
That person gave off
the scent of terror and suffering.
Enough to make her yearn for death.
What's the deal
with this mountain anyway?
With one of the Twelve Demon Moons present...
Stay still, Inosuke!
Cut that out! I don't need that!
...and a demon family living here...
I'm totally fine!
But...
I thought demons never herded together!
Ouch!
Something just pricked me!
What the hell? This is so annoying!
I can't find Tanjirou and Inosuke
anywhere! This sucks!
Where did they go?
Which way?
And it stinks around here, too! Stinks!
I think I'm gonna cry!
And this sound of spiders
rustling around is so creepy!
I'm sure these spiders are doing their best
to survive, too, but still!
Dammit! Shut up! Just stay still!
Is this even possible?
EPISODE 17:
YOU MUST MASTER A SINGLE THING
That's a spider with a human face!
What's up with that? What's up with that?
Please be a dream! Please be a dream!
Please be a dream!
If this can just be a dream,
I promise to do my best!
If I wake up to find myself
resting my head on Nezuko-chan's lap,
then I promise to give it all I have!
I'll even plow fields!
I'll be glad to plow a whole acre,
no, even two acres!
So, please!
Let me wake up from this nightmare!
What the heck is that?
Are those humans
who got turned into spiders?
Is that house floating?
I can see a glimpse of something,
but are those threads?
And it really stinks!
Talk about pungent!
This would kill Tanjirou
with his keen sense of smell!
This smell is making my throat ache!
I'm tearing up!
My eyes hurt, too!
It's huge!
It's huge! It's huge!
It's so huge!
That thing is too huge!
You know what! I refuse to speak
with anyone like you!
It's no use running away.
You're already losing.
What are you muttering about?
I don't wanna hear it,
so stop talking to me!
I don't like guys like you, all right?
You already know
how dire your situation is, don't you?
What are you talking about?
Take a look at your hands.
My hands?
What's wrong with my hands—
What's this?
It's poison.
You got bitten by a spider, right?
That poison will turn you into a spider, too.
In another 30 minutes,
you'll be my slave, crawling all over the ground!
Look at this. It's a clock.
Do you understand?
By the time this long hand
goes around once,
you'll have become
a member of the spider clan!
When the needle arrives here, you'll start
to feel tingling and pain in your limbs.
When it's here,
you'll also feel dizzy and nauseous!
Here, you'll experience intense pain,
your body will start to shrink,
and you'll black out!
And by the time you wake up...
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
Running away...
...is futile! Right, right, right!
I know that, all right? I know that!
What do you think you're doing?
Shut up! Just shut up!
There's no need to be afraid.
Once the poison makes its rounds and you turn
into a spider, you'll lose all intelligence, too!
No! That's just what I don't like about this!
Why can't you understand that, huh?
I have no friends or girlfriend,
all right? No one will like me!
Huh! I can see that you want an extra dose
of poison to turn into a spider faster.
No! No! I don't want to turn into that!
Get a hold of yourself!
Stop crying! Stop running away!
Doing that won't get you anywhere!
Zenitsu!
Come down from there!
We're going to continue training!
Oh no! I'm sure I'll die
if I do any more training!
I'm sure that I'll die, so...
You won't die!
Not from this level of training!
Come down from there, you little moron!
Gramps!
Call me "Master"!
But I love you, Gramps!
When the girl I loved made me raise money
so she could run off with another guy,
you did rescue me
from my mountain of debt!
Well, maybe all you wanted
was to train a swordsman!
I want to live up to your expectations, too!
But it's totally beyond me!
I do feel terrible
about the fact that I'm like this!
Just so you know, I've been training
on my own in secret, too!
I haven't been getting any sleep!
But I have absolutely nothing
to show for it!
What does this mean?
I mean, really, what does this mean?
Calm down, Zenitsu!
You do have the ability to...
I've had enough!
Zenitsu!
How tragic is my life anyway?
I got hit by lightning.
My hair color changed.
I was thankful just to be alive, but...
I...
I hate myself more than anyone else.
I always think
I have to get my act together,
but I end up cowering,
running away, sniveling.
I want to change.
I want to be a competent person.
Even still!
I'm doing everything I can, all right?
So, why do I have to end up going bald
and turning into a monster?
It can't be true, right? It so can't be true!
What's up with this guy?
Oh, crap! Don't climb up here!
Just leave me alone for a minute!
Just for a minute, all right?
My hair's falling out already?
My hair is falling out.
Hey, he never mentioned that part to me!
Who is this guy?
Isn't he a demon hunter
who came here to kill our family?
Did he just faint?
I can't believe how spineless he is.
He's gonna fall onto his head and die.
What the hell?
Breath of Thunder, First Form.
Poison Sputum!
Did he just twist his body
in midair to dodge that?
Such quick reflexes!
It's like he's a totally different person!
Breath of Thunder, First Form.
Hey, you guys! Pounce on him!
He's been assuming
the same stance over and over.
No question about it. This guy...
is only capable of that one attack!
That's all right, Zenitsu.
That's good enough for you.
If you can master one,
that's cause for celebration!
If you can only do one thing,
hone it to perfection.
Hone it to the utmost limit!
Hey, but Gramps...
Just a little while ago,
you were hopping mad.
Because Breath of Thunder has six forms,
and all I can manage to do is one.
Do you know how to forge a sword?
I have no idea.
Will you keep hitting me? I think I'll cry.
The thing about swords...
You strike and strike and strike
to get rid of impurities
and anything you don't need,
and to increase the purity of the blade,
so a durable sword can be forged.
So that's why you keep
clobbering me day in, day out?
But I'm not made of steel, am I?
I'm living flesh, you know.
You're not much of a threat, are you?
You call yourself a demon hunter?
Any minute now, you'll be rendered
immobile by that poison.
Zenitsu, perfect it!
It's all right to cry.
It's all right to run away!
Just don't ever give up!
Just believe.
You endured all that hellish training!
You'll be rewarded for that without fail!
Hone it to the utmost limit!
Become the strongest blade of all!
Hone that one thing to perfection!
Get out of my sight.
Don't make me repeat myself.
You know what I'm talking about.
Aren't you ashamed
of crying like a baby all day long?
You laggard...
Any time spent on you is wasted.
Sensei is an extraordinary man.
But Gramps said—
"Gramps"? Don't speak of him
in that familiar way!
Sensei is a former Pillar!
Someone who earned the highest title
in the Demon Slayer Corps!
Almost no one ever gets the chance
to be trained by a former Pillar!
The time Sensei spends training you
is all for nothing!
You're an eyesore, okay?
Get out of my sight!
Why are you here?
Why do you insist on clinging here?
I have no parents,
so no one has any hopes for me.
There's no one who dreams that I'll grasp
or accomplish something one day.
That I'll prove myself useful to somebody.
That I'll manage to protect somebody
and make that person happy,
just once in my life.
Not even a simple future like that.
There's no one who hopes that I'll have one.
If you fail, cry and run away even once,
they say, "Oh, this guy's no good,"
and they walk away.
But not Gramps!
Time and time again,
he steadfastly reprimanded me.
All those times I kept running away...
Time and time again...
He'd drag me right back.
Clearly, he did smack me around
a bit too much.
But he never abandoned me!
Pierce him!
Inject him with more poison!
That should do it for him!
What's this?
The air is vibrating.
Thunder Breathing, First Form...
Thunderclap Flash!
Sixfold!
He vanished?
Did I get slashed?
Me?
Slashed?
By him?
By a guy like him?
But that's absurd!
By a guy who can barely move
his arms and legs?
I'm dreaming...
It's a happy dream.
I'm powerful.
More powerful than anyone.
I can help the weak and anyone in trouble.
Anytime.
Everything that Gramps taught me,
all the time he spent on me...
It wasn't for nothing!
A dream that, thanks to Gramps,
I became powerful
and helped out a lot of people.
But now, it's all over!
Chuuntarou...
I'm so sorry.
Don't ever give up!
Don't ever give up.
Use the breathing technique to slow down
the poison as much as you can.
Even if it's painful, even if it's agonizing,
don't try to take the easy way out...
or Gramps is gonna let you have it!
Right.
And Tanjirou's gonna yell at you, too.
What was that sound?
Did lightning just strike?
How should I know?
But I'm not smelling any thunderclouds.
The acrid odor in the air
is stronger now, so I can't tell.
Inosuke!
I think I'll go that way.
Go ahead and do whatever you want!
Are you descending, Inosuke?
Are you going down the mountain?
Why would I? Just beat it!
No, no, because you're severely wounded.
I am not wounded at all!
N-N-No, Inosuke! Your injuries...
Anyone can see that...
A demon!
Because of the odor wafting
all over this mountain,
I couldn't pick it up at all!
I'm gonna tear you to shreds,
you damn demon!
Come back here, dammit!
Inosuke!
Father!
Who are you calling "father"?
Inosuke!
Don't come near my family!
Stay away!
I'm leaving the rest to you, Father.
Breath of Water, Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Combined Junior and Senior High School!
COMBINED JUNIOR
AND SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL!!
TALES OF A DEMON SLAYER ACADEMY
Tales of a Demon Slayer Academy!
DEMON
SLAYER
ACADEMY
A prefect's day starts
early in the morning!
ONE MORNING
Honestly, I'd like to quit!
But there's one thing
stopping me from ever quitting!
And by that, I mean "dress code check"!
I can ogle the girls all I want
and not get yelled at!
Nezuko-chan!
Makomo-chan's looking cute today, too!
And that senpai's gorgeous, as well!
Tomioka-sensei!
It's not what it looks like!
That was just a dress code check!
Before you start finding fault
with other people's clothing, fix your hair!
Even though it's my natural color?
Next, Episode 18, "A Forged Bond."
But it's my natural color.
TO BE CONTINUED