Take this!
Move it!
Draw your sword and fight!
You cowardly weakling!
Enough!
I'll just have to skewer you
along with that box!
Knock it off!
EPISODE 14:
THE HOUSE WITH
THE WISTERIA FAMILY CREST
Knock it off!
He broke his bones!
Aren't you a member
of the Demon Slayers Corps?
Don't you get why Zenitsu refuses
to draw his sword?
It's because it's taboo for us to draw
our swords on each other for no reason!
But here you are,
giving him a one-sided beatdown!
Is that fun for you?
You're the lowest of the low!
Oh, so that's why?
My bad.
In that case, let's fight barehanded.
No! I don't think you get it at all!
First...
We're not supposed to fight
each other, period!
Fighting barehanded doesn't make it all right!
Listen to me!
Look at him!
How can he move like that?
I mean, Tanjirou just busted
some of his ribs.
Actually, hasn't Tanjirou
broken the taboo himself?
He did break his bones.
Th-This guy...
His attacks are bizarrely low!
It's just like...
Just like...
battling a four-legged beast!
Target him low!
Even lower than your opponent!
The flexibility of his joints!
It's superhuman!
Pretty amazing, aren't I?
He said it twice!
Singing his own praises...
And look what else I can do!
Cut it out! Don't do stuff like that!
Knock it off when you've got busted bones!
It's gonna get worse!
Worse? Fine by me!
Nothing can top
the pleasure of this moment!
You need to think hard about the future!
What do I care?
You need to...
calm down!
That sound!
Are your skulls fractured?
Huh? A girl? Huh? Your face!
What the hell?
You've got a problem
with my face or something?
You're one creepy guy, you know that?
You've got such a ripped body,
but there's a girl's face sitting on top of it.
Why the hell are you staring
at my face like that?
I-I'm not!
I'm not looking at your face!
We don't have a problem with your face!
It's quite petite, fair-skinned,
and therefore attractive!
You're a corpse! Come at me!
Not happening!
I'm not gonna attack you anymore!
Try headbutting me one more time!
Nope, I'm done!
I said do it! Come on!
You sit yourself down! Are you okay?
Hey, Big Forehead!
Let me tell you my name.
It's Hashibira Inosuke!
Don't you forget it!
What characters do you use to spell that?
Spell? Spell...
I don't know how to read or write!
My name is written on my loincloth—
What's wrong?
He froze.
What's the matter?
He collapsed!
Is he dead?
He's not dead.
It's probably a concussion.
Because I headbutted him
with all my strength
Are you okay, onii-chan?
Yeah.
Amazing! Can I touch your head?
Here!
That's scary!
Not a drop of blood from Tanjirou's head.
How hard is it anyway?
I mean, the wild boar's passed out.
Onii-chan, your head is so hard!
You think so?
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
He's awake!
Fight me! Fight me!
Hey, you!
This is how he is when he wakes up?
I hate that more than anything!
What the hell are you guys doing?
It's a burial.
You help out, too, Inosuke.
There are still people
who were killed inside the house.
What's the point of burying
the corpses of creatures?
I'm not doing that! I'm not helping out!
Forget that! Fight me!
Man, he really is a loon.
What does he mean, what's the point?
I see.
You can't do it because
your wounds are hurting you.
Those two are beyond help!
They're both crazy!
No, that's okay.
After all, we all have
a different pain threshold.
Moving everyone who died
outside that house,
then burying them by covering them
with dirt is a lot of work.
Zenitsu and these kids and I
will do our best, so don't worry!
He's so off.
You should get some rest, Inosuke.
Sorry to ask too much of you!
Don't underestimate me, dammit!
I'll bury a hundred,
no, two hundred of your corpses!
Just watch! I'm going to bury
more than anyone of you!
What is that person doing?
Better not look.
Yeah.
Descend the mountain!
That crow is talking!
Just don't think anymore.
Okay.
All right, follow me!
Follow yours truly!
Hey!
Where are you going?
We're descending the mountain.
We're not done with our battle yet!
You're tired, aren't you?
Come on, we're heading down.
I'm not tired!
Let's fight!
I won't have it!
I won't have it! I won't have it!
You can't go, Shoichi-kun!
You're powerful, Shoichi-kun!
Shoichi-kun is the one
who's gonna protect me!
Can't you see Shoichi-kun doesn't want to stay?
Please don't leave me behind!
You stop that right now!
Hold out your hands!
That will ward off demons.
You with rare blood,
keep that on your person!
It smells like wisteria.
Wisteria?
It's a flower that demons can't hate.
You should hold onto that.
Demon repellent!
We're truly grateful!
We can get home on our own.
Take care, now!
Now then, follow me!
Follow yours truly!
Fight me!
I swear I'm gonna find a weak point
and bring you down, you!
My name's not "you"!
It's Kamado Tanjirou!
Kamaboko Gonpachiro!
I'm gonna bring you down!
Who the hell are you talking about?
- You!
- No, it's someone else!
Can you talk any louder?
WISTERIA
A wisteria family crest...
Rest time! Rest time!
Since you've sustained injuries,
you're to rest until you're fully recovered!
You sure it's okay to rest?
I just fought a demon
while injured, you know.
Ke-ke-ke.
"Ke-ke-ke"?
Let's eat this thing.
What?
Yes?
Sorry to bother you so late at night!
A monster!
It's a monster!
Hey you!
Who the hell are you?
I see you're a demon hunter.
You look pretty weak!
Hey!
Come in.
That old lady sure walks fast!
This is where you'll be staying.
A change of clothes.
And here is your meal.
She has to be a monster, Tanjirou!
That old lady's a monster!
She's so quick, it's eerie!
She's a monster!
Old monster lady—
Use your chopsticks.
If you're that hungry,
you can have this, too.
Here.
No!
He's totally forgotten about the box!
Gimme a break, you thug!
Moron! Eyelashes!
Your bedding.
There she is! Old monster lady—
First come, first served!
I'm taking this one!
That's fine. Sleep wherever you want.
Where do you want to sleep, Zenitsu?
Here is the doctor.
Hello.
Yes.
Severe!
Who would've guessed
that all three of us had broken ribs?
2 RIBS                3 RIBS                   4 RIBS
This bump hurts more than my ribs.
Sorry.
Hey, you'd better apologize.
It really hurt, you know.
Getting pounded to a pulp like that.
Say you're sorry.
I'll pass.
Say you're sorry!
I'll pass!
Just say you're sorry!
If you're gonna be like that,
we're not eating with you anymore.
What's up with that?
Meals always taste better
when you eat together, you know.
He's right about that.
Did you guys hurt
your heads or something?
Who are you to talk?
Is there something I can help you with?
Monster!
Hey!
WISTERIA
According to the crow,
this house with the wisteria
family crest belongs to a family
that was once rescued
by demon hunters.
That's why they take care of people
for free if they're demon hunters.
That's what I was told,
but I never thought
they'd show us this much hospitality.
Just how great is the Demon Slayers Corps?
Now that you mention it, Inosuke,
why did you join the Corps?
You had some kind of reason, didn't you?
A member of the Demon Slayers Corps
barged in on me on my mountain,
so we competed to see
who was stronger, and I seized his sword.
What an unfortunate soul.
And then, I heard there was something
called "Final Selection,"
and the fact that demons do exist.
So that's why you joined
the Demon Slayers Corps?
And hey, so you and I both
grew up in the mountains, huh?
Don't lump me in with you!
I don't have any parents or siblings!
Testing my strength against other
living creatures is my only pleasure!
Is that right?
Tanjirou, no one else is asking,
so I'm gonna ask myself.
Why are you traveling with a demon?
Zenitsu...
You knew about that
and still protected the box, huh?
You really are a great guy,
you know that?
Thanks!
You...
You really shouldn't heap
so much praise on me!
I've got a keen sense of smell.
I knew it from the start.
How kind you are, Zenitsu...
and how strong...
No, I'm not strong.
Don't give me that.
I haven't forgiven you for stopping me
from bringing Shoichi-kun along.
It's trying to come out!
It's all right.
How can it be all right? Huh? Huh?
Shush!
It's the middle of the night, Zenitsu!
Why won't he take the bait?
Even when I stole his food...
Come to think of it,
why did he get mad a couple of times?
I forgot.
Oh my gosh! It's not even locked?
P-P-Protect me!
Someone please protect me!
Even you'll do, Inosuke!
Stay away from me!
It's out!
I gotta hide! I'm so scared!
Nezuko!
That's too much thinking.
Zenitsu...
Nezuko's my—
Tanjirou...
You...
Z-Zenitsu?
Just who do you think you are?
So, you've been traveling
with a girl this cute?
With a girl this cute in tow,
day after day, you've been traveling,
and you've been on cloud nine
the whole time, huh?
Zenitsu, it's not like—
Give me back all the blood I shed!
I... Listen, I...
I didn't give it my all just so you could spend
time in la-la land, making out with a girl!
That's not why I got pummeled and kicked
by that weird wild boar, right?
Zenitsu, calm down!
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
Demon Slayer Corps
is not something you'd join for fun!
Guys like you gotta be purged! Immediately!
Come to think of it, there's also the crime
of thwarting my marriage
and sending Shoichi-kun home.
Purged immediately!
Don't ever underestimate the Corps!
A guy like you! A guy like you!
Zenitsu, cut it out!
Mock the Demon Slayers Corps...
and you'll get sent to Hell!
You shall feel my wrath!
Combined Junior and Senior High School!
COMBINED JUNIOR
AND SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL!!
TALES OF A DEMON SLAYER ACADEMY
Tales of a Demon Slayer Academy!
SELF-INTRODUCTIONS
The new semester's begun.
Announce your names.
Yes, sir!
I'm Kamado Tanjirou!
My family runs a bakery,
and I'm the eldest of six children!
NO PIERCINGS
Take off those earrings.
I'm Hasibira Inosuke!
NO DRESSING DOWN
Button your shirt.
Um, I'm Agatsuma—
NO HAIR COLORING
Dye your hair black.
But this is my natural color.
Don't talk back!
So unfair!
It's also forbidden
to hold bread in your mouth!
NEXT EPISODE:
NATAGUMO MOUNTAIN
Next, Episode 15, "Natagumo Mountain."
TO BE CONTINUED
No Spartan education!