How should we kill them, I wonder.
I can feel power flowing through me.
Because of all the blood
he shared with me.
Of course we're going to
slaughter them cruelly.
Get down!
Did you decide how to kill them?
Cruelly, of course!
EPISODE 9:
TEMARI DEMON AND ARROW DEMON
You were right, Yahaba!
A building just appeared out of nowhere!
The handiwork of a Blood Demon Technique
wielder adept at hiding objects.
And is the demon hunter
accompanied by a demon?
What's going on here?
Isn't this fun?
Still, I have to say, Susamaru...
Your way of doing things
is so immature.
So careless.
You got it dirty!
You got my kimono dirty with dust!
Oh, stop whining!
We found them right away
thanks to my temari, so who cares?
And now we can have tons of fun!
You've gone and got dirt on me again!
You're so uptight.
Your kimono isn't the least bit dirty.
And besides...
Found 'em! Found 'em!
A ball!
So, she caused all this damage
by throwing that ball?
That woman...
Is she one of Kibutsuji's minions?
Tamayo-sama!
Yushiro-san!
Dammit!
Nezuko!
Take the lady sleeping in the back room
somewhere safe outside!
It's too dangerous outside!
We have a basement, so take her there!
Understood!
Nezuko!
That's one down!
She's giving off a totally different scent
than any of the other demons!
Is it because she's stronger?
It's a really thick scent!
It feels so heavy
once it enters my lungs!
The demon hunter
wearing hanafuda-like earrings...
It's you, isn't it?
So, I'm the one they're targeting?
Tamayo-san!
Please find a place to hide!
I'm the one those demons are after!
Tanjirou-san, I want you to fight
without worrying about us.
We'll be fine without your protection.
Since we're demons.
All right.
It's all over for you now!
Even if I dodge, that ball will still turn towards me.
Of the ten forms...
The fastest thrusting technique...
Full Focus...
Breath of Water!
Seventh Form,
Drop Wave Pattern Pierce · Curve!
Oh, so you thrust with a diagonal curve
to soften the ball's power.
But...
How can that ball
move around like that?
It swerved unnaturally
when it struck Yushiro-san, as well!
It's not like it's spinning
in any special way, and yet...
What is this?
Yushiro!
Ta...
Tamayo-sama!
Didn't I tell you?
That we shouldn't get involved
with that demon hunter!
From the start!
My Blindfold technique
is still a work in progress!
I know you're well aware
of that yourself!
I may be able to conceal the presence
of buildings and people, their scent,
but it's not like I can mask
their very existence!
The greater our numbers,
the more traces we'll leave,
and the greater the odds
that Kibutsuji will discover us!
Those demons got this close to us,
yet there was no scent
until we came under attack!
That was Yushiro's Blood Demon Technique, huh?
Anyone who ruins the time
I spend alone with you...
I despise such people!
I despise them with passion!
It's unforgivable!
What are you babbling about!
How fun!
To be killed by me,
one of the Twelve Demon Moons...
You should be honored!
Twelve Demon Moons?
They serve directly under Kibutsuji!
She grew more arms!
Now then, let's keep playing!
Until the night ends!
Until your life ends!
If I were to cast my spell now,
it would affect Tanjirou-san, as well.
And Yushiro needs time to prepare
to switch to attack mode.
But if this goes on...
There it is again!
Even without hitting anything,
they changed trajectory!
If I slice them apart,
it blunts the blow,
but then they hit me anyway!
Two different scents of blood.
There are two demons!
Their scent tells me where they are!
But...
Tamayo-san! Yushiro-san!
It's no good!
I don't have time to protect them!
We'll recover soon enough!
So don't worry!
Hey! Moron demon hunter!
If you look at the arrows,
you can tell which direction they're going!
Dodge the arrows!
Arrows?
Seriously, you can't even see them?
I'm going to lend you
my sense of sight!
That should at least enable you
to behead that temari woman!
I can see now!
She was using these arrows to control...
...the trajectory of the balls!
Thanks, Yushiro-san!
I can see the arrows now, too!
Then, hurry up and defeat her!
Nezuko!
Nezuko, let's go outside!
Take care of the demon up in the tree!
I'm the one you want to take on!
The demon hunter
wearing hanafuda-like earrings...
No question.
I'm going to bring
that head of yours to him.
How fun!
Nezuko, how much longer?
They're gone!
Breath of Water...
Third Form, Dance of the Swift Current!
Tamayo-san!
Are these two demons
closely related to Kibutsuji?
Most likely.
Then, I'm going to extract blood
from them for sure!
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
I have two favors to ask of you.
One, permission to study
your sister's blood.
Two, to retrieve
blood samples from demons
as closely related to Kibutsuji
as possible.
By "demons closely related to Kibutsuji,"
I meant demons who have received
a massive amount of power from Kibutsuji.
It won't be easy to extract blood
from such demons.
Third Form, Dance of the Swift Current!
Tamayo-san!
Are these two demons
closely related to Kibutsuji?
Most likely.
You think you're going to extract
blood from us?
I don't know what you're scheming,
but I won't allow you
to do anything to displease him!
If you think you can extract blood
from us Twelve Demon Moons,
then have at it!
Watch your back!
Don't let your guard down for a second!
If those two really are Twelve Demon Moons,
then they're undeniably more formidable
than any other demon you've killed until now!
Right! Understood!
Watch my back, don't let
my guard down for a second,
undeniably...
until now...
Right! I'll do my best!
Tamayo-sama!
Let's use those two as decoys
and escape!
I'm just kidding!
Don't kick up dust like that.
So filthy!
She grew new arms
in such a short time!
She can regenerate way faster
than those Final Selection demons!
I'm going to bring
that head of yours to him.
Nezuko!
Now then, why don't you both die at once?
Are you okay, Nezuko?
Hey, Demon Hunter!
You get rid of that arrow man first!
We'll take on the temari woman
with your sister!
Understood!
Nezuko, whatever you do,
don't push yourself too hard.
I'm counting on you.
I swear...
I'm going to extract their blood!
If it means the medicine will be perfected
even a minute sooner,
I'll gladly fight any demon!
I'll fight and win!
There it is!
The line of interval!
What a grimy little urchin you are.
You stay away from me!
The thread snapped!
This hurts! I mean this really...
It seriously hurts!
A move!
Unleash a move to blunt the attack!
Eighth Form,
Waterfall Jar!
He vanished?
You hurt Tamayo-sama!
I'll never forgive you for that!
Tamayo?
Hey, Susamaru, the one over there...
Wouldn't that be Tamayo the Fugitive?
What a great souvenir she'll make!
Is that right?
Idiot!
You mustn't kick it!
How fun!
I like kemari, too!
Yahaba!
Will four heads be enough to take home?
No. We're taking two.
The demon hunter and the fugitive.
We have no use for the other two.
Nezuko...
The bleeding isn't stopping instantly.
She's recovering so slowly.
This medicine will help heal your leg
right away, all right?
What should I do?
I can't lose no matter what!
But even if I can see the line of interval,
it won't be easy to slash him!
Any move would be pointless
unless I can land my blow
in the opening with pinpoint accuracy!
If I'm off by even a little,
the move won't be nearly as potent!
He'll only change the sword's direction
using his arrow skills!
And I hate to say it,
but those eyeballs
on his hands are creepy!
Though I hate to say it!
The speed of this arrow!
It's not going to disappear until it hits me!
And I can't slash it with my sword!
The instant the blade touches it,
I'll get blasted away
in the arrow's direction!
What should I do?
It's all going the way I want it to!
Your arm's going to get twisted right off!
So, you eluded it by spinning in the same
direction as the Kouketsu Arrow?
Damn monkey!
I can't take much more of his attacks!
I gotta strike back!
I gotta change the arrow's direction
without touching it directly!
It's about time for you to die!
Adapt your moves!
First, use the Sixth Form
to envelope the arrow!
Then use the footwork of the Third Form...
to close in on him!
Twist!
Envelope!
Twisting Cyclone Current!
My sword's so heavy!
But...
Second Form...
Modified!
Horizontal Water Wheel!
PREVIEW
RUSTLE RUSTLE
Those are some powerful demons!
Those temari-and-arrow combination attacks
are giving me so much trouble!
Are you okay, Nezuko?
Today, I have a Taishou secret for you
about those demons!
Those two, Yahaba and Susamaru,
met for the first time today.
I hear that they became friends
chatting with each other on their way here.
I can't believe how much in sync
they are when they only just met!
Well, we can't let them beat us!
Nezuko, let's practice our teamwork!
First Form!
Second Form!
Third Form!
Looking good, Nezuko!
Next, Episode 10, "Together Forever."
I'm leaving the temari woman to you!
Let's fight together!
TO BE CONTINUED