EPISODE 7:
KIBUTSUJI MUZAN
Nezuko!
Don't chase after him!
Get back here!
Come to me.
Nezuko!
Urokodaki-san did tell me...
that Nezuko is a demon now.
And that she's not necessarily so weak
that I have to protect her.
Is it all right to let her handle this?
If I have her watch over those two,
I can focus on my attacks.
Nezuko!
I'm going underground!
I want you to protect those two!
You can do that, right?
Inside a swamp...
And these are...
Are these the clothes and belongings
of the people who were kidnapped?
Just look at all the innocent people
they've murdered!
It's unforgivable!
Unforgivable!
Getting hard to breathe, brat?
There's hardly any air inside this swamp.
On top of that, the darkness coiling
around your body must feel pretty heavy.
You can't move the way you would
aboveground! Serves you right!
You should've looked
before you leaped in, you damn fool!
Don't underestimate me!
Just where do you think
I got my training anyway?
The air was thinner on top of Mt. Sagiri!
Not to mention...
there are moves that only unleash
their full potential underwater!
So, they can move at angles
like that inside this swamp?
But it doesn't matter!
All I have to do is slash
when they get near enough to attack!
The form that can be utilized
even when there's no sure footing...
Generating a powerful vortex
with a violent twist
of my upper and lower body!
Here comes the scent!
The line of interval!
Full Focus!
Breath of Water!
Sixth Form!
Twisting Whirlpool!
I can't breathe!
I gotta get out of here!
Nezuko!
This girl is powerful!
She doesn't seem to have mastered
any morphing skills yet,
but look how strong she is anyway!
She must have gotten
a huge amount of blood from him!
She moves so fast!
I can't dive back into the swamp!
But hey,
I'm getting used
to these one-note attacks of hers!
Even if she kicks my head clean off...
Even if my internal organs explode,
demons can regenerate in a flash!
All right!
Now I'm gonna drill a hole
right through your face!
Hands off my sister!
Did I just get taken out?
Both of my other selves
got taken out by this guy!
You give off a scent like rotten oil.
It's a horrible smell!
How many people have you killed?
Listen!
If women live any longer,
they turn ugly and start tasting like crap!
So, we killed them for their own good!
You should be thankful to us demons—
Never mind.
You're going to tell me
what you know about Muzan Kibutsuji.
Talk to me!
Start talking!
I-I can't tell you.
I can't tell you!
DEMON SLAYER:
KIMETSU NO YAIBA
I can't tell you!
You mustn't tell.
You mustn't tell anyone about me.
If you do tell anyone,
I'll know right away.
I'm always watching you.
I can't tell you!
I can't tell you! I can't tell you!
The smell of fear is strong.
He's trembling
all the way down to his bones!
I can't tell you, all right?
Once again, I failed
to get any information.
Nezuko!
She's asleep.
She stopped bleeding, too.
So, she's sleeping in order to recover?
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Wait just a little longer, okay?
I promise to turn you
back into a human again!
Kazumi-san?
Are you all right?
I've lost my fiancée.
How can I be all right?
Kazumi-san...
No matter how many people
you may lose,
you have no choice but to go on living.
No matter how devastating
the blows may be.
What do you know about it?
A kid like you?
I'll be on my way now.
Take this.
I hope you'll find something
of Satoko-san's in there.
So, you went through the same thing, too?
Is that it?
I...
I'm sorry!
That was an awful thing to say!
Please forgive me!
I'm so sorry!
Those heartbreaking pair of hands.
That tough and strong thickness.
Those weren't a boy's hands.
I'm leaving that young woman
in your hands!
All right!
It's not just me.
How many people have you killed,
tortured and tormented?
Kibutsuji Muzan,
I'll never forgive you as long as I live!
Next up, Asakusa, Tokyo!
Rumors of a demon lurking there!
I'm heading to my next mission already?
Oh yes, you are!
Hold on a minute.
No can do!
Come on, just give me
a minute! Hold on! What?
Just shut up and go already!
Are the cities this advanced now?
It's nighttime, but it's so bright out!
The buildings are so tall!
What is this?
The cities...
I feel dizzy.
Uh, let's go that way, Nezuko!
I-I beg your pardon!
UDON
Excuse me.
A bowl of udon
with grated yam on top please.
Uh, sure thing!
I've never been to a place like this.
It's way too crowded.
Here's your udon with grated yam on top!
Thank you very much.
This scent!
Why would it appear here all of a sudden?
It's the same scent
that was left in my house!
Kibutsuji Muzan!
Is this the guy giving off that scent?
It's him!
Daddy?
Who's that?
He's...
It's all right.
Don't worry.
He's...
He's living here,
pretending to be a human!
Is there something I can do for you?
You seem to be quite flustered.
Oh my. What's going on?
Mother!
They're humans!
The girl and the woman...
Their scent is human!
Don't you know?
Can't you tell?
That this guy is a demon?
That he devours humans?
Do you know him?
No.
Much to my consternation,
I've never seen this child before.
He must have mistaken me
for someone else.
Oh, you think so?
Dear, what's the matter?
Dear?
Stop!
PREVIEW
RUSTLE RUSTLE
I've finally tracked down Kibutsuji Muzan!
If I can bring him down,
then Nezuko can be human again!
Still, everyone in Asakusa
sure is stylish, huh?
I bet you'd look great
in an outfit like that!
Now, it's time for a Taishou secret!
Yutaka from the udon shop
was born and raised in Asakusa.
He makes udon in Asakusa
because he loves Asakusa so much, I hear.
A suit, huh?
Now I feel kind of grown-up!
I'd better get back to my mission!
Next, Episode 8,
"Bewitching Fragrance of Blood"!
TO BE CONTINUED