Here he comes...
The man himself!
The crowd's energy changed...
Why's that?
No one expected to see this man compete again!
Every person in here is abuzz with excitement!
Suiryu has entered the ring!
His opponent is Max!
Look at this big-shot.
Could he really be so much better than me?
No, not at all.
Remember back, Lightning Max.
This isn't the one you're after.
Compared to that monster, this guy's just a scrub.
Suiryu!
I have to get stronger.
If I fail, I can't be a hero and protect people.
Sorry it has to be this way,
but I consider you a capable opponent,
so I'll use you to test out my
new monster-fighting technique!
So you're a pro hero, right?
I see.
You train with lofty ideals in mind.
I guess everyone's got
their own reason to seek strength.
Fighters, take your stance.
Begin!
Lightning...
...Front Tuck Giant Double Axe Kick!
The reason I sought strength...
...was so I could live the easy life.
I was stronger. Sorry.
D-Did you see that, Charanko?
That kick Suiryu did?
I did. Why?
Wait,
how're you so calm?
Oh, I get it.
Because he's such a newb...
A Class A hero defeated by a single kick...
I didn't realize so many people
were stronger than professional heroes.
Well, it is only natural.
Master Saitama was but a
hobbyist under everyone's radar.
It is to be expected that there would be more like him.
Though I doubt anyone here
could rise to Master's level.
That man there, however, might satisfy
Master's wish to experience martial arts.
This is...
Ladies and gentlemen,
I see you're still riled up,
but our next match features Benpats of
"The Way of the Cruel" vs. Snakebite Snek!
The winner will face Suiryu in the second round!
A Class A hero?
You don't look too tough.
If I can beat Suiryu, who defeated Lightning Max,
it might have a positive effect on my ranking.
Here we go.
Snakebite Fist!
That flashy stance isn't fooling anyone!
Eat knuckles, bottom-ranked bastard!
I'm not the bottom...
I'm the bottom of Class A!
We have a situation!
There's a group of violent monsters nearby!
What?
We have to evacuate the stadium!
Oh crap!
I'll announce it right—!
That won't be necessary.
Huh?
Bakuzan?!
Evacuating would only invite panic.
But if the monsters attack the venue...
We have all these martial arts masters here.
Could anywhere be safer?
That's true...
Don't worry.
If the monsters get inside the arena, I will slay them.
More monsters?
There have been so many lately.
Now they have come here to City C...
Should I tell Master?
No, I can handle this.
The tournament must go on.
No matter how many there are,
I will exterminate them all.
W-Wasn't expecting that...
He's not weak at all...
Snek wins!
I want to believe I rank among the strongest.
But reality can be a cruel thing.
The field of top heroes abounds
with the monstrously powerful.
Incinerate.
It's Demon Cyborg!
That was awesome!
We're saved!
I am currently in City C, near the stadium.
Give me an update.
Monsters have simultaneously
appeared in multiple areas.
We have five confirmed in City C alone.
Mr. Demon Cyborg,
there's a monster down that way, too!
And another over there!
I came from down that way!
I eliminated one.
Where are the other four?
There're monsters all over!
Understood. We'll direct you.
Using a combined electrical shock and strike,
Boltane takes the victory!
Gatling's super-fast punches were like a barrage!
Hamukichi is down! It's a knockout!
And Dave ends things quickly
with a thunderous body press!
Logy is out!
The referee stops the fight!
Choze sure is tough!
Mentai was simply outclassed!
Rocket Stomp!
There is another monster nearby.
Tell me where it is,
or suffer excruciating pain until death.
Your choice.
Next on the card is Jakumen,
from Giga Pro Wrestling!
He's up against Sourface,
with his Sourface-style Kenpo!
A battle between newcomers!
Do your best, Sourface!
Shut up, you!
I used to be Master Bang's number-two disciple!
He's pretty huge.
Now, now.
I'm stronger!
Probably.
Remember all that strenuous training!
This guy's
got a scary face.
I'll be taking your face.
Found you.
You will be eliminated.
Oh ho?
Somebody famous.
Can I carve off your face too?!
How ya like my blade work?
I baited you into hitting my reinforced skull.
High-Voltage Fist.
Begone.
He took care of them in no time at all.
Genos really does have the power of a demon.
Demon Cyborg!
The last monster is two klicks to your northwest.
Several heroes have already engaged it.
Can you speak?
Wh-When you fight the bastard,
don't take your eyes off him...
He was always behind us...
A Class S hero?
Have you got something against cockroaches too?
I have something against bug monsters in general.
This is the last one...
If I can take him out quickly,
maybe I can still catch Master's fight.
I'm pretty hard to get rid of.
Jakumen taps out!
Sourface wins with a beautiful choke hold!
The two fighters congratulate one another!
Such beautiful sportsmanship!
Did you win, Sourface?
What?!
You didn't see the match, Charanko?
Your valiant comrade won!
I was in the bathroom.
You're hopeless.
Wait.
Your opponent next match...
Be wary of him.
I've seen Bakuzan in action.
Oh, dang it.
He's not the type to show mercy,
even toward inferior opponents.
I undid my belt in the bathroom
Hey!
and I forgot how to retie it.
Did you hear a word I said?!
The next match is Charanko,
who advanced by beating Zakkos,
versus two-time consecutive champion Bakuzan.
His frightening "Dark Hell Murder Arts"
have turned many of his
matches into pure bloodbaths!
Will his opponent once again be demolished
and hospitalized after a one-sided battle?
Hmph.
All I do is teach lessons
to those who don't belong here.
Listen up.
When martial artists trade blows,
it's not some friendly "sport".
It's kill or be killed, life and...
Hey!
Well, this'll do.
You're dead.
Begin!
Here we go, folks!
How will Charanko fight
against the likes of Bakuzan?
His guard's wide open.
What's with this fool?
Does he really want to fight?
Bakuzan boldly closes in!
Are you...
an amateur?
Yeah.
Truth is, this is my first time at this.
Give me a taste of your martial arts.
Fine with me.
I'll give you the full-service execution you desire.
Starting with the legs.
My Demon Sweeper Low Kick will shatter
your bones so you never walk again.
Next, your body,
starting with my Bear Killer Mid Kick,
followed by my Carnage Punch.
Both your arms will break,
and your major organs will explode.
Finally, your head.
Oh!
My Straight-To-Hell Hand Chop
will split your skull and send you straight—
Don't touch my head!
He's outside the ring...
Darn it.
I blew another chance for a match.
The fight is over!
Call the doctor! Bring the stretcher!
What a bracket buster that was!
Bakuzan, a favorite for the championship,
beaten by first-time fighter, Charanko!
Another one-shot knockout.
All right.
I'll do that too.
We've invited Mr. Saynuthin to tell us about
the monster emergencies occurring in various areas.
Mr. Saynuthin,
what are your thoughts on the simultaneous
monster attacks going on right now?
It's too early to say much?
Ah, we have some breaking news.
Class A hero Lightning Genji was
found collapsed with severe injuries.
Any comment, sir, on this new development?
It seems we're all searching for the right words.
Hey!
Pull yourself together!
Ow!
Are you okay, Mohican?
You must've seen a man and his child here.
What happened to the child?
Mr. Richman's son, Narcisse,
was kidnapped by monsters.
What?!
For what purpose?
We don't know.
But Mr. Richman represents seven percent
of the Association's funding.
Losing his trust would be devastating.
Indeed.
The rescue of Narcisse is of the utmost priority.
Put every hero Class A and above on it.
But sir...
Can we allow the monsters'
rampage to go unchecked?
Class S hero Metal Bat was found
unconscious and in critical condition.
C'mon! What's the matter?
You can't hit me like that!
Tsk...
I can't track his movements!
Looking for me? Here I am!
It's not just his speed.
On top of his unique gait throwing me off,
he's attacking from the buildings' blind spots.
You leave me no choice.
I didn't want to use this, but...
Oh?
You got some special ability
you've been squirreling away?
Gonna shoot laser beams
from your eyes or something?
I originally opposed installing this component,
but Doctor Kuseno was right.
Heat-seeking missiles?
Poison gas?
In situations where my
adversary gains the upper hand,
I must acknowledge reality if I am to grow.
I sure hope it's not roach repellent!
Wh-Wh-What's this?!
M-My legs...!
What have you done?!
It's an ultra-strong adhesive.
I came prepared to stop even
a speedy ninja in his tracks.
But to use this acknowledges
that his speed is an issue for me.
What're you talking about?
No concern of yours.
Incinerate.
He sacrificed his legs to escape?
No matter. He won't survive that.
Better return to the stadium.
I might make Master's fight.
High-speed object approaching!
The roach?!
No, something different...
Hey...
You guys...
Don't fall so easily for the enemy's tricks.
Your face is so cute when painted with panic.
Unfortunately, these fools are my pets now.
How'd that feel, having your lackeys taken?
Come now, you've got to resist more!
Or have you been holding back?
What if I let you join
Mistress Super S's harem of slaves?
It'll come back to bite you.
Shut up!
You've held up, even after taking on so many.
But how much more can you take?
Time for some real punishment!
That did the trick.
Now you're mine, body and soul.
And I believe you're one of those esper sisters, yes?
Your younger sister is the
Class S hero Terrible Tornado.
Which means I can keep you around as bait
to tempt her to come out and play!
Nice to have a big name as your little sister, huh?
Even after all that lash, her mind's her own.
Such strength of will...
I hate girls like her.
That hurt, bitch!
I thought you'd be the bait
to snag your sister, but forget it!
I'm killing you right now!
You will be seeing my older sister regardless.
What are these tremors?!
She was closer than I thought.
She felt it when I was in pain.
That's her.
Explosions?
Something is approaching...
Something frightening.
My sister...
Terrible Tornado!
S-Super S!
The heroes had a monster of their own...!
This is more serious than I imagined.
Our side... was wiped out...
We need to retreat and regroup...
That's her.
Tatsumaki!
I'm still fighting this—
You can go home, Fubuki.
I'll clean up the whole mess.
You people!
Delay her while I escape!
Wait, Tatsumaki!
They're my team!
Don't attack them!
I said not to attack...
That was barely an attack.
No, that counts...
And these nobodies aren't a team,
they're just burdens.
I don't know why you still hang
around with that Class B club.
Now look! The monster got away!
Why'd I start chit-chatting with you?
There are other monsters to destroy.
Let the nobodies know, will you?
In real emergencies, if they don't evacuate,
they're just in the way.
I mustn't doubt myself,
so I've tried to keep it out of my mind,
but I can't.
It's bothering me again.
Wanna eat humans!
Wanna eat human flesh!
That's far enough!
Now that I, Class A hero Snakebite Snek,
have arrived, you won't lay a finger on anyone!
Looking back, I once shone
more brightly than anyone.
My spirit was filled with the pride
of being one of few heroes who
truly had the power to protect people.
But then, gradually, reality set in.
There were others who,
try as I might, I could never defeat.
Even among the nameless masses,
there were others far stronger than myself.
Are professional heroes really necessary?
Recently, I've been having doubts.
If I didn't exist...
If the Hero Association didn't exist...
Wouldn't someone else
defeat the monsters in our place?
At the very least,
there seems no need to protect this man.
I liked Max from earlier. He was nice and aggressive.
Says the guy who's been on
his heels and won't fight back?
I was just checking out how skilled you are.
Class A heroes make a lot of money, I hear.
If your level is all it takes,
it might be worth my while.
Just kidding.
I want money, not a job!
How'd you get to be strong?
Why is a guy like you,
who has no real purpose, so strong?
Just talented, maybe?
Everything about you disgusts me.
Back when I trained,
all I did was keep my master company.
I haven't even practiced in years.
But how'd you get to be a hero?
I mean, with that level of ability.
Wh-What?!
More and more strong monsters are appearing.
Even performing at your best,
you won't make any difference.
Heroes or no heroes,
those who are going to survive will survive.
Monsters or no monsters,
natural selection will weed out the weak.
It's the way things are.
Are you suggesting we ignore
the people being attacked by monsters?
What's going on?
Is this part of the show?
Monsters!
How'd they get in the hospital?!
We'll hold them off here!
Everyone head to the roof!
Whatever happens, we'll survive.
What's a monster doing at a prison?
If you came for the Boss,
he broke out to bash you bastards!
Puri-Puri Prisoner is not here?
Doesn't matter.
Who do you mean by "we"?
The strong, of course.
What?
Understand now?
They sound excited.
Report, Gyoro-Gyoro.
Have my monsters created chaos?
Oh, yes indeed.
Some casualties were incurred,
but overall, the advantage belongs to us.
The Hero Association is in a panic.
And what of Gouketsu?
He's heading to the venue where
the martial artists have gathered.
Our confirmed victories include Demon Cyborg,
Metal Bat,
and Metal Knight.
Yet our greatest weapons still await their turn.
You may be assured of the
Monster Association's overwhelming victory,
O Monster King Orochi!