What is it now?
You can't even get up?
Tell me, Charanko...
What have you been doing
here the past six months?
When I made you my disciple,
didn't I say to train like your life depended on it?
I cannot see you ever improving your skills.
You haven't one iota of talent for the martial arts!
From this moment, you are expelled from the dojo.
Never come here again!
Bang is acting strangely?
He switched to full-contact training,
then beat the crap out of me.
But Master Bang has always been so kind-hearted...
Something's going on.
I thought you guys might know what it is!
I do not.
Bang, as in the Class S hero Silverfang?
If you're done talking, let's play some more.
There's more of them now...
I can make an educated guess.
It probably has to do with Garou.
Garou?!
The guy Master chased out of our dojo?
Why him?
I see.
So you haven't heard?
Bang's former disciple, Garou,
has been added to the Association's
wanted list as a violent monster.
Bang volunteered to take him down.
A monster?! Garou?!
Apparently, there was an
incident at Association HQ.
The Association's keeping it quiet,
but if a violent battle ensues,
people might get hurt.
Perhaps that is why Bang pushed you away?
I had no idea.
So Master Bang
considers me a burden?
Master, what are your thoughts on Bang's behavior?
I don't really know the old dude so well...
"Silverfang",
now that's a cool hero name.
Especially compared to "Caped Baldy".
There is one thing that bothers me.
Who are you?
Master, this pissant is Charanko,
Bang's current top disciple.
You met him before.
Huh? I did?
I can't allow myself to be a burden.
For my master's sake, I need to stop Garou.
But it's not like I can just go find him.
And even if I did track him down, I'd only—
Hey, you.
You're a hero, yeah?
I am indeed.
I'm the Unlicensed Rider.
Time to hunt.
"Hunt"? What do you mean?
You don't seem like one of my fans.
To complete my evolution into a monster,
you're the exact prey I need.
Found you!
You sure that's the one?
I'm sure.
Now, time for a little payb—
You came for vengeance, Tank-Top Vegetarian?
You're here to throw away the life
you barely escaped with before?
Your stupidity is almost cute.
Your muscle-head friends
won't be leaving alive either.
Die!
What the—?!
I hear you roughed up my boy.
A Class S?! Hell yeah!
Looks like I hooked a big one.
This is perfect!
I'm fired up!
Tank-Top Tackle!
There it is! Master's Tank-Top Tackle!
He's used that move to take out tons of monsters!
Get him, Master!
That bastard can't stand up to—
Big Bro!
He didn't go down!
Get ready to run, Lil Bro!
Is this guy
seriously
human?
Have you put all your affairs in order?
I'm an old man, alone in the world.
Just like you.
There you go, being ridiculous.
I said my farewells to several hundred disciples!
You cut ties to everything you have
to come to your dear brother's aid.
Who could ask for more, brother?
If we don't stop that Garou fellow,
he'll no doubt come after my dojo too one day.
Of course I came!
We must be careful, brother.
No telling how strong the
wretch has become by now.
He certainly concerned you enough to call me.
Yeah, another Tank-Top Punch!
When he survived Master's tackle,
I was scared for a second!
Looks like this won't take too long.
He's human.
That's for certain.
But then,
why?
Why this premonition that
I should kill him right here?
Unfortunately,
you die now!
Hold it right there!
Unlicensed Rider?!
Have you no shame?!
A Class S hero, about to kill a human?!
You already won the fight!
The bastard attacked a hero! It's his own fault!
Stay out of it!
We'll teach him to mess with us!
That's enough.
What he says is right.
I didn't earn the right to wear this tank-top
so I could battle humans.
Listen up, you...
Let this be a lesson never to harm others again.
Yeah, all right.
I'm leaving.
Sorry for the trouble.
Fuck that!
I'm still gonna slaughter every last one of you.
Yeah, thought so.
You die right here, right now!
Damn, it slipped out.
I've been avoiding this style,
since it reminds me of the old geezer.
Eh, whatevs...
This guy
was hiding his true strength?
Imagine that!
A Class S hero on his knees!
Don't think you've won.
You caught me off guard is all.
You stay right there.
Watch while Garou the Monster
murders your "bros".
Garou?
He's that human who calls himself a monster!
D-Don't! Leave them alone!
Justice Crash!
Now, you douchebags come at me too.
Garou!
I've already seen through your fighting style.
I'm done with you,
Tank-Top Master.
Let's see.
All that's left is a little clean up.
Scumbag!
You think you can win against our numbers?!
Damn you!
Stop!
Help!
That's enough, Garou!
You're a disgrace to the dojo!
Take this!
Fist of Flowing Water Crushing R—!
This is awful.
We were too late.
Hey, Bang,
can you predict where he might appear next?
Bang?
Charanko.
I heard the hero hunter
took down Tank-Top Master.
No way!
He defeated a Class S hero?
They say Tank-Top's disciples and
Unlicensed Rider were beat all to hell.
So Class S and Class C alike are being hunted?!
What're we supposed to do?
How about showing some spine?
Let's us three capture this "hero hunter" ourselves!
Yeah, right.
He beat a Class S.
Don't you get it?
He's not some scary monster.
He's just a human being.
But I heard he's Silverfang's former disciple.
Well I know a bit of martial arts myself.
If an opponent punches like this, you do this!
And if they come this way, you block like this.
And if he comes at you like this, you go like th—!
He's here.
You came all this way to see me.
Thanks, Saitama.
Yeah.
Can I put these bananas here?
Sure, thanks.
Oh, they're for you.
It was all over the Hero Association's
newsletter, you know?
Said dozens of heroes were
beaten by a single monster.
Lucky you survived, eh?
Here, have a banana.
He was a human.
What?
A human who called himself a monster.
But he was strong.
A scary-strong human.
Was he stronger than that fish monster thing?
Hmm...
Deep Sea King was insanely tough,
but somehow this guy was different.
His moves.
They're sophisticated martial arts techniques.
It seems Silverfang raised a true monster.
Any idea who this eavesdropper is?
Shh!
That's Tank-Top Master, the Class S hero.
Oh, right! He was in the newspaper.
It said he took the worst beating of all.
That's because I kept getting back up!
Damn it...
I never imagined I'd lose to a punk like him.
The path of martial arts is a treacherous one.
Martial arts?
Have a banana.
Huh?
Oh, thanks.
So, think you could tell me the details?
Hey there, kid.
Interesting book you've got there.
This is King, a Class S hero.
He's the strongest ever.
This is Lightning Genji, a Class A hero.
He patrols my neighborhood all the time.
See? I got his autograph.
His autograph, eh?
I want his autograph, too.
Think you could help me find him?
Sure thing!
Are you into heroes, mister?
That hero almanac is cool.
Hey, could you lend it to me for a week or so?
What? I don't want to.
C'mon, don't be all stingy.
Oh, look at that!
It lists monsters, too.
Now that's exciting.
Huh?
Exciting? The monster pages?
They're super scary.
The scarier the better.
These guys are way cooler.
What?
You've got some bad taste, mister.
Aww man...
I wish I were listed in this book too.
You want to be a hero?
I do too, actually.
But I'm so bad at sports and stuff.
That's for the best.
You're not too nice, mister.
Alright.
It's patrol time.
I'd better get going.
According to that almanac, Golden Ball from
Class A shows up at his usual pub around this time.
See you later, little turd.
Be careful on your patrol, mister.
I will.
And don't call me "mister".
You're making me feel old.
Huh? You say something, mister?
Go home, runt.
He parried,
sidestepped, or slipped all my attacks.
And he responded perfectly
with throws and counters.
His moves reflect his opponents'
power back at double strength.
Hits on pressure points and joints are also trouble.
Where he strikes,
you suffer a loss of physical function.
Most monsters that I've encountered
have relied on their overwhelming physical strength.
Garou is different.
His techniques are devised for breaking humans.
In other words,
he's built precisely for defeating heroes.
You want opponents good at martial arts?
Yeah,
I'm feeling curious.
Know anybody good?
Er, was it...
Chumpo?
My name's Charanko!
Here,
I'll even give you a banana.
Don't put it there!
You should ask Master Bang for help.
He seems to like you, after all.
Nah, what would I do if the
old dude strained himself?
Now you're just being rude!
Some amateur can't just go
around challenging the pros!
First you master the basic forms...
No, before that, you build your stamina,
running up and down hundreds of stairs.
Maybe start by cleaning the dojo!
If you don't know anyone, just forget it.
Wait! Wait!
There's this mixed martial arts
tournament I signed up for...
I'm pretty sure I have the ticket.
Here.
It's all crumpled up.
I registered to fight, but I'm gonna have to forfeit.
This'll get you inside, though,
so take it and go watch the matches.
You'll get to observe plenty of fighting styles.
Thanks.
And you're forfeiting, Charanko?
Well, I'm injured.
It says the prize is three million.
Well, it's a big tournament.
Prize money: three million.
Just to be clear,
you can't enter in someone else's place.
Hey, are you listening?
You're the Class A hero, Golden Ball.
I'd like a word.
Step outside.
I'm drinking here, buddy.
What the hell?!
Aw man, what a waste.
Okay, tough guy.
There's a parking lot nearby.
We'll do it there.
I've seen your kind...
Dweebs looking to take on a professional hero.
If it's liquid courage making you step up,
better step off now.
While you can still walk.
Quiet down! Your drunken—
You...!
Not too sharp, are you, "hero hunter"?
How did Tank-Top Master lose to a jerkoff like you?
See, I ain't too bad at hunting things down myself.
So I'll lay you out quick,
then get a new drink!
He read the trajectory from my hand movement.
In that case, take this!
Rebound Shot.
Oh, lucky nothing vital got hit.
How about it?
Ain't heroes incredible?
I'm lucky, you say?
Because you're drunk, your coordination's off.
Not finishing me with that
shot means the end for you.
Unfortunately for you, I got plenty more ammo.
Shape Memory Golden Bullets!
Multi-shot!
Killer Move...
Golden Breakout!
He's dodging all that with minimal movement...
I take it back.
This kid's on another level...
Still,
I got one last shot.
Better make it count!
How about it?
Ain't monsters incredible?
It's over.
Die.
You weren't in the pub, so I thought
you'd perhaps forgotten about our drink.
Class A hero, Spring Mustachio.
I see my reputation precedes me.
And you, I presume,
are the much-rumored hero hunter.
Ding ding ding.
Your prize is: You get crushed, too.
His right leg's injured.
He can't use his footwork.
I see it.
That's useful to know.
What about you?
Kinda tight quarters for that long thing.
Let's find out, shall we?
Now you're mine.
Tomboy!
I've
got you!
Did you know?
Your killer moves
are listed in the hero almanac.
Once I know your weapons and patterns, it's over.
You're plenty cocky now,
but you can't keep this up forever.
Oh, I'll be getting much, much stronger.
Take me down me if you can.
Until then, I'll be as cocky as I want.
Say, the Hero Association
makes lots of money, right?
Don't talk nonsense, my dear.
It takes a lot of capital to maintain peace.
We don't make money!
Then how did you buy me this?
Hm?
And you always spend so much at our place.
That's for peace, of course.
As a director of the Hero Association,
having fun with you is a necessary expense.
People like me who fight evil on the front lines
need to relax and recharge our batteries.
"Relax", "relax".
Do you need to "relax" every day?
Exactly right.
Next time, maybe I'll bring Handsome Mask along.
What? Really?
I'm a huge fan!
I'll introduce you for a kiss on the cheek.
Well, I don't know...
You really, really mean it?
Introduce him to me, too.
I'll even land you a kiss on the cheek.
"Relax", "relax"!
It's for peace!
I was riding high after hunting down those Class A's.
Now I feel like I stepped in shit.
"Fighting evil on the front lines"?
What a load!
Oh, finally.
I've been looking all day.
Was he tailing me?
Is he a hero too?
Never seen that face before.
Probably some nobody,
trying to climb the ranks by capturing me.
But tables turn!
Huh?
What's the big idea?
Who the hell are you?
Are you trying to rob me?
Don't bother me when I'm shopping.
Excuse me!
I'd like this one.
3,000 yen, please.
That much?
Not bad.
Master...
Has it come to that?
No, that's not it.
It's not like I'm planning
to wear a wig the rest of my—!
Doctor Kuseno, this is Genos.
There is an emergency.
No, it has to do with Master Saitama's condition.
The reinforced artificial hair fibers we discussed,
can they be implanted into living skin?
Yes, that is right.
It appears necessary after all.
Black hair-fibers are available, correct?
Then when are you available
for the implant procedure?
As soon as possible.
Wednesday next week... I see.
Yes, I will be there too.
I understand.
Please arrange it for that date.
Thank you very much.
Master Saitama!
Are you available next Wednesday?
You can't just transplant reinforced hair-fibers
into someone's head without asking.
I'm using this to enter a fighting tournament.
As Charanko.
Today?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go see what this
"martial arts" thing is all about.