Now I will cover the world in darkness!
You won't get away with this,
Devil Earl!
That lame theme song means Justice Man is here.
Just when it was getting good,
the hero butts in again!
Hang in there! Don't give up, Devil Earl!
Kick Justice Man's butt!
Justice Punch!
Darn it! He got beat again...
When will there be a monster
that can defeat Justice Man?
What?
Heroes never lose?
Why not?
Does good always win out?
But that's so unfair!
Monsters have things they want, too!
And monsters try really hard...
So why do they always end up getting killed?
I root for them! What about what I think?!
Monsters are just cooler.
Why should the popular win, while the hated lose?
It's tragic!
If that's how the world works...
I'll become the strongest monster,
and I will lose to no one!
What am I doing here?
My memories from last night are so cloudy.
Last night's brutal attack on Director Zeimeet
was almost certainly the work
of the "hero hunter", Garou.
You mean he's now targeting not just heroes,
but the entire Association?
He was able to defeat Tank-Top Master.
Ordinary protective details will not dispel fear.
Issue a cautionary memo.
Executives should remain indoors if possible.
When going out, they must be
accompanied by a Class S hero.
Is that realistic?
Recently, the Class S seem
so busy dealing with monsters.
The directors are the conduits to our sponsors.
Their safety takes precedence.
Act as a bodyguard for an executive?
I refuse.
"Why?"
Because I'm in the middle of a battle.
My opponent is down.
Now I'm going to take out the boss in his secret lair.
Ask someone else.
I'm counting on you to protect us today,
Mr. Metal Bat.
They said it was a critical assignment,
but when I got here...
Association executives are
now targets too, apparently.
But my boy here insists on trying "peasant food".
Wow! Look, Papa!
They've got crème caramel!
This sushi won't total even 10,000 yen.
How amusing to experience just how inferior it is.
What is this?
Am I in Hell?!
Hey! Don't put empty plates back on the belt!
Why not?
They need it to tally your bill.
Come now, it's only good
manners to return one's plate.
I said don't put them back!
The color of this uni is off-putting.
Perhaps they have caviar?
What's "medium-fatty tuna"?
Is anything but extra-fatty even edible?
Don't put it back!
The next time a plate goes back, I kill them both.
Phone call?
It's my little sister!
Stay here while I step away for a second.
I didn't have a choice.
An important assignment suddenly came up.
I'll take you shopping another time.
Huh? Where am I now?
Mouse Sushi.
Oops!
No, that's not it.
It really is an assignment!
Come on, don't cry...
I'll explain later.
I-I have to hang up.
Bye!
I'm the one who should be crying.
Last time I do a favor for some exec!
Crap! Is it Garou?!
Papa!
I don't think that's him.
Help him!
That thing has my son!
That's the Hero Association executive, all right.
With his kid. Perfect.
We're taking the child.
Hold it.
No one's taking a step out of this place.
They haven't paid yet.
Charanko said he signed up on a whim.
What a dummy.
But this might do.
Some seriously strong fighters could be here.
What name did you register under?
Uh...
Charanko.
All right. Please write in your fighting style.
Fighting style?
Uh,
what was it, now?
I think it's...
This must be the tournament bracket.
Some fighters got seeded.
This Bakuzan guy must be tough.
In the opposite bracket, Suiryu is the top seed...
Yo!
Charanko, from the dojo, right?
Oh no, someone who knows Charanko!
Hey, what's the matter?
Surely you haven't forgotten me?
"Fist of Seltzer Water on the Rocks"?
That a joke?
Well, I don't blame you for being nervous.
After all, you never could beat me.
That jerk.
He better not be competing in my place.
Nah, he wouldn't be that stupid.
Wait, Saitama does seem pretty friggin' stupid.
Saitama?
Hey, you're...?
Are you acquainted with Saitama?
Charanko, know why I entered this tournament?
Who cares?
Just hurry up and get out of here.
Two reasons.
Reason one: This Super Fight is ideal
for making a name as a martial artist.
Master Bang was the champion once.
And reason two:
The incident at the previous tournament.
A masked fighter named
Wolfman won the championship.
But after the tournament,
the real Wolfman was found unconscious.
Because of that,
registration under an alias and use
of headwear became strictly banned.
H-Headwear?
You lied about your fighting style.
That might be a grey area.
What happens if they find out?
You'd be disqualified and banned for life.
And after the incident,
you'll probably be sued
and hit with a heavy fine as well.
Might even be arrested.
R-Really?!
What's the matter?
No way...
You...
...know exactly who the perpetrator was, don't you?
I'm safe!
I saw his technique in a video.
There's no doubt.
The criminal is...
...Garou!
Yo. I'm back.
Oh, hey Mister!
Patrolling again?
I told you not to call me "mister".
Now lend me that book.
I still don't want to.
Huh?
You know!
Let's read it together!
Garou?
There's that name again.
It was six months ago...
Right after it went down and he was expelled.
It had to be him.
"It went down"?
You were skipping classes, so you don't know.
It was a day when Master Bang was out.
Hmm?
I'm done.
Huh?
There's nothing left for me to learn here.
Let's fight for real.
He'd hidden his true self as he sharpened his fangs.
If it hadn't been for him,
we wouldn't have had to leave the dojo.
Damn him!
That's why I'm here today!
I'll win this tournament,
and get my mojo back!
I want to know that I can
hold my own against Garou!
But I never imagined you,
the runt of the dojo,
would enter the Super Fight tourney!
You got lofty ideas.
I heard you even call yourself the "top disciple".
Don't let it go to your head.
I see.
You're saying Saitama might enter in your place?
Yeah.
If by some chance an amateur managed to get in,
he'd get himself killed!
Nothing to worry about.
Because, you know,
he's a hero.
If I'd have known that Garou would be expelled,
I'd never have left the dojo.
Then Master Bang's top disciple right now
would be me, Sourface.
Whatcha think?
Wanna practice choke holds
until you black out again?
But you left the dojo, right?
What?
I, Charanko, took on Garou by myself.
That's why I'm here: to get rid of Garou.
If he keeps up his hero hunting,
one day we're gonna meet.
What I'm saying is,
someone who runs off
shouldn't be acting like a big shot.
I'm gonna make you eat those words!
The Super Fight is a one-day tournament.
If by chance you win and move up,
we'll meet in the ring.
If that happens, I'll teach you
what it's like to be in a real fight.
A real fight...
I really don't remember what they're like.
Did you see that, Papa?!
He took care of the monsters in no time!
Okay, let me get a few pics.
Hey, it's still dangerous. Let's get out of here.
Venus Peopletrap and I were no match for you.
But we expected you to easily overcome us,
Metal Bat.
You are truly a Class S hero.
Yet the strong often mistakenly believe
they're at the top of the food chain.
In fact, I believed that once.
Not done dying yet, bug?
Want me to finish you off?
But then, Senior Centipede appeared.
Another one?!
I will avenge you, little one.
That thing's gross!
This one's a whole lot bigger!
What's that smell...?
These things got nothing to do with Garou, I guess?
No use thinking about it!
I'll just smash 'em!
That's right!
No matter what terror he faces,
he stands up and fights.
I'm saying,
you don't have to worry about Saitama.
Y-Yeah, but...
He'd never use a false identity and break the rules.
After all, he's a hero.
Uh... uh...
Well, in that case, it's okay.
Yeah!
So much time to kill...
And this is Watchdog Man.
Cute, isn't he?
Just looks like a guy in a dog suit to me.
Is he tough?
Of course!
He's a Class S hero.
Class S Rank 12, eh?
He keeps watch over City Q
from his lookout in Watchdog Plaza.
He's always hanging out there!
Really...
Warning! Emergency evacuation!
A monster has appeared
in the shopping district of City S.
Threat level: Demon.
The Class S hero Metal Bat
is currently engaging the monster.
Citizens outside are requested
to move indoors quickly.
Mister?!
You heard her.
Hurry up and get home.
Okay!
We repeat:
Warning! Emergency evacuation!
Centipede Parade!
Quite an obstinate enemy.
I understand how he could beat Junior Centipede.
What are you damn worms after?
Why target that man and his son?
If you beat us, we'll tell you.
At last, my Hypno-Scent is taking effect...
Excellent!
Losing... consciousness...
Eternal rest is yours!
Take this! And this! And this!
He hit... himself?!
He's gone mad!
That cleared my head!
What?!
He's gotten even stronger?!
It shouldn't be possible
to undo the sedative so easily!
What happened?
Once my fighting spirit's up,
I can take almost anything.
You really slapped the hell out of me just now.
But I'm a nice guy,
so one whack each,
and we'll call it even!
It's been a while since I felt that much fight in me.
I didn't ask the monsters what they were after!
Totally slipped my mind.
Looks like they're uninjured.
Hey wake up, you two!
Need a good punch to get you up?!
We're here to help!
We'll help you fight!
I just finished up.
What?!
Thank goodness for Metal Bat.
Now the director and his son are—
What is it?
Junior Centipede and Senior Centipede
appeared one after the other.
That means...
It can't be!
Remember what happened two years ago?
If he appears again...
Right.
Mere bodyguards won't be enough.
The entire city will be leveled.
That's...
The giant bug monster, Elder Centipede!
It's threat level Dragon!
Dragon?
I'll request some Class S backup.
Let's keep clear for now.
Bastard's here for those two over there.
Get them to safety while I occupy him.
Fast as you can!
Hurry!
Now, then.
What to do?
Is he looking this way?
You shan't escape!
It's charging!
Don't look back! Run!
It's friggin' hard!
Out of the way!
Tagged with a full swing and not even a crack...
But...
The bastard protected its face-thing when I went in.
That's where I need to bash it!
He's coming after us!
No, look!
On top!
That's...!
Killer Move!
Fighting Spirit!
Dragon Pummelin'!
Centipede Undulation!
So this is what Level Dragon is like!
Mankind wasn't meant to face this kind of thing!
Warning! Emergency evacuation!
A new monster with a threat level
of Dragon has appeared in City S.
Evacuation shelters are no guarantee of safety.
Evacuate as far outside of the city as possible.
What happened to the heroes? Were they defeated?
It's the end of the world!
We have to get away!
Well, well.
Everyone's all excited.
Level Dragon gets announced,
and suddenly it's a party.
I wonder if Metal Bat will
still be alive when I find him.
Metal Bat?
How did he...?!
Oh, that's how.
A Class S beaten up by a monster other than me?
I wasted my time—
Better get back to it.
H-Hold it right there, Metal Bat!
Huh?
You're alive. That changes things!
My second Class S.
You'll be fighting me now.
I'm hunting you.
Huh?!
You serious, dumbass?
Can't you see that centipede?
Get your ass out—
Now I see.
You're that human who calls himself
a "hero-hunting monster".
That's right.
I am Garou.
You can see I'm busy.
Come at me,
and I'll take that crazeball head of yours,
and crack it wide open!
Whoa!
They're saying City S is at threat level Dragon.
Will they be okay?
Ladies, are you on your way to watch Super Fight?
Mind if I come with?
It's been so long, I forgot how to get there.
A-Aren't you...
Yeah!
So it's all right then?