You think you're hot stuff, don't you?
But today, I end you.
Get a load of this!
Light low kick spam!
It's a cheese stunlock combo I discovered!
Good grief. You just don't get it.
Let me show you
what real "cheese" is.
Take that!
Bunny bunny hop!
I demand a rematch!
This game's trash!
It's fucking shit!
Huh? What's this?
Oh,
they gave those out to a bunch of heroes recently.
Still a prototype or something.
It shows requests for backup and their locations.
I didn't get one.
Hmm?
Oh,
maybe they figured you'd have trouble using it,
what with the buttons and all.
We're going again.
This time my low kicks will
be so fast I'll beat you for sure!
We received a message from the Monster Associ—
We received a message
from the Monster Association.
Something's taken him over!
Get the heroes stationed at HQ in here!
This is West Building, conference room 7!
Should I fire?
Shoot it! Shoot it!
Hold!
Let's hear the message.
Ladies and gentlemen of the
Hero Association, greetings.
I am Staff Officer Gyoro-Gyoro
of the Monster Association.
We have the son of your
highest-ranking executive with us.
What is it you want?
We have but one demand.
We are sick and tired of being
oppressed because we are monsters.
From this day on, we wish to be left alone.
Right now, we hide in an abandoned area of City Z
where we eke out a meager
and barren existence together.
We seek nothing presumptuous,
like leading lives in the outside world.
Our offer is to halt our conflict
with ordinary humans
and to cease entering areas where they live.
In exchange,
we want you to guarantee us a safe place to live.
All we hope for is the realization of a society
where humans and monsters can coexist.
Then why this destructive rampage?
By demonstrating our strength,
we wished for you to understand
that our proposal has merit.
I'm sure by now we both would like
to avoid any further losses.
An offer of a ceasefire? About what we expected.
Very well.
We pledge that henceforth the Monster
Association will remain unmolested.
Now release the hostage immediately.
Revel in your momentary sense of security, vermin.
Before you can extend your power,
you will all be extermin—
Oops...
my finger twitched.
Now, now, Destrochloridium, we're still negotiating.
I'm a bad boy!
I must show restraint!
H-He's dead!
Have you truly come to negotiate?!
Teasing grown adults is so fun!
Humans and monsters "coexisting"?
This is truly my best prank yet!
You all believed every word!
You're stupider than I thought.
What will you do with the hostage?!
Tell me you haven't—
He's still alive.
We took the hostage to ensure
you cowards can't back out.
We'll give you three days.
In that time, assemble the best the Hero Association
has and come rescue the little brat.
My lord Orochi and the members
of the Monster Association await you.
It exploded?!
There's still one left. What's keeping the heroes?!
If we're all done talking,
I think I'll get a little freaky!
Was that the emergency?
Oh! Blackluster!
Thank heavens we have you as security for the HQ.
No, it's not over!
That was just a husk!
There's the parasite itself!
Slow-witted fools!
Now this S-class body
is all mine!
Huh?!
My feeler drills are hard as steel!
Why aren't they cutting straight through you?!
This is living tissue, right?!
Can you even hear yourself?
Everyone knows steel
is no match for a hardened body.
This Monster Association is quite audacious!
What now?
It's obvious.
Rescuing the hostage is top-priority!
Can we send in S-class heroes knowing it's a trap?
This is no good.
The monsters' actions have
thrown the executives into a tizzy.
Better step up.
Ahem.
Check me out!
Well?
Wh-What is it, Blackluster?
Did seeing these muscles calm everyone down a bit?
I... guess?
We're full of audacity, same as them!
It seems the time has come at last for me to shine.
Let the enemy be the ones who tremble in fear.
I just hope they're tough
enough for me to go all out!
Think the heroes will come?
We all saw it today. We're way stronger!
Hostages are pointless.
If we go all out, they're good as dead!
Boldness is a virtue,
but rushing in headlong
is a strategy filled with flaws.
There are freakishly strong ones
in the Hero Association, too.
If we allow them to get away,
it'll mean trouble later.
So we must pull them all in,
then crush them with our full force.
The hostage is the bait.
Once we've slain their strongest fighters,
the remainder will be exterminated.
With none left to resist us,
nothing will prevent our victory,
and human civilization will fall.
Then Lord Orochi will reign supreme
and a new world ruled by monsters shall be born!
What's the matter?
I expected applause.
You'd rather not swear fealty to Lord Orochi?
I thought we were here
to destroy the Hero Association.
Who said anything about "fealty"?
One moment.
Why are there weaklings amongst us?
Hey! What're you doing?!
Is that you, Roach Awakening?
You have the gall to return after failure?
Wait a second! All I lost was my legs!
I can still fight!
Next time, I'll...
Aren't we on the same team?
Come on!
No! Stop it!
Stop, please! Please stop!
He ate him...
And what of you, Super S?
I'm still...
mostly unscathed.
I didn't lose!
Well, she does have a useful set of skills.
It might be worth allowing her to live.
Next time you won't be spared.
Damn it all...
Where was I?
Anybody who's got a problem can take it up
with Lord Orochi once the battle is over.
If you manage to defeat him,
you'll even be the new boss.
Sounds good.
By the way, Gyoro-Gyoro.
I don't see Gouketsu.
Oh?
Now that you mention it, he hasn't come back.
I'll check on him right now.
Gouketsu... killed?
Who could have done this?
It seems my plans won't come
to fruition so easily, after all...
Where am I?
Did I lose a fight?
Better get back to the hideout for now...
Is that...?
No doubt about it.
It's Death Gatling, a Class A.
But King roughed me up pretty bad.
My body's at its limit.
Maybe I'll call it a day.
That should do it.
How's it feel, Genos?
Everything seems to be working correctly.
Yes.
Thank you very much, Doctor Kuseno.
Sorry for the rush.
Well, you did want to get back
to the front lines as soon as possible.
I only made minor modifications,
but the upgrades should
certainly make you stronger.
Understood.
I will not lose again.
No need to overdo it.
It's okay to lose at times.
As long as you stay alive, that is.
Seeing you yesterday
reminded me of my younger days.
A time when I burned with a passion for justice
and dove in head first without fear of anything.
Genos...
Don't do anything rash.
Extra! Extra!
Monster Association?!
Is it true they infiltrated the HQ?
It says an executive was killed!
Can't they do anything?!
Today before dawn,
a group called the Monster Association
claimed to have taken a hostage
with ties to the Hero Association.
They have openly declared their hostile intentions.
Will we be okay, Bat?
Tch!
The Hero Association warns that
the contents of that declaration
Seems the two associations are headed for a clash.
So it's war?
indicate a likely further spread
of monster-related disasters.
Damn this Monster Association and its dirty tricks!
What happens to us if the heroes lose?
It hurts to admit, but we'd be powerless.
Damn it!
They can win, right?
The heroes, I mean.
What do you mean,
you're not taking part in the operation?!
Metal Knight, are you sure
you understand the situation?!
If they goad us into storming in,
it will only increase our casualties.
Sacrificing resources recklessly makes no sense.
This is no time for excuses!
They've taken a hostage!
I'm saying that your kind of thinking
will only make matters worse.
Once we locate the enemy lair,
we should abandon any plans to rescue the hostage
and immediately commence bombing.
I proposed as much to the council,
but they rejected the plan.
Seems they are prioritizing their own interests.
And if that's the case,
I want no part of the current plan.
There it is.
He insists on having it his way.
The populace is watching for our next move.
That leak to the press was no small thing.
Now that the public knows about our failures,
we must take a hard-line approach.
The Monster Association?
It didn't say where to find them, but I got an idea.
They're in City Z!
They're planning a revolution.
This message wasn't just meant for the humans.
They're talking to us, too.
Let's join the Monster Association
and wipe those bastard heroes out!
More monsters today, too.
Were these guys looking for me?
But more importantly,
the garbage truck's about to come by!
What?!
Somebody's in our secret base?
Yeah, some dude's in there sleeping.
Seriously?
Tareo, go check it out.
Huh?
Yell at him, then chase him away!
I-I can't do that...
Shut up! Just get going!
That hurt...
This fever's not going down.
I might be out of commission for a few days...
Who's there?!
What're you up to?
Th-Th-This shack is...
o-our secret base, so...
Oh, hey,
you're that kid with the Hero Almanac.
Huh?
It's you, mister!
I told you to stop calling me mister.
Why are you here?
U-Uh...
I want you to leave this shack... please.
Huh?!
You're telling me to leave? Why?
U-Um...
Well, the others told me to tell you that.
Your friends did?
Tell them to buzz off.
But...
Stop crying! It's annoying.
Yeah, all right.
I'll move to another place soon.
If they have a problem with that,
bring your friends in here.
Got that, little brat?
G-Got it.
Want some good advice?
About getting respect from others?
Huh?
Yes. I want to know.
What's keeping Tareo?
Maybe something happened to him.
Stand back, boys.
Whoa! It's Death Gatling!
It's dangerous here.
Smile Man and Stinger, too!
Wow!
A bunch of heroes are here!
The hero hunter is in that shack, wounded, huh?
Yeah.
"Garou the Hero Hunter."
Today it's your turn to get hunted.
Excuse me... Is there something inside?
There's an evil monster inside that shack.
Get clear of here right now.
Y-Yes, sir!
Oh no...
We made Tareo go in by himself.
The heroes are here.
He'll be okay.
Right.
Yeah.
If you want respect and to not get bossed around,
you gotta get strong!
What?
Well?
Pretty good advice, eh?
No, that's just obvious.
Right! It is obvious!
So you do understand!
Laughing makes me hurt.
Are you all right, mister?
Don't worry about me.
You should go on home.
O-Okay.
The door's opening.
Heads up!
At the first sign of him, light the place up!
They're all around us.
Wait!
In exchange for that good advice,
let me see the Hero Almanac.
You got it, yeah?
I have it.
But why?
I need a look.
Okay, sure.
Here.
This hero almanac has comprehensive
info on the heroes, right?
Yup.
But not all of them.
I see.
Out front...
four.
In back,
two.
And one to each side.
Eight in all.
Ordinarily, taking them out'd be a cinch.
But with all these injuries...
Luckily, this almanac has useful information.
Mister! There's someone outside!
Keep quiet.
Tch!
I'm out of time.
Come on out, hero hunter!
We know you're in there!
Brat,
get down on the floor.
All right, I'm coming out!
Don't shoot!
Do me a favor and don't shoot up the shack.
Aren't you sweet. Turning yourself in?
Don't be stupid.
I just need a place to catch up on sleep
after I hunt you bastards down.
After you hunt us down?!
Don't fall for his taunts, Wild Horn.
He's in pretty bad shape.
We'll take him back to the Association alive.
Under questioning, he'll tell us his motives,
and give up any accomplices!
That's a hero for you.
You're very kind not to kill me.
Wow!
Heroes!
And they're really tough ones, too!
You won't get off easy.
You'll have to pay.
We'll make you regret ever
calling yourself a monster.
You got it backwards.
You're the ones who'll pay
for calling yourselves "heroes".
Time to hunt!
And you guys are gonna put me over 100 kills!
It's the end of the line for you!
I'm taking you down first!
He did that airborne?! Amazing.
That was pretty close.
He wasn't trying to take me alive.
Arrow Rain!
How'd he know?
Arrow Rain is one of my lesser-known moves!
Those are poison arrows.
Good thing I read the almanac.
Why are heroes after you, mister?
Despite the odds, he isn't backing down...
Is the Hero Hunter just a damn fool?
Chain Toad, both Tank-top Master
and Metal Bat were badly beaten.
Remember what we discussed about Garou?
"Never underestimate him."
I got it.
I won't go easy on him!
I can believe he was Silverfang's top disciple.
And he's no fool.
His senses are frighteningly sharp.
At medium distance,
Chain Toad and Smileman launch
a ceaseless barrage of attacks...
Got him! Two hits!
But if I back off too far,
I'm in Shooter and Blam-Blam's field of fire.
With Death Gatling on clean up, eh?
So what's that guy been up to all this time?
Shooter!
Thanks!
He's here for support.
That explains why he kept his distance from me.
In that case...
You're gonna be my meatshield!
Stay there!
Damn.
If I leave myself any more exposed,
I'll get shot in the back.
Little shit...
It's my job to chase you down if you run.
In terms of stamina and persistence,
you won't beat me.
You're wounded and poisoned.
You can't hold out long.
But the close-in fighting is their job.
I don't have the legs to break through them.
In the shape I'm in,
I'd be a fool to think I can
avoid all their bullets, arrows,
and other weapons...
This is your final chance to surrender, Garou!