I heard you calling for help, Suiryu.
You fought hard on your own.
Let me take care of the rest.
I know that head...
A hero?
A goddamn hero?!
More like some puny runt
out to make a name for himself!
Pathetic!
You have no idea how outclassed you are, small fry!
You're nothing but...
You're...
Wait, do I know you?
Have we met?
Shut your face!
This time, Bakuzan the Monster
will rain down upon you a buffet of death blows!
Art of the Darkness Hell Killer:
Demon Sweeper Low Kick!
He got you guys, too...
That you're still standing is impressive,
but by now you've realized the
unimaginable difference in our strength.
Bear Killer Mid Kick!
Is he protecting the injured?
P-Protect yourself first!
Carnage Punch!
You've got one last chance
to apologize for our match!
Tch! This guy's no fun.
He must have gone into shock.
Time to end this!
Those scrawny nothings have to go too!
Hellbringin' Hand Chop!
Darn, I just can't remember.
Who was this guy?
Eh, whatever.
That really sucked for you.
Right after you'd won, too.
Well, I defeated the monsters,
so maybe next time won't be so bad.
Okay, yeah...
Thank you for saving me...
Wh-Who are you, really?
I'm Saitama.
A hero.
Saitama?
So you fought in the tournament under an alias?
Uh... oops.
What were you doing here?
Was this all some plan of the Hero Association's?
No.
I wanted to experience martial arts.
And win the prize money.
There's this guy calling himself a "Hero Hunter".
They say he's a martial arts master,
so I sort of got interested.
I see.
You were looking for ways to counter him?
Well, I wouldn't exactly say that.
I just happened across an entry ticket.
More specifically...
I was bored.
You were bored?
Thanks to you, though, I'm still alive.
Sorry I didn't get here sooner.
Saitama!
You shouldn't go out there.
Some dangerous group called the
"Monster Association" is on a rampage outside.
You serious?
Yeah.
Seems they're able to turn humans into monsters.
That guy you just beat, Bakuzan, was one of them.
Remember, from your second match?
So that's who he was?
I mean, I can't remember every opponent I punch.
Anyway, it's dangerous right now,
so we should lay low.
Gouketsu is still somewhere nearby.
Gouketsu?
Yeah.
He's another monster I'd avoid.
Nothing I could do had any effect on him.
That kind of strength should be illegal.
When my repairs are done I must return at once.
Even if he caught me off-guard,
a monster that can beat me with one punch
must not be allowed to survive.
I need to gather the Class S
heroes and Master Saitama,
then strike together!
So he's that strong?
Even with the most meticulous preparation,
who knows if he can be beat?
I see.
So, where'd this monster go?
What?
That way, but...
Oh...
So all that noise earlier was him, huh?
I'll check it out.
What?
No!
Weren't you listening? I'm trying to warn you!
I heard you. And?
You still don't get it!
He was once a preeminent martial artist.
He's no ordinary fighter! You'll be killed for sure!
Whoa, a master of martial arts, eh?
Perfect.
Might make a decent fight.
H-Hey...
You're injured.
Take it easy.
I'm not letting go.
I won't let you throw your life
away when I owe you mine!
I couldn't stop him!
I finally saw what a hero, a true hero, can be!
He shouldn't die now.
He's destined to save many, many more people.
Oh, by the way,
there's something I forgot to mention.
That thing about me lying
to get into the tournament...
Could we keep it a secret?
Was Gouketsu tough?
Hmm...
When they only take one punch,
it's kinda hard to compare.
I want to ask you something.
Yeah?
I don't know if I can overcome my fear,
but I'd like to try.
Do you think I could become... a hero?
No idea.
Huh?
But, you know...
If I became one, maybe anyone can?
It's natural to be afraid at the start.
Before I got excessively strong, I was afraid too.
A hero who's excessively strong?
Doesn't sound too bad.
Can I ask you another question, Saitama?
Sure.
Could I be your disciple?
Absolutely not.
Damn it...
His whole body's covered in spikes.
How do I fight him?
Prisoner! Don't use your hands!
Use your ball and chain!
Yeah, nail him with your chain!
Thank you for the enthusiastic
support, young people!
Later I'll shower you with kisses of gratitude,
but for now evacuate the rooftop!
It's no good, he can't hear us.
Does he have to fight completely naked?
You fresh-faced boys cheering me on
without regard for your own safety...
Your love will not go unrewarded!
Ah! Love!
That's it... That's the answer.
I can accept the pain with love so deep...
...there will be nothing left to fear!
Angel Hug...!
He keeps staring at us... with blood all over him.
Hello? Puri-Puri Prisoner speaking.
What?
It broke into my comfy cozy
home and stole my honeys?!
Where is this monster now?
They're gone?
Yeah...
They all left together... maybe 30 minutes ago.
They came all at once,
went wild, then left all at once?
What were they up to?
Damn it.
How'd I miss such a huge disaster?
The other heroes were out here fighting.
What was I thinking?
I can't call myself a hero if I don't defeat monsters.
Wait a sec...
I don't fight monsters because
I want to be called a hero.
I might have forgotten something important.
Like the reason why I became a hero...
I started out just having fun.
But since joining the Hero Association,
I've been so bored.
That "hero hunter" guy got me curious again.
That's why I entered the martial arts tournament.
But...
Against Suiryu and the others,
even a monster who was a master martial artist
I didn't really feel anything.
And I didn't get anything out of it.
Saitama?
King?
You sure it's safe to be out here?
Well,
I heard the alarms, but it's all quiet now.
Why're you looking so down?
You know... Got a lot on my mind.
I get it.
But you're still young, so you can't give up.
King...
Besides, it might grow back.
And there's treatments—
Wait, hold on!
That's not what I'm talking about!
It's more of a big picture thing.
Being down isn't like you.
You're always so strong.
Well, I'm not going to be getting any stronger.
What?
I've become too strong.
No matter who I fight, I don't feel anything.
I gain nothing from it.
There's nothing I can learn from anyone.
But isn't having that much strength really awesome?
King...
Not having any room to grow
means that I can't enjoy the process of growing.
No matter how many monsters I defeat,
on the inside, I'm bored out of my mind.
I never thought being a hero could be so lonesome.
You feel lonely, Saitama?
Guess so.
There's a ballroom dance school
near the station you could check out.
Why would I do that?
If you're lonely, you could make friends.
No, that's not quite what I mean.
Then what?
It's hard to explain...
I'm not interested,
and I don't have much time these days.
Once things settle down,
what about a trip to change things up?
A trip?
Hmm...
There's no place I particularly want to go...
Good grief...
You're bored and want some excitement,
but you won't take on any challenges.
There was a time I felt that way too.
Listen to me, Saitama.
Life is a journey to nowhere.
If you want a change of scenery,
you need to find your own way there.
You sure you've been on a trip before?
Saitama, seems to me you're mistaking
getting strong for reaching your destination.
I doubt the path of becoming a hero ends so easily.
Is this a lecture?
It's not like you're some veteran hero.
It's inherently wrong to seek
satisfaction from fighting.
Battling with great courage and benefiting society.
Isn't that what gives a hero's existence meaning?
King's talking sense?!
In that respect, you've got a long road to walk
before you can truly become the ultimate hero.
That's true!
In other words, the pursuit of the ideal remains.
You must still have a great
deal of unrealized potential.
And in that case,
to say that you've reached the limit of your growth
starts to sound shallow and arrogant, doesn't it?
King...
What does it take to be the "ultimate hero"?
An unflinching sense of justice? Prowess in combat?
The courage to face any hardship?
Until you've found the answer to that question,
how can you say you have time to feel bored?
Those are my thoughts, anyway.
Plus I read it in a manga.
That just blew my mind.
The "ultimate hero"?
Should I be thinking about what that truly means?
I think it'd make me even more bored.
If you're that bored, wanna come play games?
No, that's totally not what I'm feeling right now.
I'm numb and nothing'll change it.
Don't be like that. Let's do it.
Always winning gets boring, right?
So I'll let you lose.
You can't trick me.
Anyway, I wouldn't get upset
just because I lost some game.
It takes more than that to work me up.
Yeah? Okay.
Tell you what. As a handicap,
I'll play with just one finger from each hand.
Okay, jerkoff!
I'm so gonna crush your ass this time!
I never thought it'd be him that beat me.
His speed and power were
far beyond my expectations.
I was lucky to even get away.
Martial arts designed for human opponents were
a poor match against his four-legged fighting style.
That was a good lesson.
This is the freaking best!
I can become so much stronger!
Huh?
That's...
Yeah, that's him.
I won't get a second chance.
My body can handle it, and the pain is gone.
In fact, I'm so stoked I feel full up with power!
King, it's your turn to be hunted!
What will his move be when he reacts?
I've got it!
Get ready to die!
What?
He was trying to attack you. You know him?
Nope, no idea.
As if monsters weren't enough.
Now we're fighting hoodlums too?
Where's it end?
By the way, have you heard what's going on?
I haven't.
I don't know the details myself,
but monsters are rampaging all over,
and there's a guy hunting heroes
and calling himself a monster.
It's been pretty busy.
That so?
The hero hunter dude has me a bit curious.
Yeah?
There's never been a human
who calls himself a monster before.
It reminds me of when I was calling
myself a "hero" and doing my own thing.
So I'm hoping he lives up to his claim.
He might even be stronger than me, you know?
I see.
Hope you run into him soon.
Show yourself.
Who are—
There's two of them!
You attacked me,
so I assume you're ready to die!
"Attacked"?
Sounds unfriendly.
I'm sure you agree,
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic,
last surviving member of the Final 44?
You're from the village?
We are of the Golden 37.
I am Tempest Wind.
Hellfire Flame.
What do you want with me?
To recruit you.
Interested in doing something big?
Something big?
Indeed.
We're planning on taking over this little planet
as monsters who transcend humankind.
There's an organization comprised only
of monsters called the Monster Association.
We're members.
And we're about to flip this world on its head.
Sounds like a bunch of horseshit.
Besides, where do I fit in?
We want to be certain
we can take down Flashy Flash.
Help us.
Ridiculous.
I have no obligation to you,
nor the time to play games.
Get lost, unless you'd prefer to die.
Let's give him a taste.
Remember how we said "Monster Association"?
We, too...
...are monsters!
You'll be a monster, that's all.
It's far better than any
enhancement drug or implant.
The thought of getting stronger tempts you?
This is a monster cell.
All you have to do is ingest it.
Here, you can have this one.
See you at the Monster Association.
No matter how much I train,
I see no path to beating him.
But I'd pay any price for victory over Saitama.
Now that price...
...is giving up my humanity.
Ever since I lost to him,
I've felt as if I was already dead.
And I have no attachments to my human life.
Saitama...
I've decided to be a monster.
Monsters remain in some areas.
We can't lift the evacuation order just yet.
It's been a hell of a day...
The most formidable is Martial Gorilla.
He seems obsessed with his own threat level
and declares he'll keep fighting
until he's at "Demon".
City W, huh?
Have the heroes nearby surround the city.
Not necessary.
Sending in a bunch of fresh meat
will only waste resources.
Zombieman?!
Let me take care of it.
R-Roger!
Time to get to work.
Hey! I'm not seeing any heroes!
If I read this right...
These attacks were masterminded
by something organized...
He's not paying attention.
Perhaps I could track him back to his lair...
Hmm?
There's a sturdy fellow...
Drat...
He's attacking a civilian.
You a pro hero, big guy?
Sorry?
You're a gorilla!
You're a gorilla, too.
Wh-What are you? Some freelance monster?
What's a freelance monster?
I'm just out buying groceries.
You're shopping?!
Like a monster pretending to live a human life?!
You're a disgrace to gorilla monsters!
I'm not sure how to respond to that...
If you're a potential enemy,
you die where you stand partially upright!
Take your issues elsewhere.
Changing target. I'm following him instead...
In the end,
we spent the whole day getting rid of monsters.
Though of course, that's your day job.
Say, Bang...
Think maybe one of the heroes or
monsters got to Garou in all the chaos?
I don't think so, Brother.
I didn't train him to be weak.
That's why it's my responsibility to defeat him.
Garou...
Do you realize what it means to become a monster?
If you're going down into darkness,
at least let it be at my hands.
The sun will be setting soon...
We've received a vital report from Drive Knight
regarding the enemy in today's events.
They call themselves the "Monster Association".
While their objectives are unclear,
they tout themselves as our rivals
and have a method for turning
humans into monsters.
Their leader is the "Monster King" Orochi.
We also received the
approximate location of their lair.
It's in the abandoned district of City Z.
The area that was taken by the monsters...
They went through a lot of trouble
to kidnap an executive's son...
Perhaps it's a sign they want to negotiate.
I agree.
It's their way of saying "don't try anything".
They're probably thinking they can
talk their way out of extermination.
If the ghost town monsters have formed
some sort of coalition, that makes sense...
In that case, this riot by the monsters
could have been their way of staging a protest.
These monsters possess
the intellect to act as a group.
It's extremely likely that they will reach out to us.
That could be our "in".
Let's think of some sort of ruse, then wipe them out.
We should hear what they have to say first.
Our primary objective remains
the rescue of the hostage.
Correct.
Esteemed advisor Richman is one our top donors.
If anything happens to his son, he could cut us off.
We must rescue the boy.
We received a message
from the Monster Association!
What sort of—
We received a message
from the Monster Association!
Hey!
Something's wrong with him.
We received a message...
from the Monster Association...
We received a message
from the Monster Association.
I'm sure it was a good call to cook this thing.
Common sense says not to eat meat like this raw.
I'll try not to think about it.
You just watch your back...
...Saitama!