You've lost contact with Metal Bat?
Yes.
I've already called for backup
from Class A heroes and above.
Elder Centipede, the gigantic bug-monster.
Threat Level: Dragon.
Practically a natural disaster.
This far exceeds what happened two years ago.
Numbers alone may not be enough to defeat it.
King is occupied fighting something else,
but what of the other Class S heroes?
Multiple emergency calls from all over.
Wh-What's happening?
D-Damn...
It's got us cornered!
If we don't do something, he's got us!
Wait!
That's Metal Knight, the Class S!
We're gonna be okay!
You're in the way.
A weapons test is not some spectacle.
Move off now!
S-Sorry, sir!
Not a scratch...
For a biologic, its armor is remarkably resistant.
Irksome insect!
Is that thing still after us?
I think we managed to lose it.
I wonder if Metal Bat's all right.
You thought you'd gotten away, heroes?
Leave those two with us.
Monsters?!
Let's see.
The report said Metal Bat
was taking on Elder Centipede.
Where is he and what's he doing?
This is unprecedented.
Monsters of Threat Level Demon and above
are appearing simultaneously in every city!
Our response teams are being overwhelmed.
Guess you were worn down already.
I'd hoped to have a true test of skill,
but this'll be over quick.
Shut it!
You've lost so much blood,
you're barely able to stay conscious.
Plus a bunch of your bones are broken.
What keeps you standing? Hero's pride?
His swings are coming faster?
More powerful, too.
That shouldn't be possible,
but there's no doubt about it.
With every hit he takes,
every time he gets hurt,
he becomes physically stronger.
Are you supposed to make sense?
Screw makin' sense.
It's about fighting spirit!
What the hell?
Let's get it on, "hero hunter".
I still got a giant centipede to take care of!
Is this guy for real?
And how long's that "fighting spirit" gonna last?
I'll play your game.
Eat this!
Over here!
Idiot!
I got a rule never to let
muggers or hero hunters slide!
I'll pound that rotten spirit of yours into shape!
Missed me, stupid!
You plan on swinging that
thing around 'til you're dead?
Until I'm dead?
Hell no.
Only 'til I win!
Killer Move!
Fighting Spirit Brutal Tornado!
You're just spinning around.
Don't make me laugh.
Too bad for you,
but parrying amateur attacks like yours is kid stuff.
Hmph.
Finally down, eh?
Both Tank-Top Master and
Metal Bat were nothing but brutes.
Against a human martial artist,
they have no answer.
Taking the Hero Association down
might be easier than I thought.
Wait, what's this?
Could that goon really have so much power?
If he'd caught me square, I'd have been in trouble.
Big Bro!
Bat.
Tch.
What's going on? Who is that man?
Your kid sister?
Zenko! Stay ba—
Big bro!
You let your best chance slip by.
Now it's time to put you out of your misery!
No!
My brother promised no violence when I'm around.
So no fighting allowed!
Huh?
The fight's over!
Why do I have to follow your family's rule?
It's over!
Oh right, I did have something else I was doing.
No time to waste on a jackass.
You started this fight, bastard.
You get to live for now, Metal Bat.
What?!
Big Bro, never mind him. Let's go home!
There's a monster here.
Oh yeah!
That man and his son are in danger. I gotta go.
You're kidding, right?!
Hold it! You can't go!
You'll get killed!
Go on home, Zenko.
You're such a hard-head!
Oh.
Big bro? Hello?
Hmm...
So that's the hero hunter from the rumors?
He's pretty good for a human.
Bah, he didn't even finish the hero off.
No, that man could be put to good use,
my dear Sludge Jellyfish.
Metal Bat's younger sister...
Never can have enough hostages!
Hey.
So that's why I've been feeling a creepy gaze.
You survived that?!
Hold, hero hunter!
Two against one, eh?
We are not your enemies.
Take a look at this. I'm sure you'll be interested.
"Monster Association"?
I thought he'd bite!
Why not come with us?
We shall escort you to our hideout.
Not interested. Screw off.
I'll pretend I didn't see that.
But one day soon, we shall meet again.
Assuming you manage to
keep up your hunting, that is.
You'd better watch your back!
Creeps.
Talk about disappointment...
My Mohi-Punch had no effect?
My Pine Cannon, neither...
Pineapple, I give you five points. Mohican, two.
That's on a 100-point scale.
You're both so weak, I can't even think of a joke!
Do you have any frickin' idea
how hard I've trained this horn and body
for the day of the final battle?
Any idea at all?!
Rhino-wrestler!
Bring the hostages!
We're pulling out!
What? Aren't we taking the fight to Metal Knight?
No.
That thing's nothing but a remote-controlled drone.
Besides, today is not the final battle.
You're not to go off on your own.
Very well.
Do I take both of these creatures?
No, just the child will do.
S-Stop this!
Damn it! We can't let Metal Bat down!
You'll have to kill us first!
Then die!
Did you see that, Phoenix Man?
What threat level are they gonna give me?
Who cares?
Elder Centipede! Our mission is accomplished!
Time to withdraw!
Gah!
Escaping underground?
You won't get away!
I'm not letting go!
We've done enough.
The final battle is yet to come.
Kill it!
Keep it up, Heavy Kong!
Damn, still no backup...
Where the devil are they?
You a Class A hero?
How many Class A scalps will it take
to raise my threat level?
My stun rods aren't working.
I'm a poor matchup.
My luck's bad today.
Class A hero, Lightning Genji.
That's not at all so. Your luck is good!
You see, other cities are facing
far more violent monsters.
What in heaven's name is happening?!
Hey!
You're the only one still sitting on his ass!
It's go time, doofus!
Hurry it up! Charanko!
All right.
Guess I'll go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have kept you waiting long enough!
The competitors for Super Fight 22
are now entering the arena!
First up, a first-time contestant!
The Class A, rank 19 hero
known as "Lightning Max",
of the fighting style "Hyper Karate Max"!
Got my eyes on the prize.
Our sole female fighter, with lightning-fast attacks:
Ring-Ring, with her "Palm Bells Fist"!
Let's start already.
Next, Benpats of "The Way of the Cruel" School.
Plus the perennial semifinalist,
whose slithery arms can strike opponents anywhere,
Class A's lowest-ranked hero,
Snakebite Snek!
Did he have to say "lowest-ranked"?
And that's not all!
With his super-conductor body,
Boltane, of the "Fist of Thunder"!
Bazuzu, master of "Bazuzu's Nuclear Fist"!
Gatling, of the "Many Fists" style!
From the Sunflower Dojo,
Hamukichi and his "Gentle Self Defense"!
Dave, with his
"Giant Smothering Killing Technique"!
Logy, master of Psycho-analytic Martial Arts!
Mentai, of the "Spice Fist" school!
Jakumen, the "Giga-Pro Wrestler"!
Choze, of the "Chosen People's Style"!
Formerly of the
"Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock",
Sourface, master of Sourface Kempo!
I'm so tense, I might barf...
On his seventh straight appearance,
will the man who won't quit win his first fight?
Zakkos, of the "Take-the-Plunge True Fist"!
I'll get my first win and propose to my girl.
Moving on,
the man who wrote
"Please don't aim for my head" on his registration.
Is he really here to fight?
Charanko, with his
"Fist of Seltzer Water on the Rocks."
Why are they already booing?
Isn't that Genos from Class S?
He's a fight fan?
Some say he's the greatest contender ever,
a two-time champion!
Every one of his fights has been lopsided.
But the man himself says he's never gotten serious!
Bakuzan, master of the "Dark Hell Killing Jutsu"!
Winning the championship
today will have true meaning.
And now a man who boasts unparalleled strength.
Appearing after skipping
the past seven tournaments!
A four-time champion and a legend in his own time,
Suiryu, master of "Dark Corporeal Fist"!
All right!
He's been gallivanting about the past three years
and says the prize money is his only objective!
Could his power derive from not clinging to glory?
But this time,
Bakuzan is also in the competition!
So that's Suiryu...
If I kill him, I'll truly be the strongest active fighter.
I sense his piercing aura...
But the one I wanted to face
is the last tournament's champion.
If I'm gonna fight, at least it could
have been against someone tough.
These are your 18 contestants.
Let Super Fight 22 begin!
Deep breaths, deep breaths...
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Hey old dude, nervous?
Don't call me "old dude"!
I may outrank you at the dojo,
but I'm 20, same as you!
He's younger than me?
Hey, you!
You claim a style no one's heard of.
I smell an amateur.
Martial arts isn't for fools.
Withdraw now.
Else I'll crush you without mercy.
No response?
It's you he's talking to!
You can't even tie your belt right.
Haven't you learned anything?
You're hopeless.
Super Fight is the pinnacle of mixed martial arts.
It's not some playground for amateurs.
He's a student of Fist of
Flowing Water Crushing Rock.
Him?!
I see.
How the standards have fallen.
What's that?!
Bang was slated to be chief judge today,
but he canceled last minute,
causing all kinds of trouble.
Master Bang did?!
The "treasure of the martial arts world"
ditched his dojo and disciples
so he could run off and play "hero".
I won't stand for this!
And why aren't you angry?!
Huh?
I quit, but you stayed on as his last student!
Oh, I see...
Well, it's okay.
Let him have his say.
What?!
I didn't come to argue.
He says he's gonna crush me.
Sounds like fun.
He seems kinda weak, though.
Heh, that's telling him, Charanko!
I'm gonna butcher you like a butcher!
I don't mind being on Garou's trail,
but is he really just gonna show up?
Tch! He's certainly in a mood...
Hmm?
Something's after the Class A
we've been shadowing.
What?! Let's move!
Ahaha!
The Demonic Pugilist is here to raze this city!
It's not Garou after all.
You sit this one out, Bomb.
Silverfang?
Great timing.
We can work together to... huh?
You're a Class S hero, aren't you?
I know you. You're that renowned martial artist.
When I was human, I was a martial artist myself.
But sanctioned bouts weren't enough!
That's right—my uncontrollable urge to rampage
turned me into a monster!
Wh-Whoa...
We must find him. Before he ends up like this.
All right! It's time for our first match!
Max vs. Ring-Ring!
Begin!
Ring-Ring takes the offensive!
Heart Hard Hit!
A whip can generate that much power?!
You're a hundred years too young
to come at a super sadist head-on!
You pathetic, worthless hero pigs!
H-Heavy Kong...
This the best Class A can offer?
They sure don't have much fight...
Anyway,
you all spread the word.
The one who took down Heavy Kong
was me, the great Marshall Gorilla.
This is going nowhere!
You won't escape.
I...
I just couldn't win...!
Interesting.
With the right matchup,
even Threat Level Tigers like us
can defeat Class A heroes.
Perhaps there was no need for us to hide away.
We have word that Heavy Kong
was defeated in City W.
We haven't been able to reach
Metal Bat or Metal Knight on comms.
The giant creature in City I is growing
in size as it devours buildings.
It's also ossifying!
We cannot let it continue!
Toxins!
The monster in City Y is using
a neurotoxin to paralyze the heroes!
It's no use.
There's too many of them.
If this goes on, we'll be wiped out!
Both our side and the humans
appear to have misjudged our relative abilities.
We were stronger than we thought,
and the humans were weaker than they thought.
Stop... snap out of it!
Wh-What's wrong with you, Darkness Blade?!
When I punish someone with my whip,
it imparts a special stimulus
that turns them into love slaves.
S-Stop this...!
If you desire my love,
you will fight to the death!
A-Are you guys...?
My, my...
More suitors come to vie for my affection.
How titillating!
Hmm.
That's all it takes to be Threat Level Demon?
Might be worth my time.
If I defeat you, their minds might
be freed from your control.
Then they'll be in my debt.
Two birds with one stone.
I knew it! The Blizzard Group!
You can't escape us.
Oh, I wish you wouldn't toy
with my sadistic instincts.
I might get worked up and kill you too quickly.
Quite the easy KO for Max against Ring-Ring!
Talk was that his fighting prowess was suspect.
Yet despite his low seed,
he advances uninjured and
with ease past his lady opponent!
I wouldn't say uninjured...
He managed to win without
using the gunpowder in his shoes.
What's a "low seed"?
Those who are considered less capable
start in less-favorable positions
in the tournament bracket.
I see...
So he was considered weaker than others.
Those who leave martial arts to become heroes
are often viewed as having taken the easy way out.
What about Bang?
Master Bang is unique.
And don't forget you're
a low seed yourself, Charanko!
What?
Oh, you're right.
So the two in the corners aren't the strongest...
They just think I'm weak.
No, those two are definitely very strong.
After I fight you, I'll face Bakuzan,
a championship contender.
Uh...
According to these brackets...
Oh!
You're a pushover too.
Our second bout,
Zakkos vs. Charanko, is about to begin!
You're so dead!
H-Holy crap! Charanko can hit!
Could Zakkos be concussed with a single slap?
Or is this less about Charanko being strong, as...
He's weak!
Zakkos is some weak sauce!
He even invited his girlfriend,
intending to propose today,
but now all his life plans have gone terribly awry!
Oops.
I did a bad thing.
I have new information.
Wait, it seems his girlfriend didn't show up!
Safe! He's safe!
That's good.
Nothing good about it.
The expected outcome.
At this rate, the tournament will end
with Master never tasting true martial arts.
Zakkos's moves weren't that bad...
Guess I know who I'll be facing in the finals.