Congratulations on winning
the championship, Suiryu!
There was a slight mishap in the final,
but in the end, you won unscathed!
Unscathed?
If he hadn't stopped short, I'd have been...
And now, an announcement for stadium attendees.
We have been informed that
monsters have appeared outside.
Please remain within the arena
until the warning is lifted.
Monsters?
Again?
We'll be okay if we stay in here, right?
Yeah, probably...
No use dwelling on it.
I just need to avoid him from here on out.
You're cute!
Huh?
Best to let it go.
What are those?!
Look up there!
M-Monsters!
Look! They're carrying Logy, Dave, and Bazuzu!
The competitors that were taken to the hospital!
I-I'm frickin' out of here!
You guys take care of those things!
Enjoy!
H-Hey!
Have we got all the tournament fighters?
Hmph. Nothing but scrubs here.
How the martial arts have fallen.
Whatever.
All of you
will become monsters!
Even you, the refuse of the martial arts world,
could be made useful if you became monsters.
Become monsters, you say?
You'll have to go through us heroes first!
The heroes will stop you!
Take him down!
Run for it!
We're screwed!
Did I kill them?
A single kick...?
I have not come here to take your lives today!
I am Gouketsu, from the Monster Association.
Gouketsu?!
The champion of the first Super Fight?!
That you know who I am simplifies things.
You understand how futile resistance would be.
But Gouketsu was killed years ago by a monster!
How could you be him?
It's true that I was once beaten by a monster
and taken to the monsters' lair.
But there, in exchange for my cooperation,
they offered everything I could want
in order to satisfy my ambitions!
Becoming a monster allowed me
to break through those limits
I could never overcome as a human.
You understand what that means?
The Gouketsu I once was is beneath
comparison to the fighter I am now!
Now celebrate,
for I have brought the same gift for you.
You will eat these monster cells.
Do so, and you'll become monsters yourselves.
Refuse and you will be killed.
Monster Association...
What are your intentions?
Are you simply bent on destruction and slaughter?
There can be no question that violence
is the most basic desire of all monsters.
But violence is not our sole objective.
Our plan advances towards another phase.
Ah, but for now, just watch.
Observe the inherent frailty
of the human biology and spirit.
Time to choose!
Die, or become monsters.
No! Don't do it!
This is incredible!
The power... the violence flooding me!
Hey, fat boy!
I'll teach you to sit on me like that!
He wasn't near that strong before...
If that's what they do to peasants,
what will one do to me?
My genetics reign supreme across
the entirety of human history.
Ultimate strength awaits within me to be awoken.
Choze, you're not...?!
Hmm...
It has served not only to improve physical function,
but all my vast mental capacity
is at last unfettered as well.
So this is to be a monster...
Let's see.
Jakumen!
I could kill that peon with ease now.
He humiliated me,
and he shall rue that unto death!
This one turned out fairly well.
It's hit or miss, depending on the raw material.
Now then!
You insects eat up too!
I don't want to die!
Benpats!
It's to survive.
Hamukichi!
I want to be strong.
Not you, too, Boltane!
It's like I could do anything!
I feel so energized!
They've all turned into monsters!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What do we do?!
Hey there.
If I chase them off, would you go on a date with me?
Yeah!
Okay, that's a deal!
I'll work off the stress from that final match!
Oh ho?
One of you still dares to defy me?
Enough talk, then.
We make it a rule to eliminate any potential
enemy of the Monster Association.
Destroy him!
Dumbass playboy!
Now you find some silly sense of justice?
Not at all.
All I live for is enjoyment.
And guys like you
just get in my way.
Heh. You're not bad.
Not bad?
Your vacuous mentality is an affront.
Wh-What's that?
I have decided.
I shall repopulate this world only with
those who meet my exacting standards.
You worms do not.
You shall be eliminated.
Is that all you've got?!
Impossible!
That didn't meet my exacting standards.
Try making it a little more fun.
Insufferable fool...
They're moving too fast to see!
Dark Body Quake Tiger Fist!
Dark Body Phoenix Rising Fist!
Nice work!
Ouch...
Can't remember the last time I got cut.
That was amazing, though.
That monsterfication thing made them really tough.
Killing you would be a bit of a waste.
There's still time to change sides.
From here on, the world will belong to monsters.
In it, the strong will be able to go wild,
killing as they please, enjoying true freedom.
A world of bloodlust and violence.
As a monster, you'd find your "life of fun".
Not a bad deal, eh?
He wouldn't...!
You make a point.
You're saying regardless of what world I live in,
if life is fun, it's all good. That it?
Nah, I refuse.
I'd rather die than look as fugly as you!
Dark Body Flying Dragon Fist!
Yes!
Then die.
Watchdog Man!
Way to go!
Thank you!
You're City Q's guardian angel!
I see why they consider him a Class S.
Monsters attacked just as I was about to pick a fight.
His speed and powerful
fighting ability were surprising,
but that's all.
I can handle that in any number of ways.
Watchdog Man, it's your turn to be hunted!
Are you human?
Or monster?
Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock!
I didn't say "shake"!
Th-This guy is definitely
nothing but speed and power.
But the freak's got way more of both than I thought.
What's the matter?
Done already?
Get up. I'll give you three seconds.
Three...
Two...
One.
That's it! Good!
Fight like your life depends on it!
Damn!
He's not even flinching. What can I do?
You all can have your fun, too.
Huh?
This is bad...
Now, now.
Don't get distracted!
Is it broken?
Come. What's the matter?
Get up. I'll give you three seconds.
Three...
Two...
One.
Dark Body Quake Tiger Fist!
I-I put everything into that strike...!
He's strong...
Stronger than me...
in all respects.
S-So this...
...is a monster?!
Eat up, boys!
That meat is a real delicacy.
Pick him clean!
Once, they were my disciples.
But they were weak-willed
and lost their sense of self after becoming monsters!
Crap!
If I don't do something, I'm bird food!
Hey, you!
We're in trouble here! Help me out!
Suiryu...
Watching the finals, it was clear.
You're stronger than me.
There's no way that I can beat you.
I accept that.
But right now, you're about to be killed.
Ironic, isn't it?
You made it to the top of the human world,
yet against these monsters, you're no match.
Th-Then let's team up!
My mind's made up.
I'm going to become a monster.
Resign yourself to dying here!
I don't need to be the strongest human anymore!
My goal now is simply to become
the strongest creature alive!
Aw! He ate them all!
Greedy bastard.
Keep barking!
In a second I'm gonna shut that big mouth you got!
Looks like your body can't keep up.
The monsterfication failed.
That just leaves you.
There are patients back there
in the ICU that can't be moved.
At a time like this, a hero doesn't back down!
In the end, heroes are only human.
Your kind exist only to be dominated by monsters.
All the others either ran
or have been defeated.
Aren't you lucky?
Your cries of pain won't embarrass you now.
Now, let's hear him scream.
Coiling Defense!
Lightning Kick!
Snek, Max...
You're both okay?
Why?
Why'd you come back?
To save you.
In our hero outfits, we're different fighters.
These clothes protect me against
monster claws, fangs, even beaks.
This is my Battle Suit!
And I put on my Lightning Shoes.
Now's when we show what we can really do!
We're up against three of them.
Can we leave one to you?
Yeah!
You did save me.
Thanks.
Tank-Top Tackle!
That was... a great tackle.
You risk too much for a guy without a tank-top.
Can you stand, Unlicensed Rider?
Yeah.
You bet I can.
Okay, I can still move my legs.
Time to go!
Why are you two getting ready to fight?!
We'll hold him off.
It'll give you time to escape.
That's stupid!
You don't stand a chance!
Neither of you could even outfight me!
They can't be serious...
Don't they feel fear?
I won't get another chance.
Run, go, escape!
I have to get—
Where you going?
This party's just getting started.
I hit the jackpot with this one.
You look the same as me:
a Threat Level Dragon!
Damn right!
Oh? He's getting up again?
First, objective number one.
Become known and feared amongst
the humans via rampage and chaos.
At this, we have been extremely successful.
No refuge nor safe harbor remains.
All has been enveloped in
a cloak of uncertainty and fear.
Objective number two.
Secure a hostage from the Hero Association.
This also was successful.
The son of an important executive is in our hands.
And objective number three.
Turn significant humans into monsters.
This, too, is proceeding well.
Nyaan infiltrated a prison,
monsterfied those inmates who were inherently evil,
and now leads them here.
Gouketsu has also turned
several martial artists into monsters.
I anticipate they will make
valuable additions to our ranks.
Hmm?
Gouketsu is still not finished?
Attention, Gouketsu!
Come back immediately.
If multiple Class S heroes arrive,
even you may not be able to handle them.
Bah! You underestimate me.
But I'm done here.
Hey, new guy.
Huh?
I'm taking you to our lair. Follow me!
You don't give Bakuzan orders!
Hear me out.
Several in the Monster Association
are stronger than you, including me.
Don't get carried away.
The monsters will be returning to the lair now.
That means that the heroes, including Class S,
will be coming for any remaining monsters.
They'll be too much for you to handle alone.
You've been warned.
I'm going.
The lair's in the wasteland outside City Z.
Find us there.
Hear that, Suiryu?
Monsters everywhere.
Unbelievable, eh?
I felt his power and now I'm scared.
Yeah,
I'm done. No more trying to be the strongest.
Y-You know what, Bakuzan?
I have no will to fight anymore.
C'mon...
Just let me live.
Look, Suiryu.
You should know I'm the type...
S-Stop!
...who loves beating on anyone weaker than me!
That's the only reason I ever
wanted to become strong!
Now that I've thrown off my limits,
I've never felt better!
How about the other one?!
Suiryu, screaming in pain.
Too bad there's no audience to hear it!
You had youth, ability, popularity,
money, women, and freedom...
Think you took too much for granted?
Now you'll experience a hell that
wipes all that away, and then death.
You look absolutely pathetic, "champ".
Somebody!
Help me!
A monster!
There's a monster here!
Is anyone out there?
A monster's attacking me!
Please!
I need...
a hero!
Can any heroes hear me?!
I'm over here!
Heroes!
Please! Help me!
There's a monster here...
Heroes...
No one can hear you.
No hero's coming.
You're going to die.
There's no one who can match him...
Even the strongest hero couldn't save me.
But I'm begging you...
Get up... please!
When a person is thrust into the deepest darkness,
they seek a ray of light.
It doesn't matter how small or faint it may be.
Just the fact that it's there
gives hope.
This is what it is to be without hope!
What?
Who are you?
Just your everyday hero.
I heard you calling for help, Suiryu.
You fought hard on your own.
Let me take care of the rest.