One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero