You are one of the Seafolk, correct?
What if I am?
You must be another soldier—
I am here to eliminate you.
Was that...
the last of them?
Wow!
Awesome!
Amazing!
They must have been desperate.
Now I'm angry.
I'm gonna tear you to shreds.
I let my guard down again.
I never learn.
Saitama...
You're Class C, rank 2.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Hurry it up. It's raining.
He burst through every record during the fitness exam...
And he worked with some Class S heroes to destroy that meteor.
But because he came out of nowhere, people are saying he's a fraud.
If he were any other class C hero, I'd stop him...
This may be our chance to see how strong he truly is.
I'll send you the location, Saitama-kun. Head there immediately!
Those who can walk, leave the shelter now!
I cannot promise I will win.
Run, while I keep him busy!
None of you monkeys will escape me!
Lightning Eye!
My eyes—
Machinegun Blows!
You do like combo attacks, don't you?
You can do it!
Quiet!
Go ahead and melt.
If you'd focused on me,
you could have easily dodged my little ball of acid.
Instead, you chose to sacrifice
yourself to save some brat.
You're a fool, but I give you credit for giving me a few scratches.
They've already healed, of course.
Now, die.
Justice Crash!
The Cyclist of Justice, Mumen Rider, is here!
The top hero in Class C?
D-Don't...
It's Mumen Rider!
Mumen Rider came for us.
But he...
I'm bored already.
Oh, my apologies. I nearly forgot to kill you.
Justice Tackle...!
No one expects much—
...from me.
They think a Class C hero won't be much help.
I know that better than anyone!
I'm not good enough for Class B.
I'm weak. I know that much.
No one has to tell me I have no chance of beating you.
No one understands that... better than I do!
What are you babbling about?
Begging for your life?
And yet, I must try.
It's not about winning or losing!
It's about me taking you on right here, right now!
Enough of your rambling. Time to finish you off.
You can do it!
Mumen Rider, you can do it!
You're the Cyclist of Justice!
Beat that weird monster, beat him!
You can do it!
Yeah, get him!
Beat him up!
We're counting on you, Mumen Rider!
You can do it!
Beat him!
Good luck!
I think not!
You did fine. Nice fight.
So yet another piece of garbage
has washed up on my shore?
H-Hey, Genos!
Are you still alive?!
Sen... sei...
Hang on for a second.
I've gotta pound this Seafreak or whatever it's called.
I heard that!
Impressive. You're still on your
feet after one of my punches.
Clearly you're different from the rest of this trash.
Huh? Your punch was too weak, that's all.
Hey, someone else is over there.
Who is that? A hero?
That head...
I remember it from the Hero Registry.
I know him! He's a Class C rookie.
I think he's Rank 2.
Class C?
So we're still gonna get killed...
But that punch didn't hurt him at all.
That's your imagination.
You saw how many heroes were blown away
by that thing's punches, right?
I am the King of the deep, Lord of the seas.
All life on Earth comes from the sea, as if she were our mother.
In other words, as ruler of the seas,
I am the pinnacle of a pyramid
that includes every living organism on this world!
To defy me means—
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
It's raining out, so get on with it.
Whaattt?!
Awesome!
That was amazing!
Thank goodness!
He did it!
Well... that was lame. I kinda had my hopes up, too.
I'm back with my weapons.
But damn you, Deep Sea King. You got away.
Hey, what's that?
It is the mail.
The post office employees cannot come here, so a drone now delivers the mail.
The post office's drone?
No, it belongs to the Hero Association.
I see.
The public sends these to the heroes, much like fan letters.
Seriously? Are there any for me?
There are.
Oh! Let's go in and open them!
Damn it... I'll find out who sent it.
Here's a guy with free time.
All it took was one punch!
One punch! Just one!
Is he really Class C?
He's too strong!
Or maybe...
...the monster wasn't really that tough?
Yeah, but so many heroes went down.
That just means those heroes were weaklings.
Maybe... I suppose the monster didn't look all that tough when he killed it.
I mean, a Class C hero took it out with a single punch!
What's that say about the heroes it beat?
They may call themselves Class A or Class S,
but their titles don't mean a thing.
Hey, enough of that! They risked their lives for us!
Risked their lives? Anyone can do that.
But a "hero" has to beat monsters.
It all ended well this time, so whatever.
But it's annoying when heroes
who are really just average Joes
show up and try to save you.
If you're gonna call yourself a hero, then—
Shut your fat mouth!
Why are you getting mad at me?
The Hero Association gets their
funds from our donations, right?
As long as we're paying for it,
they'd better protect us.
The fact of the matter is
that bald guy pretty much took care of it all by himself.
All the other heroes did next to nothing.
Anyone can come up with a way to buy a little time.
In the end, the other "heroes" didn't do anything heroic.
I said shut up!
We were all saved. Is that not enough for you?
Exactly!
Today's my lucky day!
The other heroes wore the monster down, so beating it was kid's play!
Good thing I was late.
I barely did a thing and now I get all the credit.
Hey, spread the word, all of you!
I'm the one who finished the monster off!
I'll beat the snot out of anyone who says
it's only 'cause I got here late!
What's he mean?
The monster was already weak?
Huh...?
Hang on a sec. That's Saitama!
Saitama?
He's the hero from Z-City that everyone calls a cheat.
What? A cheat?
He appeared out of nowhere and climbed the ranks super-fast.
Yeah, pretty fishy.
Hey, you guys!
Look after the fallen heroes, okay?
If they die on me,
how am I gonna cash in on their work?
He is a cheat!
Man, that's no fair.
So he's just taking the credit?
Compared to him, the other heroes seem a little more heroic.
Where would we be now...
if the other heroes hadn't fought?
Yeah, I feel so grateful to them all...
Saitama-sensei...
Is this really what you want?
Oh, it stopped raining.
If this is the path you choose to walk, I will not interfere.
But in the future, if you are ever forced into a corner by this...
If that happens, I will—
Hey, there's one more.
Someone's thanking me.
It must be someone you saved.
I see. Any left?
There is one from the Hero Association.
The Association?
Are they firing me?
Well, whatever.
What's this? I'm Class C... rank 1?
So, why'd you call me in?
When you registered with the Hero Registry,
you were given the Association handbook.
Haven't you read it? It lists all our rules and regulations.
Yeah, I guess I've got it somewhere.
No matter. Congratulations on attaining rank 1 in Class C.
Hm? Oh, I see.
So you guys are the ones who decide the hero rankings.
There are more members on the review board,
but the four of us here today will be handling your interview.
Interview?
The top ranking Class C hero is given the option to be promoted to Class B.
However, if you wish to remain in Class C, that's fine too.
How about it, Saitama-kun?
Do you want to move up?
Although if you do, you'll be
ranked at the very bottom again.
Either way's fine, but I guess I'll try moving up.
There'll be no more weekly quotas that way.
Besides, I can't stick to Class C
forever with Genos in Class S.
I see, so you want the promotion.
First, we'll need you to answer some questions
and undergo a psychiatric analysis.
This Saitama-kun...
He's the one who finished off the Deep Sea King.
What do you think?
Some say he's a fraud...
He set new overall records in the fitness exam,
so his physical ability is solid.
Well, according to rumors,
he cheated on the exams, too.
Rumors are just rumors.
No sense in doubting him now.
The bottom line is that he wants to move up.
Why not let him go for now?
If he's for real, he'll make it in Class B.
But if he's a fake, he'll soon regret it.
He is entering a cruel and callous world.
We'll cross that bridge when we get to it.
Promotion to Class B?
You interrupted my filming for this?
It's not something that needs my attention.
This is a decision for the executive committee.
Listen.
I only want input on managing heroes Class A and above
since they have a strong impact on society.
As a hero in the same class,
if they're inadequate, it hurts my image too.
Especially this last incident...
It was beyond inadequate; it was appalling.
Don't you agree?
Speaking of social impact, the hero now wanting to move up
is the one who finished off the Deep Sea King.
Why the sour expressions?
That's no way to show off those cute faces!
You?!
I thought you were in prison!
I escaped just to see you!
Now... it's time for your Angel shots!
You guys! You need your meds!
So I'm Class B now...
Those tests took long enough.
Eh, not like I had to be somewhere.
Something smells good...
Welcome.
Assorted oden, please.
All right.
Want a drink?
If you're not drinking, let me buy you a plate.
Why?
That.
You were at the Association?
Let's celebrate your promotion.
Thanks.
For giving me a ride.
Should I walk?
N-No... I can handle it...
Hey, are you scared?
You got separated from the Class S hero, Genos, right?
The enemy is threat level Demon.
A monster so formidable that even if
the Class C and Class B heroes all
ganged up on him, they'd never win.
So if you wanna run...
Are you Class S too?
No, I'm Class C.
Laugh if you want to.
I'm not laughing.
Making those weekly quotas
sure is tough for us Class C's...
You're a funny guy.
I'm Mumen Rider. A hero, just like you.
Huh?
Hey! Watch it!
Oh! You're that guy!
I've been looking for you.
I couldn't say everything in my letter.
I see.
Maybe some mozuku then?
Hey! Give us your best mozuku!
Comin' right up!
It... it approaches!
Shibabawa-sama? What's wrong?
A violent catastrophe draws near...
Shibabawa-sama! Get a hold of yourself!
This is the end!
The Earth is doomed!
Eh? What is this place?
I am the Deep Sea King!
If I made one mistake, it was
not fighting the battle at sea.
An away game!
If we'd fought at sea, things would be different!
Next time: One Punch Man episode 10, "Unparalleled Peril".
Really? There's something even
more dangerous than me?