It's been five days since I debuted as a professional hero.
There haven't been any serious incidents so far.
However, for some reason Genos is staying at my house.
What are you writing over there?
I'm recording the details of your lessons and training regimen.
Crap. He's raising the bar again...
I can't think of a single thing I can teach the guy.
I feel bad, like I'm scamming him or something.
Come on, think. Or just make up some techniques or a spiritual theory.
Ugh, strength training is all I've got!
I know Genos won't be satisfied with that, plus the dude's a cyborg!
By the way.
At the seminar they said if you're a Class C hero
and you have no hero activity for a week,
your name will be removed from the Hero Registry.
Will you be all right, Sensei?
They said that?!
Yes.
But I was watching TV and there wasn't anything going on.
The news only reports major incidents,
like natural disasters, terrorism and dangerous monsters.
You always fight the most powerful enemies,
so you probably do not know it,
but Class C heroes primarily take care of purse snatchers,
robberies and random attacks.
With Class C so full of heroes,
in order to survive they must
actively look for cases to resolve.
I hear many of them get discouraged and change careers.
Like a salesman doing cold calls,
nothing will come your way without legwork.
This is no time to be reading manga!
So we're going?
You stay here!
If I'm with a Class S hero,
a Class C like me won't get any credit!
But as your student—
Genos, from the beginning my intense desire to be a hero
was what drove me to strength training.
That's how I made it this far.
For you, perhaps things will change if you aim higher as a hero.
Frankly speaking, you're a cyborg, so training your body won't do.
Instead, a change in mindset may lead you to greater strength.
Damn, I'm just making all this crap up...
So... in other words,
it's not about having raw power or technique,
it's about training your mind.
You must first fight your way through the professional hero industry.
Aim to break into the top ten of the Class S heroes.
That will be your goal for now.
I understand. I will try!
He bought it... thank goodness.
After that, I sped around town.
While frantically looking for bad guys...
I ran.
And ran.
But!
The city was quiet!
I give up...
Just one more day left.
Guess I'll head home.
I'll leave tomorrow's problems to tomorrow's me.
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
THE FOLLOWING DAY
It's quiet today too!
There's nothing to do!
I'm gonna lose my registration!
Hey! You're that guy...
What was it?
"Seed-on-the-Ground..."?
No wait, "Lost-and-Found..."?
Jack-o'-lantern Panic!
It's Speed-o'-Sound Sonic.
I've finally found you, Saitama.
Today is the day we—
Hey sorry, I'm busy. See you 'round...
Huh?
You think...
...you can run from me?!
What the—? I didn't see what happened.
His face should have been sliced open, but the blade...
I told you... I'm busy.
Plus I'm pissed, so anyone in my way...
...gets punched.
That's him!
He's very, very dangerous.
Please stop him.
So you're the offender, eh?!
Well, the hero Tank-Top Tiger is here now!
Hero?
Sonic, they think you're some sort of criminal.
Maybe getting tossed in a cell will cool off your hot—
She means you, baldy.
Huh?
He's been running around town
with this scary look on his face since yesterday!
But I'm a hero too!
I've never heard of a hero like you.
So what? I just started!
In any case, you're causing problems for everyone.
If you're really a hero, then don't go around frightening people.
You're hurting all the other heroes' reputation.
Hey, isn't that Tank-Top Tiger?
Oh yeah, it is Tank-Top Tiger.
No way!
Awesome, he's the real deal!
Even Class C heroes get recognized if they're in the top 10.
So how 'bout it, new guy?
Wanna go a little wild here and make me look good?
Exploding Shuriken.
EXPLODING
SHURIKEN
Tank-Top Tiger?!
Is this really happening?
What are you doing, Sonic?
He was interfering, so I put him to sleep.
Hey, call a hero!
A hero!
Run!
Saitama...
So you too have become one
of these worthless "heroes"?
Then all I have to do is create a situation
where you have no choice but
to fight me, Saitama the Hero!
Hail of Carnage!
Huh?
Hey! Cut it out!
Saitama, come stop me!
You're a hero!
I'll kill them all!
Damn it.
What's with everyone getting in my way?
I don't have time for this!
I gotta find a bad guy to take down.
A bad guy?
If you're not coming, I'll come to you!
I'm right here.
I wonder if this will count as work?
The man apprehended in Z-City by the Class C hero
is suspected of being involved in several heinous crimes,
including assassination.
Z-City...
What's the status of the investigation I requested?
The one for the ghost town?
Yes.
Let's see...
We've submitted an official request.
Well now, doesn't that sound interesting.
Want me to go?
Tatsumaki-san?
Where'd you come from?
Why? There a problem with me being here?
No...
But for Z-City, the investigation is just a formality.
What?
You think I'm not good enough?
Not at all.
The Association decided that
this was not a Class S matter.
Yes, exactly right.
You'd better tell me if you find
anything that looks like it can fight.
It'd be so much faster if I just went myself.
You're such an idiot.
A-CITY – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
At present, each location is being investigated.
First is Watchdog Man,
Class S hero, investigating Q-City.
"Nothing unusual".
Nothing unusual?
That's right.
That's hard to believe.
We all know Q-City is a hot zone
with more casualties and monsters than any other area.
Knowing him, I'm sure he's implying that,
"Whatever occurs, I'll be able to take care of it".
Though he has focused his efforts on Q-City,
his track record at monster elimination is top-notch.
Class S heroes don't pay much attention to details.
They're not cut out for writing reports.
Next, W-City.
Class A hero Heavy Kong reports: "Nothing unusual"
for H-City, reports from Mushroom for Class B, and Horsebone, Class C!
"Nothing unusual".
For D-City, Lightning Genji, Class A, says
"Slow restoration after the devastation caused by
the gigantic creature aside. Nothing unusual".
Cities B and D both sustained extensive damage.
The Association took a lot of heat for that.
In order to prevent more such disasters,
we must detect any covert activity
that could threaten the community.
Well, this investigation was requested for that express purpose.
But early detection of monsters is proving difficult.
F-City, Class A hero, "Snakebite" Snek.
"Hammerhead, former leader of
the Paradiser terrorist group,
has been spotted in a suit and tie.
Further investigation is being conducted".
No other reports.
What of Z-City?
I hear rumblings of a potential disaster brewing
in the abandoned area there.
No reports available.
However, two highly capable Class A heroes
have been sent to the area to investigate.
Here we are in Z-City.
CLASS A, RANK 33
SPRING MUSTACHIO
Shall we begin our little inquiry?
CLASS A, RANK 29
GOLDEN BALL
Yeah, let's get on with it.
Z-City is quite expansive, but further ahead lies
the uninhabited area we were told about.
Compared with other areas,
BEWARE OF
MONSTERS!!
Z-City has an abnormally high rate of monster-related incidents.
The frequency has been gradually increasing over the past 10 years,
while the last few have seen more and more highly advanced monsters appearing.
The residents have entirely fled for the city center.
I know all that.
The place is a real ghost town,
just with the water and electricity still intact, yeah?
On the lookout for a cheap house?
Come off it.
People say something real nasty's living 'round here.
Even you must've heard.
But of course.
I assume that's why we have
been assigned this investigation.
Once we hit the abandoned area,
we better be ready to fight.
Indeed, we mustn't let our guard down.
But, why here?
Why the increase in monsters here?
That's the mystery.
Many theories have been advanced, but my own is this:
A colony of monsters here is naturally producing more of them.
Or perhaps a Queen exists, birthing more of her kind.
Of course I have no proof yet,
but there is something to this ghost town...
Or rather, something in it.
Of that you can be sure.
The proximity alarm?
If we can hunt down this mysterious being,
we'll go straight to the top of the rankings.
That's true.
We can't let Amai Mask-san remain first for—
Something's there?!
Was that a monster?
No way to be sure...
But it's hard to imagine a human still living in these conditions.
Let's pursue it!
Seems they are not after us.
Is this be the place I heard about?
Sure don't seem like it...
Aw man, I came all this way. Isn't anyone around?
A monster. It popped up out of nowhere.
Golden Ball-san, are you ready?
Hell yeah!
Victory to the swift!
Hey, people!
I can blast through a 20mm steel plate
with one of my shape-memory golden bullets!
Eat this!
He flicked it away like nothing.
Golden!
Wow!
Tomboy...
...Thrust!
It slipped past my Tomboy?
Not bad.
Those tentacles...
From the way they react, they're tough as steel.
A monster that can use its infinite number of tentacles
like steel whips...
Such power!
I must call in reinforcements from the Association.
May I ask if you were born in this neighborhood?
Nah, I'm from out of town.
I heard a bunch of crazy strong monsters were all getting together here.
Looks like it was just a rumor though.
But now,
I feel like it'd be kinda fun to stick around and make the rumor true.
"The Ghost Town Monster..."
It's got a nice ring to it!
We have a backup request from the heroes dispatched to Z-City.
Class A rank 29, Golden Ball, has been knocked out.
Class A rank 33, Spring Mustachio, is in trouble.
They're in the abandoned city.
Call in all nearby heroes for immediate assistance!
Class A and above!
See the monster alert for Z-City?
The threat level seems to be Tiger or higher.
Is it the ghost town monster?
They're not sure yet.
I'll go...
I want to catch the tiger by its tail.
Now I see...
If it means running into monsters like this all the time
I wouldn't want to live here either.
Man, boring. This is boring me!
I finally kick a hero's butt and I
don't get even a single scream.
Now that I think about it, even if I start living here,
I'll never be famous if there's no people.
Guess I'll keep going. Gotta find where they live.
There's somebody.
Another hero?
Or a regular guy?
I thought all the humans cleared out.
If all those monsters were really around,
there's no way he could live here...
I guess that means it was just a rumor.
Shoot...
I forgot to buy konbu soup stock.
Sensei, I saw a lot of konbu right outside the door.
Oh yeah, I just...
just happened... to get it for cheap.
Yes, people say that konbu is good for hair growth,
but since there is no real scientific proof,
its real effects are yet to be confirmed.
I did some research, so I am sure, Sensei.
For example, according to this site—
No one said anything about hair!
Z-City Investigative Report.
"Nothing noteworthy about the downtown or residential areas.
During our investigation,
we encountered a ferocious monster in the abandoned area,
but were unable to exterminate it.
We escaped death,
but the monster we encountered disappeared
and it is possible that it still roams the area.
Also, according to this monster, there's a rumor that...
...powerful monsters already exist in this area."
Sounds like it was pretty brutal.
A monster?
Y-Yes.
I think I'll pass this time.
See? I told you I should have gone!
But...
faced with this,
I'm sure even you would have had a tough time.
I would have been fine, idiot!
The rumor has not been confirmed, but the reinforcements saw signs
that point to the existence of some horrible monstrosity.
Holy crap, what is this?
What kind of monster could cause such violence?
I'd hate to face off against this thing.
Hey, what's this?
Is it a part of the monster Spring Mustachio fought?
There may have been a territorial dispute
between the monsters...
Seems like there's definitely "something" here.
We must continue our investigation and maintain vigilance over Z-City.
Hey, did you hear?
There are monsters living in the Z-City ghost town.
Yeah, rumor has it the toughest ones are secretly plotting something.
No, no. Not that rumor.
It's about a more dangerous monster.
What's that?
You didn't hear?
I hear the place has now become terrifying
for both humans and monsters.
THE TERRIFYING CITY
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I close my eyes and think of you
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I want to see you... I feel like crying
romantikku na kibun
I feel so romantic
todokete kono omoi
I hope these feelings reach you
datte zutto shitteiru no
I know very well
ganbatteru koto takusan
how hard you work all the time
daisuki na hito ga
You're the one I love
tsuyokute shinpai
You're so strong but I'm still worried
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
I'll find you before any stars
massugu kaette kite ne
Come back home straight
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
Sensei, I filled in the holes in front of the house.
Oh, thanks!
Also,
your rank has gone up from last place, 388th, to 342nd.
Oh? Because of that Panic guy?
He boosted my ranking.
So it's been a week now.
Have you done anything?
No, not yet.
I guess it's only been a week.
I'm still ranked last in Class S for ability... in 17th place.
Sounds like you've still got a
lot of training to do, Genos.
But in the public polls, for popularity I rank number six.
Why?!
"A genius who, at the tender age of 19, made his debut in Class S."
"He'll do great."
"He's so handsome."
"Love how he refuses to do media interviews. Very cool."
Those kinds of comments.
You're not embarrassed to read those out loud?
These comments are based on
impressions from my photo,
not evaluations of me.
I think nothing of them.
Oh yeah?
They continue.
"The Cyborg Prince."
"Behind the steely exterior, I feel his fragile self."
"Among the top five most handsome heroes."
Enough already!
Next
Time
The
Ultimate
Student
My name is Fubuki.
Perhaps you know me better as "Blizzard of Hell"?
Well, I only had a bit part this episode.
Next time: One Punch Man episode 7,
"The Ultimate Student".
The Blizzard Group will finally make its appearance.
Fubuki-sama, we're not scheduled to go on next week!
That can't be right!