nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon
tameiki ga mikazuki wo yurasu yoru wa
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
me wo tojite kimi no koto kangaete bakari
I close my eyes and think of you
aitai kibun nakitai kibun
I want to see you... I feel like crying
romantikku na kibun
I feel so romantic
todokete kono omoi
I hope these feelings reach you
datte zutto shitteiru no
I know very well
ganbatteru koto takusan
how hard you work all the time
daisuki na hito ga
You're the one I love
tsuyokute shinpai
You're so strong but I'm still worried
watashi ni dake wa yowasa misete
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
hoshi yori saki ni mitsukete ageru
I'll find you before any stars
massugu kaette kite ne
Come back home straight
nee hayaku kaette kite ne
Hey, come back home soon